<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Reviews Archive - MrStocks.org</title>
	<atom:link href="/review/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/review/</link>
	<description>Best Online Brokers for Free Stock Trading</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 19:55:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>
	<item>
		<title>IBKR Interactive Brokers Review</title>
		<link>/review/ibkr-interactive-brokers/</link>
					<comments>/review/ibkr-interactive-brokers/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Maximilian Weber]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 13:08:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.commissionfreetrading.net/?post_type=affiliates&#038;p=360</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From a broker comparison you will find in the best case the test winner and the top broker that offers its investors the most favorable conditions and the most diverse trading instruments possible. In this article, we want to look at the Interactive Brokers experience. This is one of the largest online brokers that currently [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/review/ibkr-interactive-brokers/">IBKR Interactive Brokers Review</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">MrStocks.org</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From a broker comparison you will find in the best case the test winner and the top broker that offers its investors the most favorable conditions and the most diverse trading instruments possible. In this article, we want to look at the Interactive Brokers experience. This is one of the largest online brokers that currently exist on the market for domestic and international trading. Accordingly, you can access a wide range of trading instruments. This includes ETFs, futures as well as stocks and CFDs, commodities and currencies as well as options. With this following guide, we would like to help you get started with Interactive Brokers and answer the most frequently asked questions.</p>
<h2>Who is Interactive Brokers?</h2>
<p>Interactive Brokers is abbreviated as IB. The predecessor of this online broker is Timber Hill. It is an American stock broker founded by Thomas Peterffy in 1977. Today it remains to say that Timber Hill was one of the first brokers to work on the American Stock Exchange market and the trading floor with the portable computers. The associated GmbH in Germany was founded in 1990. At that time, the main focus was on electronic trading with regard to the German Futures Exchange, or DTB for short. This became Eurex a little later. In 1993, Timber Hill and Interactive Brokers merged to form Trader Workstation &#8211; TWS.</p>
<p>Already in 1997, the volume of equity derivatives listed on the stock exchange at Timber Hill online included 5% worldwide. In total, the broker came up with 15,000 transactions. A respectable selection, considering that the digital market was still in its infancy at that time. Already in 2000, an average of 6% of the global volume was traded via this network. In 2001, Timber Hill GmbH changed its name to Interactive Brokers Group LLC.</p>
<p>In 2003, the company was already executing 12,000 of the world&#8217;s listed index and stock transactions. In 2007 the company went public. Per share, Interactive Brokers issued $30.01. Today, the company is listed on the NASDAQ with the abbreviation IBKR.Anyone who is extensively involved in securities trading and wants to learn more about the shares and international trading, can not get past the Interactive Brokers.</p>
<div class="slider-carousel-group"><h5>Screenshots</h5><div class="owl-carousel carousel-screenshot"></div></div>
<h3>Top brokers in price and revenue worldwide</h3>
<p>Time and again Interactive Brokers top the ranking for the cheapest brokers, the last time the broker climbed the podium in 2009 in terms of the cheapest brokers. This was the fifth time in a row. In 2009, the provider also launched its trading app iTWS, which was available for the iPhone. In the statistics, it came out that the prices keep improving when it comes to the US stocks and the options. Whereas the THG statistics is an independent analysis, which in turn is carried out by the company IHS Market.</p>
<p>In 2011 Interactive Brokers was selected among the largest US online brokers when it comes to the average yield of transactions per day. In technical terminology, we are talking about the so-called Daily Average Revenue Trades. For investors, it is precisely these revenues that play a decisive role. That with the most favorable online broker, which on the trading platform only small yields are made. Basically, investors want to get the maximum out of their assets with an online broker. According to relevant Interactive Brokers experience, this is easily possible with this provider.</p>
<p>Since 2011, there has been a new user interface on the Trader Workstation with the TWS Mosaic interface. In 2017, the broker received the award for the fifth time as the best online broker in trade magazines such as Barrons. Worldwide, more than 1400 employees work on the TWS Mosaic interface &#8211; every day, investors execute over 1 million transactions with this online broker. Thus, this provider alone has an equity capital of a considerable 5 billion US dollars. These are enormous values, with which almost no German online broker and certainly no Neo Broker can keep up. However, first and foremost, this provider is all about stability, years of experience and the wide range of products that traders benefit from.</p>
<p>This company is known for its very conservative approach and business policy. For this reason, Interactive Brokers has also not been directly affected by the financial crisis, making significant losses. For years, this company has been operating consistently and profitably, regardless of the political and economic movements on the world stage. This is remarkable and today it ensures that more and more users find their way to Trader Workstation.</p>
<p>What markets can be traded at Interactive Brokers?</p>
<p>One of the direct benefits is the market access to options, forex, futures and stocks as well as the fixed income securities, CFDs and ETFs. All this is possible only with an account at Interactive Brokers. In turn, the broker allows its traders to trade with over 125 international exchanges, spread across 31 countries. The most popular exchanges include Europe, North America, Asia and Australia. Interactive Brokers brings all these linking points together in the Trader Workstation.</p>
<p>Additionally, traders can trade ETFs in 26 countries. Commodities, futures and options are offered in 35 market centers worldwide. More than 15 trading options are available to the trader. In addition, the complex financial instruments such as CFDs are applicable to all available and common stocks, currencies and indices. Currently, the current offer in this area includes 7,250 stocks. With regard to Forex trading, Interactive Brokers scores with 100 currency pairs.</p>
<h2>Security: How is Interactive Brokers regulated?</h2>
<p>In fact, there is no minimum deposit at this online broker. You can get in from very low stakes, which should appeal to private investors in particular. At the same time, Interactive Brokers never puts the safety of its investors at risk. The Financial Conduct Authority is entrusted with the regulation and supervision of Interactive Brokers. Due to the legal and worldwide supervision, the common risks can be avoided. In this way, Interactive Brokers performs well in the test, as does Trader Workstation.</p>
<p>Attention: Currently there is no legally regulated deposit insurance. This is not because Interactive Brokers does not care about the safety of their investors&#8217; deposits from Europe. It is a certified company from the USA, which does not fall under the legislation of Europe. According to it, all the accounts are managed as so-called segregated accounts. Interactive Brokers stores its own assets separately from the investors&#8217; assets, thus providing massive security.</p>
<p>In addition to these segregated accounts between Interactive Brokers and equity &#8211; the US Securities Investor Protection Corporation (SIPC) steps in if the very unlikely event occurs and IB goes bust. All other non-U.S. territory positions and cash positions can be protected and hedged again through a U.K. company. Sudeck, the Financial Services Compensation Scheme (FSCS), protects the assets of 50,000 British pounds.</p>
<h3>How can I register a demo account with Interactive Brokers?</h3>
<p>It is very easy on the home page to open a demo account without any complications. This can be done directly from a menu bar at the top of the screen in the right corner. You can recognize the demo account by the inscription Free Demo. Next to it is the Open account button. This step should be taken later, when you are satisfied with the offer and trading and want to deposit your own money into the account.</p>
<p>Based on the Interactive Brokers test, the account opening process is straightforward and very fast online. For this, you need to have a few important information ready to completely fill out your personal account starting from the Interactive Brokers experience. This includes the name with the appropriate</p>
<p>proof of identity,<br />
the address,<br />
the place of residence,<br />
the country of birth and<br />
the date of birth and<br />
citizenship.</p>
<p>Where are you resident for tax purposes? In addition to this, Interactive Brokers asks for your name and address from your employer and would like to receive information about your personal income and five assets. What are your securities trading experience and investment goals? The online brokers are required to put investors through their paces. This is to avoid the risk of a beginner simply putting a lot of money without knowing about each financial instrument, its features and risks.</p>
<h3>The conditions at Interactive Brokers</h3>
<p>At Interactive Brokers, investors are offered tight spreads, which are accompanied by strengthened liquidity and very good conditions. This applies, for example, to foreign exchange trading. A market share of more than 60% on the global Internet banking market speaks for this provider. In fact, through Interactive Brokers it is possible to provide the cost quotes with an accuracy of one tenth PiP.</p>
<p>Among the most popular traded products at this broker are.</p>
<p>ETFs,<br />
warrants,<br />
futures and<br />
options and<br />
stocks.</p>
<p>There are two different commission models at Interactive Brokers, such as the tiered model, where fees decrease as trading volume increases. Alternatively, Interactive Brokers allows investors to calculate and set a fixed price commission for each financial product. Alternatively, there is a percentage trade value that is recalculated depending on the trade value. Basically, it should be about bringing you the fixed terms through Interactive Brokers that fit your trading behavior and budget.</p>
<div class="ups-downs"><h5>Pros / Cons</h5><div class="row"><div class="col-md-6 col-sm-12"><div class="icon green"><i class="fa fa-chevron-up" aria-hidden="true"></i></div><ul></ul></div><div class="col-md-6 col-sm-12"><div class="icon red"><i class="fa fa-chevron-down" aria-hidden="true"></i></div><ul></ul></div></div></div>
<h2>How much does it cost to trade through Interactive Brokers?</h2>
<p>You can trade the US stocks from $0.05 per share. The mini malst of the fee is one US dollar. The fees for German stocks are 0.1% calculated on the transaction volume. Interactive Brokers charges a minimum fee of four euros per order and is therefore not the cheapest online broker in a direct comparison. The commissions for the options depend on the volume of the contract at Interactive Brokers. You can access the German stock options with this US online broker for a fee of 1.10 euros per contract. For example, Interactive Brokers offers the safe DAX, which comes with a commission of 1.70 euros.</p>
<p>The cost of the futures options or the US futures ranks at around $0.85, which is per contract. For the German futures, you pay Interactive Brokers a fee of two euros per contract. The commissions that accrue when trading forex through this broker are again dependent on the amount traded each month. It is best to call up the current price-performance list directly from Interactive Brokers. In the Interactive Brokers test, the provider scores with transparency and a clear listing of the costs and fees that investors have to pay plus if you work with one of the market leaders.</p>
<p>Index CFDs cost from 0.005% at Interactive Brokers, which in turn accrue per execution. If the view goes to the European shares and CFDs, the commissions amount to 0.02% or else to 0.05%, which again applies to each execution of the broker. This is also true for CFD trading, here the fees you pay to Interactive Brokers are the same. If you hold the CFD positions beyond the close of the market, you will have to pay interest for each day. It is a blended rate that is payable depending on the amounts.</p>
<h2>Interactive Brokers leverage and margin requirements.</h2>
<p>There is a European Securities and Markets Authority since August 1, 2018, which are referred to as ESMA. This authority specifies so-called thresholds. In return, Interactive Brokers commits to liquidate these open positions and thus provide qualified capital. In addition, Interactive Brokers determines chief positions and margin requirements. This is the amount of collateral that an investor must bring to speculate with a certain capital and dispose of his money on the exchange.</p>
<p>In August 1, 2018, there are going out from Europe and the Securities and Markets Authority thresholds. These refer to the minimum inclusions. In this regard, Interactive Brokers undertakes to liquidate all open positions. This is the case whenever the qualifying capital of the CFD account falls below the 50% mark. What is meant is the margin requirement that applies to all CFD positions. In addition, there are the in-house requirements of Interactive Brokers from the UK. These go back to the historical volatility of the underlying assets as well as individual influencing factors. These are the main requirements that are attached to the trade. It doesn&#8217;t matter whether trading is done in Euros or USD. The margin requirements for all equity CFDs are set at 20% with regard to retail clients. The margin requirement also applies in this area. The minimum of the large in indices is 5%. Otherwise, the minimum requirements are 10%.</p>
<p>In addition, there are further margin requirements at Interactive Brokers Group as far as the major forex pairs are concerned. This is set at 3.33%. You can trade the smaller currency pairs starting from a margin of 5%. In addition, there are so-called exotic currency pairs at Interactive Brokers UK, which in turn oscillate between 10 and 15%.</p>
<p>For the DAX futures, for example, the margin requirements come to €13,491 and with regard to the over night values to €26,983. However, these values can also be adjusted depending on volatility. Thus, they can be higher depending on the daily level. For the US Dollar/Euro, the spread at the broker Interactive Brokers is 0.01 Pip. As for the competition, Interactive Brokers U.K. Limited can not be faulted in terms of service. Thus, as a customer, you do not pay a cent for the deposit and services. You can also trade securities with the staff on the phone and do not have to expect any additional costs here.</p>
<h2>Does Interactive Brokers automatically deduct the final withholding tax?</h2>
<p>With this provider, the final withholding tax is not withheld. This means for the traders, that you make your entire capital including profits and earnings available in full for further investments. In the following year, it is then the taxpayer&#8217;s responsibility to declare the investment income from Interactive Brokers in the personal tax return.</p>
<p>The custody account management at Interactive Brokers llc is carried out in Great Britain. This brings with it a distinct advantage: you do not have to pay the final withholding tax until the end of the year in your tax return. You do not need an exemption order at Interactive Brokers.</p>
<p>At Interactive Brokers there is a hedge fund portal. This is a portal in the online version, which is fundamentally different from the traditional Capital Introduction program. As a client of Interactive Brokers you can market the funds as a qualified buyer or investor. As one of the leading CFD brokers, the provider convinces all along the line with transparent services and a wide range of investment opportunities.</p>
<h2>What about the experience with Interactive Brokers?</h2>
<p>It remains to be said that the experience with this broker is very good. Traders are positive about the services and the offer as well as the security. They can trade stocks and CFD per order at a reasonable price and keep track while trading. Customers thus benefit from good support at this broker, which is available in many different languages. Each broker who is part of the team brings an experience of over 20 years.</p>
<p>Especially in the area of custody, pricing and execution, the platform scores with strong services for all German customers and on the international level. This leads to consistently positive experiences, which is not least due to the comprehensive offer for all customers.</p>
<p>Especially in the training area, you can take seminars, webinars and tutorials without fees. A free demo account forms the rounding off, for all beginners who first want to get an overview of the securities, index CFD investments and Forex investments. A customer does not have to pay any fees with a demo account yet and can benefit from the comprehensive range in the securities account and on the platform.</p>
<h3>Contact the customer service of Interactive Brokers</h3>
<p>Every customer has the possibility to contact the German trading platform directly via email and receive an answer from the support within a few hours. In addition, there is the possibility of contact via chat, telephone and digitally. Of course, the trade desk is also available at any time. In this way, questions and problems should be resolved as quickly as possible. The platform is logically and intuitively structured, so you will find comprehensive information on the individual CFD options and investment opportunities.</p>
<h3>Deposit and withdrawal at Interactive Brokers</h3>
<p>Based on the current experience, the management of the Forex account is smooth, which also applies to the deposit and withdrawal. You need a deposit memo to deposit money into your account. You set this note directly in the account management. In most cases, the deposit will take no longer than two business days to be credited to a securities account. For withdrawal you need a reference account at Interactive Brokers, which you specify when opening the account. When trading, you can make a withdrawal at any time. The duration of the transfer depends on the credit institution or bank you are a customer of. Interactive Brokers offers a comprehensive and customer-friendly service, which stands for short times and quick solutions.</p>
<p>On the German trading platform you really use very practical trading tools for free. For example, Interactive Brokers offers the trading software Trader Workstation &#8211; TWS for short. In this context, numerous analysis options are available to you. With it, you can, for example, observe the development of the prices and how the stocks and futures as well as the Forex investments change. Let the platform show you the key figures and profiles and the Forex data to analyze them and draw conclusions for your own strategies when trading. In addition, you have insights into the order book and time and sales at any time.</p>
<p>When trading, you can also use Chart Trader. It is a real-time chart that you can adjust to your needs via 70 indicators. Another beginner-friendly tool in trading is Book Trader. Through it, you can quickly enter and submit your orders. It only takes a few clicks for you to select an order in the order book and then submit it to the appropriate exchange. Basket Trader is a trading tool that allows you to create an index of securities and trade them simultaneously. You can change all the values in a basket or in an index at any time. Thus, the tool is suitable for the investors who trade different positions simultaneously at regular intervals through the platform.</p>
<p>In addition, you can use the Portfolio option. This tool is a kind of risk profile that allows you to keep an eye on the Forex options. You can set your some goals and analyze the data based on that.<br />
In addition, Interactive Brokers has a programming interface &#8211; API for short. With it you can create your own trading software. In most cases, however, you will need several years of experience and knowledge in the programming language and in terms of programming protocol in trading.<br />
For those who want to trade on the go, iBot is recommended. This is a text-based or voice-based interface, but it is only suitable for desktop trailers with corresponding years of experience. You get all the information you need through this platform in the test. In this way, you have the opportunity to complete trading and place your own orders with your own voice.<br />
The iBot understands voice commands and text commands if they are in an easily understandable language. In the test, it then immediately delivers the information. You do not have to use a specific sentence structure or technical language for this. In principle, CFD trading and social trading is about using such tools to make trading even easier and more enjoyable.<br />
Trader Workstation TWS &amp; the Option Trading</p>
<p>A powerful tool allows you to trade options at will. We are talking about Trader Workstation TWS. You make the analyses according to any price criteria and can have the data displayed visually. This includes the respective risks and Cinar Yen with regard to the call and put options, which they set for the maturity and for certain time periods. Interaktiv Brokers offers a matched returns and risk profile for individual trading strategies with this options portfolio and algorithm. Cost-effective social trading solutions are to be found above.</p>
<h2>Interactive Broker Experience: The strengths at a glance</h2>
<p>Interactive Brokers offers US stocks and indices. The IB Risk Navigator is available for comprehensive security. It is a risk management platform. You can take a look at trading through it. In addition, the Interactive Brokers algorithm takes a look at the current risk situation. Especially about the options portfolio, the algorithm allows an extremely cost-effective solution to achieve your set goals in trading. Furthermore, Interactive Brokers has Securities and Exchange Commission for comprehensive security and Commodity Futures Trading Commission &#8211; which in turn ensures control and regulation over the EU.</p>
<p>Continuously, the algorithm knows the entire market and then provides the latest results every 30 seconds. This way you can&#8217;t miss anything. With this CFD broker, you can be sure that the best results will always appear on the dashboard. For German customers, this is an absolute must, because in the test you only trust the safest brokers. In the data query you have the possibility to change the details again and again and automatically adjust the list of results. Attention, you will lose money with any Forex broker if you do not inform yourself about the risks beforehand.</p>
<p>Deposit protection is available via the mobile version and the desktop version of Interactive Brokers is available. This includes EU regulation and protection of their personal assets. In the event of insolvency, your financial assets are fully protected to a certain extent via the deposit insurance. You do not run any risk here with the certified brokers like Brokers Interactive. In addition, you use their depot free of charge.</p>
<h3>Analysis &amp; optimization of trading options</h3>
<p>Among the complex option orders is the option strategy lab. These, in turn, work on the basis of prices and volatility. Based on this, you create forecasts that help you to assess the dangers logically and place your money effectively via a test. Based on this, a list of acute trading strategies appears online for German clients. In the current test, you have the option to order the results according to different criteria with the CFD broker. Filter by the respective strike price and maturity date, as well as the premium.</p>
<p>If you the potential profits and losses over the scan results off. About it you get an overview of the ratios of risk and return in the practical test. The CFD broker offers you via this chart a comparison option for the current performance and the Forex strategies that sSe can be displayed graphically.</p>
<p>This includes components for the strategy and for the details and parameters that affect a Forex or CFD order in the test. Pay attention to how the fees are in terms of currencies. For example, it makes a difference whether you use Euros, US dollars/ USD or British pounds. Depending on how many USD per order you sit, you can then determine the losses or gains when translating to the other currency consequently. With regard to USD, you have the possibility to start from 0.65 Euro per order. A minimum deposit of 10,000 USD is associated with these stakes.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>IB Test: Research and Extras</p>
<p>Another unique selling point with this broker is the comprehensive market analysis and news subscriptions. This is accompanied by a handy research platform through which the CFD broker helps its investors to invest the money in the most profitable way. TWS is such a practical feature through which the CFD broker summarizes and makes available its most important news and data. In addition, practical research services are available for you to choose from free of charge. Of course, you can use these as a beginner via the demo version right after opening the account with this Forex broker.</p>
<p>Beware: you will lose money if you do not inform yourself sufficiently about CFD investments and the impact of margin beforehand. Anyway, you should only use free capital. About the deposit insurance, the assets are protected. However, you can always lose your money if the prices and the order do not turn out as you expected.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Interactive Brokers Experience &amp; Education</p>
<p>Online, the platform offers not only deposit protection and EU regulation, this broker scores with a wide range of education. Take a look at the Trader Academy, this is peppered with helpful services and products. In the education center you can access practical digital tools as well as a filter bubble, in which difficult terms are explained.</p>
<p>At the latest when you have taken a look at the Trader Education Center at this Forex broker, you will understand the digital tools around financial products as well as regulation and margin much better.</p>
<p>In the courses you can acquire a comprehensive knowledge. To do so, access the technical analysis and fundamental analysis section. Here you will find various practical tools that will help you navigate the platform.</p>
<p>You gain access to Interactive Brokers webinars as soon as you open a securities account on the platform. Here, the most common trading topics are available to you. You can actually have all the world markets explained to you in a few minutes. In addition, you should use the IBKR video tutorial for yourself. Behind it are a variety of different courses in which you can learn more about various topics, such as the Trader Workstation or the various TWS trading tools. Furthermore, you can learn about stocks, options, futures, securities and bonds in this area. Get to know the individual tools better step by step and also access this area in the app. The essential terms are explained in more detail in the IBKR glossary.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The Interactive Brokers App</p>
<p>Interactive Brokers offers a trading app &#8211; IBKR Mobile. The application is available once through the Google Playstore and through the Apple Store. It combines in itself all the essential functions in a mobile app and can be accessed through your own account. Of course, you can also trade via the app. Use the trading tools and control all order types on the go.</p>
<p>From now on, you are always available on the go and always have all 50 data sources at hand. Here, too, the TWS trading platform scores across the board. The advantages are immediately obvious, via the mobile app you can trade futures, stocks and options as well as currencies and bonds on the go. You call up all charts and streaming quotes in real time, giving you a compact overview of your stocks.</p>
<p>Note: Based on the Financial Conduct Authority (FCA), every investor has the chance to be classified as a retail client or a professional client. The broker Interactive Brokers UK can also voluntarily classify a client as a professional. The prerequisite for this is a qualitative review and test. This is accompanied by further discounts and lucrative investment opportunities with regard to the Magin, the mobile app at the Forex broker and the CFD offers.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>What do investors pay Interactive Brokers in case of inactivity?</p>
<p>Basically, there are no account maintenance fees on the trading platform for the account you open. If the investor&#8217;s commissions exceed 10 USD in a calendar month or if the account capital is over 100,000 USD per calendar month, the whole thing remains free of charge as well. If the account does not meet these criteria, Interactive Brokers charges a fee of 10 USD. By and large, the provider remains transparent in all areas.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/review/ibkr-interactive-brokers/">IBKR Interactive Brokers Review</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">MrStocks.org</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/review/ibkr-interactive-brokers/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Robinhood Review</title>
		<link>/review/robinhood/</link>
					<comments>/review/robinhood/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Maximilian Weber]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2017 15:20:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://demos.pokatheme.com/pokatheme/?post_type=affiliates&#038;p=238</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>You&#8217;re probably familiar with the legendary heroic character &#8220;Robin Hood&#8221; who lived in Sherwood Forest near Nottingham, according to the English folklore. Robin regularly fought his enemy, the Sheriff of Nottingham. He is famous for dressing in green, his archer skills, and his habit of taking from the rich to gift the poor. In this [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/review/robinhood/">Robinhood Review</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">MrStocks.org</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>You&#8217;re probably familiar with the legendary heroic character &#8220;Robin Hood&#8221; who lived in Sherwood Forest near Nottingham, according to the English folklore. Robin regularly fought his enemy, the Sheriff of Nottingham. He is famous for dressing in green, his archer skills, and his habit of taking from the rich to gift the poor.</p>
<p>In this case, however, Robinhood is an online trading platform that offers vast ways for traders to invest in self-directed accounts through the Web or mobile appliances. The broker enables you to perform an unlimited number of commission-free trading in stocks, options, funds, and cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>Robinhood burst onto the assets trading scene in 2015, with their competitive edge being the <strong>commission-free stocks and ETFs trading</strong>.</p>
<p>If you have been in the trading market, you understand that commissions are a costly part of the business. Generally, commissions are payments to the broker for the sale or purchase of stocks. They are a massive chunk of the broker&#8217;s profits.</p>
<p>Commission fees range from $3.95- $19.99 per trade.</p>
<p>Robinhood states, &#8220;Our mission is to democratize access to the financial markets.&#8221; That, coupled with its mobile-first approach, gave this broker an edge over most competitors.</p>
<p>While Robinhood has been mired in controversy recently, it continues to be popular among traders due to its minimal brokerage fees.</p>
<p>In 2018, Robinhood allowed its users to trade cryptocurrencies (Bitcoin and Ether). The platform has since added more coins to its wallet.</p>
<p>In this review, we look at the platform at large, including its regulations, reputation, customer support, fees, and more.</p>
<p>Let’s get started.</p>
<div class="slider-carousel-group"><h5>Screenshots</h5><div class="owl-carousel carousel-screenshot"><div class="item">
                    <a href="" class="lightbox"><img decoding="async" src="  " alt="Screenshot"/></a>
                </div><div class="item">
                    <a href="" class="lightbox"><img decoding="async" src="  " alt="Screenshot"/></a>
                </div><div class="item">
                    <a href="" class="lightbox"><img decoding="async" src="  " alt="Screenshot"/></a>
                </div><div class="item">
                    <a href="" class="lightbox"><img decoding="async" src="  " alt="Screenshot"/></a>
                </div><div class="item">
                    <a href="" class="lightbox"><img decoding="async" src="  " alt="Screenshot"/></a>
                </div></div></div>
<h2>Robinhood Review: Overview</h2>
<p>Robinhood (formally known as Robinhood Markets Inc) is a United States-based financial service company founded in 2013 by two Stanford classmates. High-frequency traders (HFTs) themselves, the Stanford graduates realized commission-free trading is possible and sought to bring it to the individual investor.</p>
<p>The platform began as a waiting list. After a month, it had 100 000 members on the list. It is headquartered in Menio Park, California.</p>
<p>Robinhood aims to make asset trading more affordable, easier to access, and intuitive for all investors – regardless of their experience level. Users can manage their financial assets and portfolio anywhere in the world – except in a few countries. That is made possible by the Robinhood app for iOS and Android devices.</p>
<p>Moreover, the users can keep up to date with their investments upon setting (customized and flexible) news and notification alerts.</p>
<h2>Robinhood Gold</h2>
<p>Over the years, the platform has expanded its web version, rolled out Robinhood Crypto, and built up its Options Trading Services. While it falls short on its word – taking from the rich and giving to the poor – the platform is shaking up the online trading industry.</p>
<p>Besides fee-free stocks, Robinhood also offers easy to use cash management account through which users can earn interest and pay their bills with a Mastercard debit card. In addition, users can withdraw cash from 75,000+ ATMs for free. Moreover, there are no foreign transaction fees, no transfer fees, and no account minimums.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the cash in the bank program is eligible for up to $1.25 million of Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation (FDIC) insurance. Or up to $250K per bank, subject to FDIC rules.</p>
<h2>Commission free</h2>
<p><strong>Progress</strong></p>
<p>In December 2019, the trading platform announced that its app had surpassed 10 million customers. As such, Robinhood has a large customer base despite its late entry into the financial service industry.</p>
<p>In six years, the broker has impacted the financial industry by lowering prices and making investments more affordable and accessible and easy to use to young people. The broker is quickly becoming a client favorite with its zero account minimums and zero-commission ETF and stock trading.</p>
<p>In fact, the broker is considered a significant threat to competitors that are forced to quickly change and adapt their structures and strategies to remain competitive. This change is clearly seen in the acquisition of TD Ameritrade by Charles Schwab, as announced in November 2019.</p>
<p>This $26 billion all-stock deal has led to a 12 million increase in Schwab’s client base, as well as $1.3 trillion in customer assets. In total, the acquisition gives the firm over $5 trillion in assets and 24 million client accounts.</p>
<h2>Stocks ETFs Options</h2>
<p>See, commission fees have, for a long time now, driven online trading companies. With the rising popularity of Robinhood’s zero-commission strategy, companies have to think of ways to make money.</p>
<p>The broker highlighted its impact on the financial service industry when announcing its 10 million clients milestone. In Robinhood&#8217;s words:</p>
<h2>RobinhooRobinhood Gold</h2>
<h2>d Gold</h2>
<p>“…We pioneered commission-free stock and ETF trading with no account minimums. And since then, we’ve added commission-free options trading, commission-free crypto trading…”</p>
<p><strong>Countries</strong></p>
<p>The broker only offers trading services in jurisdictions where Robinhood Financial is registered. Currently, the platform is available in most countries, excluding Syria, North Korea, Cuba, Iran, and the Crimea region of Ukraine.</p>
<h2>Robinhood Gold</h2>
<p>However, some of Robinhood&#8217;s products and features may not be available to users in certain regions because of legal restrictions. In fact, attempting to login in from within the mentioned countries can lead to account restrictions.</p>
<h2>Robinhood Review: Regulation, Reviews, and Reputation</h2>
<p>Robinhood Financial LLC is a member of FINRA (Financial Industry Regulatory Authority). Here, asset trading is provided to self-directed clients by Robinhood Financial.</p>
<p>The company is also a member of SIPC (Securities Investor Protection Corporation), which safeguards securities clients of its members up to $500,000 – inclusive of robinhood gold $250,000 for cash claims.</p>
<p>Robinhood International, Ltd., a subsidiary of the broker, is regulated and authorized by the FCA (Financial Conduct Authority) to operate as a trading broker in the UK. Its reference number is 823590.</p>
<p>Cryptocurrency trading is provided through Robinhood Crypto, a subsidiary of Robinhood Markets LLC. Unlike Robinhood Financial that offers fiat trading products, Robinhood Crypto is not a member of SIPC or FINRA. Moreover, cryptocurrency investments are not regulated by SIPC or FDIC.</p>
<p>Nonetheless, the broker assures its users that all the cryptocurrencies it holds on their behalf are stored in a mix of hot wallets and cold wallets. Many cryptocurrencies are held in cold wallets to safeguard them from hackers and cyber insecurity; however, some remain in hot wallets to aid the day-to-day trading operations.</p>
<p>Besides regulations, Robinhood reviews has a crime insurance cover, underwritten by Lloyd&#8217;s, that protects some of its assets against theft-related losses, including cybersecurity breaches.</p>
<p>On the downside, Robinhood has been faced with serious complaints and lawsuits pertaining to its reliability and trustworthiness.</p>
<p>In March 2020, the Robinhood gold app had several outages, locking traders out on their accounts – during a volatile period in market history. The broker claimed that the outage resulted from high account signups and increased orders. But, outages have persisted since then, causing some frustrations among investors.</p>
<p>In December 2020, the broker was charged by the SEC (Securities and Exchange Commission) for misleading customers. The commission discovered that &#8220;Robinhood clients&#8217; orders were executed at prices that were inferior to other brokers&#8217; prices,&#8221; and that added up to an extent that the users were deprived of $34.1 million, even after taking into account Robinhood&#8217;s commission-free trade offering. The broker agreed to pay $65 million to settle the claims.</p>
<p>In the same period, the Commonwealth of Massachusetts accused the broker of aggressively attracting newbie investors to the platform and employing gamification techniques to manipulate clients. The claims also pointed that most Robinhood traders were allowed to access advanced and risky trading options, even after identifying as having limited or no investment experience. Recall that the broker had announced plans to hire hundreds of newcomers support representatives in 2020.</p>
<p>In January 2021, the Robinhood app came under criticism to restrict operations during the high market volatility surrounding heavily shorted stocks and GameStop. It&#8217;s worth noting that the market volatility led other brokers to take measures to safeguard their operations, but Robinhood&#8217;s restrictions were extremely expansive.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Robinhood is not a full-service broker, which leaves it at a disadvantage with some competitors. The broker&#8217;s education and research tools are also not par with the industry standard. And their customer support could use an improvement. Besides, the platform does not offer joint accounts.</p>
<h2>Robinhood Review: Trading platforms</h2>
<p>Robinhood is available on Android, iOS, and most web browsers.</p>
<p>Its Web runs on PCs and Macs, with support for most web browsers such as Edge, Safari, Chrome, and Firefox.</p>
<p>Signing up for the broker is intuitive. But you&#8217;ll have to share your contact details and address to verify your identity. And advanced traders can perform more sophisticated strategies such as strangles, straddles, iron condors, and more.</p>
<p>Nasdaq’s Level II market data is available on the broker&#8217;s Gold account, which has a suite of useful tools, strategies, and data. This data displays different bid/ask levels for selected stocks, which determines stocks availability at given prices.</p>
<p>Moreover, the platform allows you to trade cryptocurrencies: Bitcoin, Bitcoin Cash, Bitcoin SV, Dogecoin, Ethereum, Ethereum Classic, and Litecoin. You can also use the broker to observe the trend on the real-time price movement of ten cryptocurrencies, including  Zcash, Dash, Ripple, Bitcoin Gold, and Monero.</p>
<p>Note, when trading cryptocurrencies on Robinhood, you can only buy the currencies with settled cash or available funds in your account. Moreover, any funds from the sales o ETFs, options, and real stocks can take up to three days before it&#8217;s available for purchasing cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>While you can place limit orders and market orders using the platform, Robinhood is a trading platform. As such, any cryptocurrencies bought will be held by the broker. In short, you cannot transfer cryptocurrencies to an external wallet or use them to pay for something.</p>
<p>All in all, the Robinhood platform features:</p>
<p>·         Web and mobile platforms</p>
<p>·         Morningstar research and insights</p>
<p>·         Level II market data</p>
<p>·         Creative watch lists</p>
<p>·         Check stock reports and details.</p>
<p>·         View candlestick charts</p>
<p>·         Customized alert notifications</p>
<p>·         Multiple order types</p>
<p>·         Technical indicators for chart analysis</p>
<h3>Robinhood app</h3>
<p>The app is popular, especially with new traders and Millenials. This is expected as the said audiences like the idea of acting quickly – and the less information on the app facilitates that. Conversely, the limited amount of information on the app can be limiting for people who prefer having more analytics and research information – before making a decision.</p>
<p><strong>Watch lists</strong></p>
<p>The platform features essential watch lists, with limited columns past the percentage change and the last price. Traders can also be restricted to a watch list at a time.</p>
<p><strong>Price alerts</strong></p>
<p>There&#8217;s no option to really customize your alerts based on specific stocks. Instead, you have to enable prompts for all your trading positions on the watch lists – which is inefficient.</p>
<p><strong>Stock charts</strong></p>
<p>The stock charts are basic enough, but they cannot be changed past six default date ranges. There&#8217;s also no room for technical analysis.</p>
<h2>Robinhood Review: Trading Tools and Offers</h2>
<p>Robinhood features the following:</p>
<p><strong>Research tools</strong></p>
<p>As noted above, the broker provides professional research by working together with Morningstar. This collaboration offers Robinhood users unlimited access to research reports and in-depth analysis on over 1700 stocks.</p>
<p>The said research is only available for Gold members, and even then, it pales in comparison to what is offered by Charles Schwab and other competitors.</p>
<p>The platform also has several inbuilt tools for managing orders, receiving alerts, and analyzing markets.</p>
<p><strong>Educational tools</strong></p>
<p>There&#8217;s also a section of the platform dedicated to educating traders via a collection o informative articles and FAQs covering a variety of investment topics. These educational materials are useful to beginners and veteran traders.</p>
<p>Note, the writers/contributors are well respected, having had published writeups by Bloomberg, Forbes, WSJ, and more.</p>
<p><strong>Newsfeed</strong></p>
<p>Furthermore, the Robinhood newsfeed is available via the app. The feed-in collaboration with Dow Jones delivers market news coverage from Barron’s, Reuters, and  The Wall Street Journal, at no additional charges to users.</p>
<p>As such, you can consume news stories from trusted sources, including news that is relevant to your watch lists and investment portfolio. Therefore, be sure to set notification alerts for assets in your watch list and portfolio.</p>
<p>The platform also features ad-free videos from Reuters, Cheddar, and CNN business displayed directly in your feed.</p>
<p>On the downside, Robinhood’s newsfeed cannot compare to that of Merrill Edge and other competitors. But it is adequate for novice traders interested in keeping the info they receive to a minimum. It’s also suitable for veteran traders not in need of much guiding.</p>
<p><strong>Fractional shares and recurring investments</strong></p>
<p>Like other trading platforms such as Charles Schwab and Interactive Brokers, Robinhood has added fractional shares to its arsenal.</p>
<p>As such, you can pay a minimum of $1 for a portion of a share, even if they share in question costs hundreds of dollars. Fractional shares make it easier to develop a diversified portfolio – as you can buy more financial instruments, even if you are short on cash.</p>
<p>The fractional share feature pairs incredibly with Robinhood&#8217;s recurring investment features. The latter enables you to set a schedule and the amount you want to invest; after that, the broker will automatically invest the amount you wish to, as scheduled. Note that the schedule plan can be weekly, biweekly, monthly, etc.</p>
<p>While a recurring investment is typical, pairing it with the fractional shares features give it a competitive edge. Often, recurring investments result in uninvested cash but pairing the two parts helps solve the issue.</p>
<p><strong>Dividend reinvestment program</strong></p>
<p>Fractional shares have allowed Robinhood to provide a dividend reinvestment program (called DRIP). DRIP is a valuable strategy for expanding your stocks over time. As such, DRIP, recurring investments, and fractional shares features work together to help Robinhood standout, now that zero-commission trading is commonplace.</p>
<p><strong>High-yield savings</strong></p>
<p>The platform provides cash management that pays approximately 0.30%. The cash management account features a debit card and free ATM withdrawals from over 75,000 ATMs. It also offers up to $1.25 million of FDIC insurance.</p>
<h2>Robinhood Review: Assets and Markets</h2>
<p>The broker provides trading services for over 5 000 Funds, stocks, options, and cryptocurrencies. Its assets include most United States equities and exchange-traded funds (ETFs) listed on US exchanges.</p>
<p>You can trade short or long on popular stocks, including over 250 global real stocks excluded on American exchanges. You can also invest commission-free in bundles of investments or individual companies.</p>
<p>Cryptos permitted include Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Dogecoin. But as noted earlier, Robinhood Crypto is not a FINRA member. That means any purchase, reception, or sale of cryptocurrency is unregulated and, as such, has a high risk of losing money.</p>
<p>Let’s expound more on Robinhood assets.</p>
<p><strong>Stock trading</strong></p>
<p>To trade stocks, click on the search icon and type the stock you want to invest in. There are numerous stocks in the arsenal, including CCL and ON.</p>
<p>Besides being commission-free,  Robinhood supports market orders, limit orders, stop-limit orders, and stop orders with good-for-the-day or good-till-canceled parameters.</p>
<p>Note, the platform shows you the number of day trades on your account, which can be tempting. However, it&#8217;s wise to steer clear of day trading – especially if you&#8217;re a novice trader.</p>
<p><strong>Options trading</strong></p>
<p>Options provide access to no-fee contracts, including no exercise fees, no assignment fees, no per-contract fee, and no commissions.</p>
<p>Options trading also has advanced trade strategies and helpful filters. Furthermore, you can trade multi-leg options strategies in one order and monitor the complex contracts together.</p>
<p>A word of caution, options trading is ideal for experienced investors as opposed to novice traders.</p>
<p><strong>Crypto trading</strong></p>
<p>Robinhood crypto trading service allows access to sell and buy Bitcoin, Bitcoin Cash, Ethereum, Ethereum Classic, Litecoin, and Dogecoin.</p>
<p>Note, the access to trade cryptocurrencies is rolled out on a state-to-state basis, and as such, you should check whether the crypto exchange is available in your state first – if your sole purpose for using the platform is crypto trading.</p>
<p>Robinhood users also have access to price and market data for 16 popular cryptos. The platform is a no-fee operation to crypto trading – a significant advantage over a well-known digital wallet. Moreover, you can trade cryptos 24/7.</p>
<p>On the downside, Robinhood&#8217;s crypto portfolio is limited compared to other crypto exchanges.</p>
<h2>Robinhood Review: Fees</h2>
<p>The broker provides three types of accounts to suit various investors. It also makes it easier to upgrade or downgrade accounts anytime.</p>
<p>The accounts offer varying benefits and also have different requirements. For instance, the cash and instant accounts do not provide leverage, but the gold accounts offer up to 1:2 leverage. At the same time, the cash and instant accounts require no minimum deposit, yet the gold account requires a minimum of $2,000 as a deposit.</p>
<p><strong>Robinhood Instant</strong></p>
<p>The Robinhood Instant account is the default account. It&#8217;s the account you start with after registration. It features an instant deposit for up to $1000 you start with after signing up. It gives access to extended trading hours and instant deposits for up to $1,000.</p>
<p><strong>Robinhood Gold</strong></p>
<p>The Robinhood Gold account is like a Robinhood instant account on steroids, thanks to its additional benefits.</p>
<p>The gold account is available for as little as $5 per month. It gives access to:</p>
<ul>
<li>Level II market data from Nasdaq</li>
<li>Research reports from Morningstar</li>
<li>Trading with margin</li>
<li>Bigger deposits</li>
<li>Quick access to funds</li>
</ul>
<p>Investing in margins provides buying power and flexibility while increasing the overall exposure. However, you can still access the account and its premium features when you turn trade with margin off.</p>
<p>The gold account boasts a 30-day free trial on the gold account available.</p>
<p><strong>Robinhood Cash</strong></p>
<p>The Robinhood Cash account gives access to commission free trades during the standard and extended-hours trading sessions. However, it does not provide access to instant deposits or instant settlements.</p>
<h3>Fees</h3>
<p>Robinhood does not charge any fee or trading fiat instruments, such as ETFs and stocks, and is said to extend free-trading to cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>However, numerous reviews have highlighted Robinhood&#8217;s Crypto User Agreement, where it points out that the broker will pass on any fees charged by intermediaries to the user. Traders also claim that the pointed fees are already added to the crypto price displayed to the trader.</p>
<p>As noted under the Instant account, you&#8217;ll initially only gain access to a maximum of $1000 in funds after a deposit. If you had added a more significant sum to your Robinhood regular account, you&#8217;d have to await the completion of normal settlements before you can purchase cryptos.</p>
<p>You can increase the fundamental limit by subscribing to the gold account, as it offers multiple tiers of instant deposit limits. However, when you use over $1000 of margin, you&#8217;ll have to pay 2.5% yearly interest – on the amount above the set threshold.</p>
<p>There&#8217;s also a regulatory charge (SEC)  of $22.10 per $1,000,000 of principal sales only. The regulatory charge is rounded to the nearest penny. Furthermore, Robinhood passes on a trading activity (FINRA) fee of $0.000119 per share (equity sells) and $0.002 per share (options sells). This trading fee is rounded up to the nearest penny and does not exceed $5.95.</p>
<p>Also, returned checks, wire transfers, paper statements &amp; other services incur fees.</p>
<p>For instance, domestic wire transfers cost $25, international wire transfers cost $50, and transferring an account to a different brokerage cost $75. Paper confirmation costs $2, paper statements cost $5, while domestic overnight check delivery costs $20. Returned wire, ACH, or check costs $30. Sending domestic overnight mail costs $20 while sending international overnight mail costs $50.</p>
<p>Seeing that brokers&#8217; fees change with time, there may be additional fees not listed in this review. Thus, ensure that you check and understand all of the latest prices, requirements, and information before opening a Robinhood account.</p>
<h3>Taxation</h3>
<p>While at it, bear in mind that dividends, as well as short and long-term gains on Robinhood, are subject to taxation.</p>
<p>Robinhood provides traders with a Form 1099 document, which includes details found on Forms 1099-DIV, 1099-MISC, 1099-INT, and 1099-B. If you use Robinhood Crypto, you will receive an additional Form 1099 as a .pdf and .csv file.</p>
<p>Note, Robinhood doesn’t offer tax advice; as such, import the tax documents that you&#8217;ll receive into TurboTax, or better yet, consult a professional when filing your taxes.</p>
<h2>Robinhood Review: Deposit and Withdrawal</h2>
<p>Robinhood provides deposits and withdrawals through bank transfers. This method is limited, and most users would prefer if the broker offered online payment processors like Skrill,  PayPal,  and Neteller.</p>
<p>On the upside, you can link a significant bank in the Robinhood iOS or Android app. To do so, choose your bank from the list of major banks, or manually search for your bank; and proceed to link the two. Once done, you can deposit into your Robinhood account with ease.</p>
<p>It takes approximately 5-6 business days to transfer any deposits over $1000.</p>
<p>When it comes to withdrawals, you can get instant access to your cash. But the ACH withdrawal takes approximately 5-6 business days – once the funds&#8217; transfer is initiated.</p>
<p>If the withdrawal is more than the amount present in the account, the transfer is reversed. A trader can transfer a maximum of $50,000 per business day into and from your Robinhood account.</p>
<p>You can also set up automatic transfers into your account or cancel pending deposits before the three specified cut-off points.</p>
<p>To fight against money laundering, you can only withdraw money to the bank account you used to deposit money into your Robinhood account in the first 60 days.</p>
<p>If the bank account is, for some reason, closed, you can initiate a transfer to another account- but you must provide the required information.</p>
<h2>Robinhood Review: Customer Support</h2>
<p>The broker isn’t here to guide, educate, help, or nurture traders. No. That&#8217;s not Robinhood&#8217;s focus, which is also understandable, seeing that they&#8217;re doing well without it.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s safe to say that Robinhood has pushed the finance service industry to provide reasonable prices for customers, but that does not include a sound customer support system.</p>
<p>Robinhood customer support starts and ends with automatic responses from their chatbots and a set of FAQs on their help page. It’s nearly impossible to get any information outside of these resources.</p>
<p>As such, if engaging with an actual person is crucial to you, then Robinhood is not the trading platform or you.</p>
<p>According to the broker&#8217;s website, customer support is offered via telephone and email during market hours (9:30 am – 4:00 pm EST). However, most customer reviews do not show confidence in that arrangement.</p>
<p>Despite the shortcomings, Robinhood is popular among novice traders thanks to its infrastructure, replete with educational materials.</p>
<h2>Robinhood Review: Opening an account</h2>
<p>Once you have decided to open an account with Robinhood, the signup process takes approximately four minutes.</p>
<p>To set the account, you&#8217;ll require:</p>
<ul>
<li> Bank information</li>
<li>Social security number, and</li>
<li>A mobile or iPad</li>
</ul>
<p>Here’s a detailed procedure.</p>
<p><strong>1. Setting up an account</strong></p>
<p>Head to Robinhood&#8217;s signup page. Once there, fill in a short form with the required personal details and hit the create count icon. Be sure to select the right operating platform for your mobile device.</p>
<p>Note, Robinhood is a mobile company, and as such, it&#8217;s not available for computer use.</p>
<p><strong>2. Fill in your contact information</strong></p>
<p>In the subsequent step, fill out more personal details with regards to contact number and address details.</p>
<p>In case of any suspicion, Robinhood has explained why they need the contact and address information – on the right of the screen.</p>
<p><strong>3. Verify your identity</strong></p>
<p>Next, you need to verify your identity. In this interface/page, you find detailed guidelines to how you can verify your account – and the reasons why they need the information they&#8217;re asking for.</p>
<p><strong>4. Fund your account</strong></p>
<p>Once you have proven your identity, transfer some funds to your account. The broker does not charge any transactional fees for deposits and withdrawals.</p>
<p><strong>5. Submit the application</strong></p>
<p>Next, read the broker&#8217;s terms and conditions, hit the submit button – and you&#8217;ll be nearly done. Note, Robinhood will notify you via email once your submission has been accepted.</p>
<p><strong>6. Download the app</strong></p>
<p>Once you have sent your submission, you&#8217;ll be redirected to either the Android or iOS version of the app to download.</p>
<p><strong>7. log in to the app</strong></p>
<p>Once you have downloaded the app, launch it and login into your Robinhood account with the exact login details you set in step 1 above.</p>
<p>Click on &#8220;Add funds&#8221; to fill in your bank information and begin your investment journey with the broker.</p>
<p>Note, you must meet the following criteria before you can think of opening a Robinhood account:</p>
<ul>
<li>Be over 18 years</li>
<li>Have a valid social security number</li>
<li>Be located in a country where the use of the app is permitted.</li>
</ul>
<p>Besides the Web-based application, you can also create an account via the Robinhood app. After a day or so, you&#8217;ll receive an update &#8211; whether your submission has been accepted or if more information is required.</p>
<p>To verify your identity and address, you can upload relevant documents like:</p>
<ul>
<li>Passports</li>
<li>Utility bill</li>
<li>Bank statement</li>
<li>Driver’s license</li>
</ul>
<p>The verification process takes approximately 5 – 7 days.</p>
<p>As noted, you can deposit funds before your account is confirmed; however, the money will not be deposited until the account is officially opened.</p>
<p>And to ease your mind, Robinhood features a device monitoring function that adds a layer of security to your account. This feature allows you to view and manage the devices accessing your account. Moreover, you can set up two-factor authentication to add another layer of security to the account.</p>
<h3>Who is Robinhood best for?</h3>
<p>Robinhood is for you if you’re a/an:</p>
<ul>
<li>Beginner</li>
<li>Cyber-security trader</li>
<li>Smartphone user</li>
<li>Low minimum</li>
<li>Option trader</li>
<li>Quick trade</li>
</ul>
<h2>Robinhood Review: Pros</h2>
<ul>
<li> Regulated by top financial commissions</li>
<li>User-friendly mobile interface</li>
<li>Commission-free trading</li>
<li> No account minimums, except for the Robinhood gold account</li>
<li>Personalized and free research analysis and information</li>
<li>Personalization and free trading and watch lists alerts</li>
</ul>
<p>·</p>
<h2>Robinhood Review: Cons</h2>
<ul>
<li>Limited financial markets</li>
<li>Limited funding options</li>
<li>Inadequate customer support</li>
<li>Too much-streamlined information</li>
<li>No Metatrader</li>
<li> High minimum deposits ($2000) for gold account</li>
<li>No forex currency trading</li>
<li>There is no option to open IRA, retirement, education, or joint accounts – the only available option is an individual, taxable account.</li>
<li>No option for bonds and mutual funds</li>
</ul>
<h2>Robinhood Review: Final verdict</h2>
<p>Robinhood offers commission-free trading on easy-to-use, customizable, and flexible trading applications. The broker has some useful offers and trading tools that assist with research, market analysis, and updates pertaining to economic news events.</p>
<p>However, the broker has limited funding options, financial products offered, as well as jurisdictions.</p>
<p>Although free, its crypto trading option is most suited for existing customers; otherwise, Robin Crypto is not enticing. Thus, you can trade fiat financial instruments and then take your cryptocurrency trading business elsewhere.</p>
<p>And even if you can ignore the recent app restrictions, complaints, and lawsuits, the broker&#8217;s lack of transparency regarding pertinent details and some fees does not inspire confidence.</p>
<p>nd other pertinent details</p>
<p>Bottom line: do your due diligence.</p>
<div class="ups-downs"><h5>Pros / Cons</h5><div class="row"><div class="col-md-6 col-sm-12"><div class="icon green"><i class="fa fa-chevron-up" aria-hidden="true"></i></div><ul><li>Praesent sed semper mauris, nec eleifend nibh</li><li>Donec ultricies placerat neque, eu malesuada lacus dignissim in</li><li>Praesent sed semper mauris, nec eleifend nibh</li><li>Praesent sed semper mauris, nec eleifend nibh</li></ul></div><div class="col-md-6 col-sm-12"><div class="icon red"><i class="fa fa-chevron-down" aria-hidden="true"></i></div><ul><li>Donec ultricies placerat neque, eu malesuada lacus dignissim in</li><li>Donec ultricies placerat neque, eu malesuada lacus dignissim in</li><li>Donec ultricies placerat neque, eu malesuada lacus dignissim in</li></ul></div></div></div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/review/robinhood/">Robinhood Review</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">MrStocks.org</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/review/robinhood/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>eToro Review: Regulations, Reputation, Pros, Cons</title>
		<link>/review/etoro/</link>
					<comments>/review/etoro/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Maximilian Weber]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2017 15:18:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://demos.pokatheme.com/pokatheme/?post_type=affiliates&#038;p=236</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When looking for a trader that permits cryptocurrencies trading, you’re likely to come across eToro sooner than later. The reason being, eToro is a top online brokerage for Forex, CFDs, ETFs, stocks, and cryptocurrencies in the world. But is it legit? Today, we present you with a comprehensive review of this brokerage company, including its [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/review/etoro/">eToro Review: Regulations, Reputation, Pros, Cons</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">MrStocks.org</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When looking for a trader that permits cryptocurrencies trading, you’re likely to come across eToro sooner than later. The reason being, eToro is a top online brokerage for Forex, CFDs, ETFs, stocks, and cryptocurrencies in the world. But is it legit?</p>
<p>Today, we present you with a comprehensive review of this brokerage company, including its background, goals, customer support, and more. We aim to help you perceive a clear picture of the trading platform and, as such, make an informed decision.</p>
<p>Let’s dive in.</p>
<h2>eToro Review: Background</h2>
<p>eToro was first launched in Israel in 2007 under the name RetailFx. The platform was the work of three entrepreneurs who sought to make trading more accessible for everyone while reducing traders&#8217; dependency on traditional financial institutions.</p>
<p>eToro began as an online platform with an intuitive interface. The interface featured graphs to represent financial instruments.</p>
<h3>The eToro Trading Timeline</h3>
<p>In 2009, the broker’s platform launched the WebTrader – the eToro platform with a wide range of professional tools for the everyday user.</p>
<p>In 2010/2011, eToro went through a significant update, including the launch of its famous copy trading platform.</p>
<p>In 2012, the company added stocks to its assets, such as commodities and currencies.</p>
<p>Initially, the platform was intended to be a forex trader, but the company introduced the option to trade stocks CFDs (explained in a later section) in 2013. Simultaneously, eToro launched the mobile app for Apple and Android systems. In addition, they dipped into cryptocurrencies, enabling users to trade Bitcoin through CFDs (Contract For Difference).</p>
<p>In 2015, eToro updated the interface to provide a more intuitive experience.</p>
<p>In 2016, they added CopyPortfolio – managed portfolios that buddle top traders or assets within a marketing strategy.</p>
<p>In 2017, they added support for cryptocurrency trading, which began with popular cryptocurrencies, such as XRP, Litecoin, and Ethereum.</p>
<p>In 2019, the brokerage launched eToroX, a full crypto to crypto exchange.</p>
<h3>What eToro Offers Today</h3>
<p>Today, eToro is known for stocks, commodities, Forex, CFDs with this provider, and cryptocurrency trading. The platform is easy to use. Its provision for copy trading makes it ideal for users interested in being copied for risk-controlled reasons.</p>
<p>Thus far, eToro USA, LLC has facilitated millions of trades thanks to its global reach. The company has registered subsidiaries in the UK, Australia, Cyprus, and the United States. It’s also focusing on entering the Asian markets soon.</p>
<p>But while most eToro’s trading services are allowed in many countries, there’s a significant number of countries that are banned from using the platform. They include Albania, Cuba, Canada, Iran, Iraq, Japan, Jamaica, Nicaragua, Syria, Serbia, and Pakistan.</p>
<p>So the background of eToro USA, LLC is quite enticing, <strong>but is the service legitimate</strong>?</p>
<h2>eToro Review: Regulations, Reviews, and Reputation</h2>
<p>To operate legally, an online broker requires permissions and licenses for each jurisdiction it avails its services.</p>
<p>In its case, eToro has secured a license from the<a href="https://www.fca.org.uk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"> FCA</a> (Financial Conduct Authority) for its United Kingdon based subsidiaries. It has also acquired approval from the<a href="https://www.cysec.gov.cy/en-GB/home/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"> CySEC</a> (Cyprus Securities and Exchange Commission) to covers its Cyprus-based users. Added to that is a license from the<a href="https://asic.gov.au/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"> ASIC</a> (Australian Securities and Investment Commission) covering Australian-based traders.</p>
<p>In addition, eToro has an<a href="https://www.fsca.co.za/Pages/Default.aspx" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"> FSCA</a> license to provide regulations for its South Africa-based users, as well as other licenses, such as FinCEN from several American states.</p>
<p>In short, eToro and eToro wallet is well regulated by top financial authorities, making it safe and trustable with funds, personal information, social trading, and stock trading.</p>
<h3>Which Accounts Lose Money, Have a High Risk of Losing Money, and Which Retail Investor Accounts Lose Money?</h3>
<p>eToro trading, trading forex, cryptocurrencies, and CFDs are complex instruments and come with a high risk of losing. (According to eToro, 67% of retail investor accounts lose money when trading CFDs with the platform.) Retail investor accounts lose money when trading CFDs with this provider at times because, at the end of the day, CFDs are complex instruments and come with a high risk of losing money.</p>
<p>Besides, the purchase of real/crypto assets, like Bitcoin Cash, Ethereum Classic, and other crypto assets is an unregulated service thus far. As such, before choosing any provider you should consider the necessary precautions to protect yourself and your money while trading CFDs and making sure you understand how CFDs work, stock trading, and using eToro.</p>
<h3><strong>Reviews and Reputation</strong></h3>
<p>Besides regulation, a good reason to use eToro is that it&#8217;s <a href="https://www.etoro.com/about/reviews/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">well endorsed</a> by most users across the globe – and understandably so. For one, that people trading eToro can feel secure since it takes precautions to safeguard its clients&#8217; account, funds, and personal data. Traditional funds remain safe and secure in banks of the top tier. While some instruments have a high risk of losing, your money is safe through the eToro mobile app.</p>
<p>eToro is a provider you should consider because it&#8217;s also easy to use and intuitive, making it suitable for both beginners and veteran traders.  The platform provides users with numerous tools to help them make responsible decisions. The tools cover all experience levels while providing guidance and risk management features for the initial steps.</p>
<p>The bottom line is, eToro is a reputable trading platform and their mobile app is top-notch. Besides, its parent company is large and well established, which adds to the trust.</p>
<p>Note, there have been complaints about their customer support system as being slow and less helpful. Nonetheless, the broker prides itself on resolving issues as seamlessly as possible. That means it may take time for them to get to your complaint ticket, but once they do, they ensure your problem is resolved.</p>
<p>There has also been the issue of the platform tending to freeze often. It could be due to technical difficulties or server maintenance, but often, the freezing results from too many people using the platform at the same time.</p>
<p>With the legitimacy out of the question, let’s dive into the platform itself.</p>
<h2>eToro Review: Trading Platforms</h2>
<p>eToro is compatible with various devices, including Pcs, Macs, Androids, and iOS systems. The main trading platform is web-based software and is available in different languages: Arabic, Czech, Chinese, Dutch, Danish, French, Finnish, German, Malaysian, Italian, Norwegian, Portuguese, Polish, Russian, Romanian, Swedish, Spanish, Thai, and Vietnamese.</p>
<h3><strong>The interface</strong></h3>
<p>The web-based trading software is user-friendly, well-designed, and provides an option to do social trading.</p>
<h3><strong>Search function</strong></h3>
<p>eToro provides a built-in search function to ease the user’s exploratory journey. You can use the function to search for any products without any problems.</p>
<h3><strong>Orders</strong></h3>
<p>Making orders on through your trading account is fast and efficient. You can load your trading account with money via credit card or bank account. As such, you can make the following orders in a minute:</p>
<ul>
<li>Limit</li>
<li>Market</li>
<li>Trailing Stop</li>
<li>Stop</li>
</ul>
<p>Traders who want to make orders, launch the eToro Wallet and scroll to the <strong>Order Interface.</strong></p>
<p>Making orders only takes a minute and is really easy. It&#8217;s appropriate for all investors whether your interested in investing in stocks, crypto trading, how to understand how CFDs work, or virtual trading platform. eToro is a multi-asset platform and because eToro is a multi-asset platform it becomes your one stop shop to buy and sell a variety of the different instruments.</p>
<h3><strong>Charting</strong></h3>
<p>The platform boasts a charting system that features numerous drawing tools and sixty-six (66) indicators. While the charting features lack a backtest function, eToro provides performance data from CopyTraders and CopyPortfolios.</p>
<p><strong><em>Bear in mind that eToro has a phenomenal mobile app but does not offer a downloadable desktop platform yet; as such, all trading done on Macs and PCs are done through your eToro Wallet online.</em></strong></p>
<h3>Mobile trading</h3>
<p>eToro provides the mobile trading versions for iOS and Android systems to enable clients to sync seamlessly between devices. The menus are well organized; however, the customization is limited in charting features. There are only five types of charting features on the indicator menu.</p>
<p>Nonetheless, you can set custom price alerts as well as push alerts about market events and account issues.</p>
<h2>eToro Review: Offers and Trading Tools</h2>
<p>eToro strives to educate traders in addition to offering them a platform for investment.</p>
<p>Upon registration, eToro clients receive a demo account with $100,000 virtual money to work on their trading skills and strategies before investing real money.</p>
<p>The platform also offers multiple other tools to aid with actual trading. Such tools include:</p>
<h3><strong>Economic calendar</strong></h3>
<p>eToro offers an economic calendar, where you can input the dates and timezone of choice and assets you trade. The economic calendar will then display how events in the set timezones are likely to impact your investments.</p>
<h3><strong>Market analysis</strong></h3>
<p>The platform provides market analyses that feature quick overviews and in-depth details about every tradable asset. As such, you can utilize as little or as much information as you want to inform your trading decisions.</p>
<p>The analyses are easily accessible, too, as every tradable asset is assigned its own webpage.</p>
<h3><strong>Research tools</strong></h3>
<p>eToro boasts technical analysis tools that are supplemented by analysts&#8217; recommendations. The tracker indicates the percentage of eToro users likely to buy or sell the asset. This can prevent you from losing money rapidly due to uneducated investments. Moreover, there are comments from analysts for popular assets.</p>
<p>Note, research is also accessible in a blog featuring numerous generic articles. However, this research is a tad disorganized, with the most detailed guides being crypto-based topics instead of Forex or market analysis. The mobile app does provide a research button, but the analyst research is only available for funded accounts.</p>
<h3><strong>Charting tools</strong></h3>
<p>The platform flaunts over 70 technical indicators and charts. This makes eToro appropriate for all investors.</p>
<p>Before you take the high-risk investment you can do your research and avoid losing money rapidly due to poorly researched positions. However, the charting tool indicates data up to 6 months, which can prove inadequate, especially when you take the high risk markets into account. They change rapidly due to leverage so it&#8217;s nice to have access to longer historical data.</p>
<p>Moreover, the data available consist of only the basic financial ratios. There are no historical records of price targets, income statements, balance sheets, or earnings estimates. This gives you some info on whether you should buy and sell but make sure to do further research before crypto trading, investing in stocks, before losing your money rapidly due to leverage unforeseen by inadequate research and preparation.</p>
<h3><strong>Newsfeed</strong></h3>
<p>eToro News Link, direct users to a social forum that features posts from different users offers further indication of future results, and offers both investing tips and which accounts lose money by real users.</p>
<p>The said posts are real-time news/video streams from verified eToro users, providing more reliable feedback about the platform and indication of future results. The posts show users purchasing and selling in real-time, which provides fast sentiment analysis. Moreover, the user can customize and save their watch lists so you can consider whether you understand to buy and sell a certain instrument.</p>
<p>On the downside, the newsfeed is limited to comments and tweets from traders with the platform. It does not include major media outlets like Bloomberg or Reuters.</p>
<h3><strong>Education tools</strong></h3>
<p>If you are still one to consider whether you understand what you&#8217;re doing, eToro&#8217;s educational materials consist of frequently asked questions (FAQs), video tutorials, and offers both investing tips and cautions, which most traders find useful. The education tools address eToro&#8217;s financial assets available, functionalities, trading fees, and related topics.</p>
<h3><strong>Trading academy</strong></h3>
<p>eToro features a link to the trading academy in the footer. There’s also a link for a Live Webinar at the bottom of the web interface.</p>
<p>It allows you to study and potentially copy the trades of more successful investors so you understand fully how to use eToro mobile.</p>
<p>As noted earlier, there&#8217;s a FAQ section and help databases that answer most of the common questions posed by traders. There&#8217;s also a YouTube library that provides tutorials containing how-to presentations.</p>
<p><em>Added to that is the platform&#8217;s social elements, such as CopyPortfolios. The ability to copy the trades and trading strategies of successful users in real-time is also innovative – and the same goes for the Popular Investor program.</em></p>
<h3><strong>CopyPortfolio</strong></h3>
<p>CopyPortfolio is a product for traders&#8217; portfolio management. See, there are numerous similarities between investments in a specific index and a mixture of assets being selected for the user.</p>
<p>Any investment made by a trader automatically copies other users or multiple markets with a similar predetermined investment strategy based on past performance of a fund or past performance of an individual asset.</p>
<p>The feature is available for traditional fiat trades and cryptocurrency trading. It features several cryptocurrency investments that deliver exposure to Bitcoin, Ethereum, and other cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>As noted, it creates a single tradable asset that comprises skillfully selected traders or assets of predetermined strategy.</p>
<h3><strong>Copy trading</strong></h3>
<p>Copy trading is an innovative option that allows users to evaluate other traders&#8217; track records and copy them – or mirror their trades.</p>
<p>Copy trading is available for both traditional fiat investments and cryptocurrency trading. With it, beginner and veteran traders can get exposure to the trading market without having to do much homework and research.</p>
<p>The copy trading feature is handy as trades can be copied at any scale. For instance, if you want to invest $10 000 but the trader you want to copy is investing $100,000, you can copy the trader at one-tenth of their original level.</p>
<h2>eToro Review: Assets and Markets</h2>
<p>With eToro, you can trade nearly any asset through one platform. The broker’s platform is a social trading network that combines user interactions and a modern trading system.</p>
<p>As noted in the background section, eToro was designed to disrupt the traditional banking system while beginning a digital financial era.</p>
<p>eToro enables traders to make investments in hundreds of securities and assets, including indices, currencies, stocks, commodities, and cryptocurrency. Each asset is traded following different investment strategies. As such, equity trading is unavailable.</p>
<p>While the platform&#8217;s assets portfolio is not the biggest, it is diverse enough to be deemed decent and satisfactory by most users.</p>
<p>eToro may not offer a large number of assets, but it&#8217;s<a href="https://www.publicfinanceinternational.org/go/etoro-home" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"> a top-rated broker for cryptocurrency traders</a>. It provides an extensive portfolio of cryptos, including:</p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin (BTC)</li>
<li>Dash</li>
<li>Ethereum (ETH)</li>
<li>Ripple (XRP)</li>
<li>Bitcoin Cash (BCH)</li>
<li>LiteCoin (LTC)</li>
<li>Stellar Lumens</li>
<li>Cardano (ADA)</li>
<li>Ethereum Classic (ETC)</li>
</ul>
<p>·         Plus 85 more.</p>
<p>In fact, the eToro wallet app has over 120 supported cryptocurrencies. The secure digital wallet provides safe storing, buying, and receiving cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p><strong>Disclaimer: trading cryptocurrencies is not currently regulated by any European Union and other regulatory frameworks.</strong></p>
<h2>eToro Review: Fees and Commissions</h2>
<p>eToro features trading and non-trading fees.</p>
<p>Trading fees are costs incurred through trading. They include conversion fees, spreads, financing rates, and commissions.</p>
<p>Non-trading fees are costs incurred performing tasks with no direct relation to trading. They include withdrawal fees and inactivity fees.</p>
<p>Here’s a further breakdown of eToro fees for the most frequently traded financial instruments.</p>
<h3><strong>ETF fees and stock fees</strong></h3>
<p>eToro provides zero-commission stock and ETF trading for its EU users. And being a CDF broker, the platform enables users to trade with real stocks and ETFs when the leverage is set to one. For example:</p>
<p>5:1 for stock CFDs</p>
<p>20:1 for stock index CFDs</p>
<p>30:1 for Forex</p>
<p>Unfortunately, zero-commission trading is unavailable for users outside of the European Union.</p>
<p>ETF and stock fees are low – and the same goes for their spread. <strong>Spread equals the difference between the bid price and ask price. </strong>When the leverage position is set above one, the trading is with CFDs – which have a high risk of losing money. These accounts lose money due to the nature of the investment and poor research so make sure you understand how CFDs work before diving in.</p>
<h3><strong>Non-trading fees</strong></h3>
<p>Non-trading fees are often high as the user is charged $10 per month if they are inactive for 12 months. There is also a withdrawal fee of $5.</p>
<h3><strong>Cryptocurrency trading fee</strong></h3>
<p>It costs 5% (4% Simplex fee + 1% standard fee) to exchange fiat currency to cryptocurrency. While it costs 0.1% to convert cryptocurrency to cryptocurrency. This exchange requires a minimum of $20 and a maximum of $10,000 per transaction.</p>
<h3><strong>Incentives</strong></h3>
<p>eToro offers a popular four-level investor program ranging from cadet to elite. Here, the trader may be eligible to receive trading perks, including monthly payments, spread rebates, and management fees. This approach differs from an active trader program that requires a volume threshold or deposit.</p>
<h3><strong>VIP account</strong></h3>
<p>eToro provides a VIP club membership with five tiers ranging from gold to diamond. The diamond tier is for users with a constant balance of $5k to $250k.</p>
<p>The VIP account offers varying benefits depending on the tier. Such benefits include access to private signals and exclusive assets as well as a dedicated account manager.</p>
<h2>eToro Review: Deposit and Withdrawal</h2>
<p>eToro requires a minimum amount of initial deposit of $200 for an online banking transfer and $500 for a wire transfer. As a trader, you can only deposit up to $10,000 into your eToro account per day.</p>
<p>You can make deposits into the platform using the following options:</p>
<ul>
<li>Skrill</li>
<li>Paypal</li>
<li>Credit or Debit card</li>
<li>Visa or Mastercard</li>
<li>Neteller</li>
<li>Webmoney</li>
<li>Giropay</li>
<li>Yandex</li>
<li>China Union Pay</li>
</ul>
<p>The exchanges use Plaid, a third-party provider, to enable the client to open a new account with a direct connection to eToro. Note, a wire transfer requires some fees from the trader’s bank to be paid.</p>
<p>You can use the same option you used to deposit money into the eToro account to withdraw funds. The platform charges a $5 withdrawal fee. You can withdraw a minimum of $50. For more details on deposits and withdrawal fees, visit eToro&#8217;s <strong>fee page</strong>.</p>
<p>It is also worth noting that your account balance can decrease due to inactivity fees. For instance, if there have been no-trading activities for a year, you will be charged $10 each month. Fortunately, the eToro Club program provides traders with additional services and some discounts based on their account’s size.</p>
<h2>Customer Support</h2>
<p>Traders can connect with eToro via an online support forum. There, they can submit a ticket for various issues. eToro had availed a customer support line – however, most users claim that the calling option is no longer available.</p>
<p>There&#8217;s a separate customer service program through eToro partners.</p>
<p>As noted earlier, the customer reviews for eToro&#8217;s customer support are somewhat negative – primarily due to delayed responses.</p>
<p>Overall, submitting a complaint ticket is faster than reaching customer service directly. And you can rest assured that once your ticket is reached, they will do all they can to resolve your issues.</p>
<h2>Account Opening</h2>
<p>Just like any trading platform, eToro requires you to take several steps before you can begin trading. First, you will have to provide specific information. The account will then require verification with proof of government-issued identification, address, and a verified phone number.</p>
<p>Account verification can take up to two days. New users must prove their identity and residence by providing the following documents.</p>
<h3><strong>POI (proof of identity) document </strong></h3>
<p>Acceptable POI documents include passports, identification cards, and government-issued driver&#8217;s licenses.</p>
<h3><strong>POA (proof of address) document</strong></h3>
<p>The acceptable POA documents include:</p>
<ul>
<li> Bank statement</li>
<li>Utility bills such as water, gas, or electricity</li>
<li>Utility bill including gas, water, or electric</li>
</ul>
<h3>POIS (proof of identity and selfie) document</h3>
<p>The photo must show you holding the POI document uploaded to the exchange.</p>
<p>Once the verification is done, you can now use the account to trade.</p>
<p>Users reports online banking as the easiest way to make deposits. Plaid, the third-party provider, enables clients to open a new account with a direct connection to eToro.</p>
<h2>eToro Review: Pros</h2>
<ul>
<li>Free stocks and ETFs trading for EU-based clients</li>
<li>Good portfolio of popular cryptocurrencies</li>
<li>Good social trading experience</li>
<li>Offers additional investments products</li>
<li>Intuitive user interface</li>
<li>Accepts deposits and withdrawals using multiple payments options</li>
<li>Easy to open a new account</li>
</ul>
<h2>eToro Review: Cons</h2>
<ul>
<li>Withdrawals are slow and costly</li>
<li>The forex fees are high</li>
<li>Withdrawals are only available in fiat currency</li>
<li>The base currency is only usable for one account</li>
</ul>
<h2>eToro Review: The Verdict</h2>
<p>Overall, eToro is a user-first trading company that has raised enough venture capital to ensure the broker meets its traders&#8217; growing needs. eToro is suitable for anyone investing in cryptocurrency or interested in trading.</p>
<p>Everything from the CopyTrader features to the open-market cryptocurrency exchange is intuitive. CopyPortfolios, as well as various graphs, give the platform a nice edge.</p>
<p>eToro is ideal for beginners, intermediates, and veterans due to its high intuitive nature and resourceful education materials.</p>
<p>eToro is not ideal for trading unpopular cryptocurrencies. However, it provides good options for users interested in using a single platform for fiat and major cryptocurrency trades.</p>
<p>eToro is a reliable platform for trading Forex &amp; regular stocks as well as investing in pre-built portfolios or various industries. It enables users to buy and directly hold cryptos assets.</p>
<p>Withdrawals and deposits are processed accurately and reliably to ensure that all funds remain safe and secure.</p>
<p>The platform has been proven to be trustworthy for many years now. It&#8217;s not a wonder that many eToro reviews recommend trying out the broker.</p>
<h3><strong>However, you can send cryptos to eToro Wallet</strong></h3>
<p>In addition, seeing that eToro is geared towards social media and social trading, it&#8217;s likely that as more users enroll, the experienced traders will be open to having their strategies copied. That will, in turn, help them have a better social media reputation and, as a result, gain rewards from the Popular Investor program.</p>
<p>Please note, before choosing any trading mobile app make sure to do research regarding their EU regulatory framework and if they are supervised by any EU entity. The EU regulatory framework will show how they do business and if they are supervised by any EU authority in addition to US regulations.</p>
<p>Please note that investing as well as trading is something that comes with risks, make sure you can afford to take risks. Make sure any money you invest you can afford to take a hit on. If you&#8217;re planning on investing in stock as well as trading other instruments like options and crypto make sure you do your research before putting your money into them.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/review/etoro/">eToro Review: Regulations, Reputation, Pros, Cons</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">MrStocks.org</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/review/etoro/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Public Review</title>
		<link>/review/public/</link>
					<comments>/review/public/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Maximilian Weber]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2017 15:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://demos.pokatheme.com/pokatheme/?post_type=affiliates&#038;p=232</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Public.com Review 2021 If you are gathering information about some of the available apps that you can use to trade, you are in the right place. In this Public review, we look at one of such apps namely, Public.com. In this Public.com survey, we&#8217;ll look at an app that allows you to purchase and sell [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/review/public/">Public Review</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">MrStocks.org</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="ql-align-justify"><strong>Public.com Review 2021</strong></p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">If you are gathering information about some of the available apps that you can use to trade, you are in the right place. In this <strong>Public review</strong>, we look at one of such apps namely, Public.com.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">In this Public.com survey, we&#8217;ll look at an app that allows you to purchase and sell stocks without paying commissions or exploring a muddled trading platform. Peruse on if you like learning the nuts and bolts of trading for nothing.</p>
<div class="slider-carousel-group"><h5>Screenshots</h5><div class="owl-carousel carousel-screenshot"><div class="item">
                    <a href="" class="lightbox"><img decoding="async" src="  " alt="Screenshot"/></a>
                </div><div class="item">
                    <a href="" class="lightbox"><img decoding="async" src="  " alt="Screenshot"/></a>
                </div><div class="item">
                    <a href="" class="lightbox"><img decoding="async" src="  " alt="Screenshot"/></a>
                </div><div class="item">
                    <a href="" class="lightbox"><img decoding="async" src="  " alt="Screenshot"/></a>
                </div><div class="item">
                    <a href="" class="lightbox"><img decoding="async" src="  " alt="Screenshot"/></a>
                </div></div></div>
<p class="ql-align-justify"><strong>What Is Public.com?</strong></p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Public.com is a stock and ETF trading application established in 2017. It used to be named Matador and is a subsidiary of T3 Securities Inc, which is a broker-trader. Public.com uses an outsider, Apex Clearing, to deal with the regulatory stuff of running Public client accounts.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Public.com is one of the commission-free platforms out there. It doesn&#8217;t need a minimum deposit for you to start investing. Also, the platform does not use Payment For Order Flow which is when brokers get to pay to direct orders to third parties for trade requests to outsiders for trade execution.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">This app has great features for executing trades. You can choose to give a tip to the specialist for executing the trade. This dispenses with irreconcilable situations among traders and clients.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify"><strong>The public review</strong> reveals that the application allows you to purchase fragmentary offers (which it calls &#8220;slices&#8221;). This implies you can buy short of one whole portion of the stock. Partial offers prove to be useful when you&#8217;d prefer to purchase, say, Amazon, which as of now trades for quite some high cost per share.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">The platform has an inspirational motto, it says, &#8220;Everyone&#8217;s an Investor.&#8221; In case you&#8217;re searching for an app that is a breeze to use and allows you to purchase and sell on the stock market, this application works effectively in addressing those needs. Remember, it doesn&#8217;t have the complete range of features, tools, and research that you find with other online platforms.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">While Public makes purchasing and selling stocks and ETFs free and simple, its features are fairly restricted when compared to other big brokers that allow you to trade stocks and ETFs without paying commissions. Public.com doesn&#8217;t support bonds, mutual funds, or other similar investments. Besides, the app has limited research on each stock.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify"><strong>How Does Public Work?</strong></p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Public accounts are easy to open. You can finish the new account signup in under five minutes.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Whenever you&#8217;re signed in and reserve your account, it is easy to navigate, look for stocks and ETFs, see other clients&#8217; portfolios, and begin purchasing and selling.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">As of now, Public provides just individual taxable brokerage accounts. There are no joint or IRA accounts.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">You can see essential insights concerning each upheld security. That incorporates a value history, expert appraisals and value targets, forthcoming income occasions, late news, and essential things.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">There is sufficient data to kick you off but it well might be a smart thought to carry out more external analysis before purchasing or selling. It&#8217;s a great deal of data for a novice to process, however light for a specialist or progressed financial backer.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify"><strong>Fractional Share Investing</strong></p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Rather than entering orders for a fixed number of offers, you can purchase partial offers. To do this, you essentially enter a dollar sum. You can number any measure of slices you need.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">For instance, if a stock expenses $1,000 per offer and you need to invest $100, you can purchase 0.1 offers. Or,  if stock costs $300 per share and you need to invest $500, you could purchase 1.6 shares. That makes any stock or ETF reasonable for any active merchant or long-term investor financial backer.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Remember that Public isn&#8217;t the lone Investing platform that allows you to trade fractional offers. You&#8217;ll discover this component with a couple of stock traders and Robo guides we&#8217;ve investigated, including, M1 Finance, Betterment, Stash, and Stockpile, to give some examples.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify"><strong>Themes</strong></p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">You can peruse stocks and assets by classification, which Public.com calls “themes.&#8221; For instance, &#8220;Race to Space&#8221; highlights organizations that are ready to profit from the space revolution.&#8221;</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">This list incorporates Shopify, Intuit, and GoDaddy, among others.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify"><strong>Public Investor Profiles</strong></p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">When you pursue a Public account, you make a Public investor profile with a public username. Anybody in the Public people group can see your profile. You can take a gander at other Public investor profiles for thoughts and motivation.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">There are likewise some &#8220;celebrity&#8221; profiles that are not difficult to track down and see. Furthermore, you can interface with your phone&#8217;s location book to check whether anybody you realize is on the platform.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify"><strong>No Commissions</strong></p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Public.com doesn&#8217;t charge any trading expenses or commissions. Similarly, as with each business, there might be some little SEC and TAF charges.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify"><strong>Safety Labels</strong></p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">When you go to purchase a stock or ETF, Public.com will have a name on the item if it&#8217;s viewed as hazardous by the Protections and Trade Commission. While all stocks have a touch of danger, some are less secure than others and Public.com recognizes those that are viewed as extremely hazardous.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">For instance, an organization that has filed for bankruptcy has a more significant level of danger than an organization that is making profits. Our <strong>Public review</strong> helps to determine whether a stock is riskier or not permits you to settle on a well-informed choice about whether to put resources into that stock or ETF.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify"><strong>Account Security</strong></p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Public.com is SIPC-safeguarded, which implies that every client&#8217;s securities investment is safe and secure up to $500,000. Sums up to $250,000 are likewise covered.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify"><strong>Investment Products</strong></p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Investing with Public.com will bring you admittance to about 3,000 of the top traded offers and ETFs. This is a fantastic determination given the mobile nature of this platform. The entirety of the offers accessible is traded on leading US markets like the NYSE or NASDAQ. Outside of this, the investment is restricted to shield financial backers from excessively hazardous ventures.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">You can also browse the available assets by theme or classification on the app itself. This makes it simpler for you as a trader to discover or recognize potential offers you might be keen on or which may fit the subject of the portfolio you are building. Stocks and ETFs just are offered as tradable resources by Open as of now.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">However, what truly separates Public.com as an extraordinary choice for new or easygoing financial investors specifically, is the admittance to fractional trading. This implies you don&#8217;t need to purchase an entire stock. Instead, you can put resources into a level of that significant stock that you can bear.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify"><strong>Trading Platform</strong></p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">All trading with Public.com is done through their application. This implies there is no desktop or electronic trading stage accessible. Each activity you perform with the broker happens through the application which you can download for both Android and iOS gadgets.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">The app is the soul of the whole activity, you would anticipate that it should be fun and easy to use. This is the situation and for trading, the application is very simple to navigate, discover the offers or ETFs you wish to put resources into, and place your trades. This easy-to-understand approach unveils an ideal decision again for the more current merchants in the business.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">An incredible addition to the application and broker is the reality you can also draw on the social side with different brokers or your companions.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">This implies you can gain some useful understanding of the trading patterns of other traders by taking part in discussions that center around investing.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">This group messaging style is also an excellent way for you to stay updated with any recent developments and continue to boost your knowledge of certain assets or trading.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify"><strong>Education</strong></p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Education at Public takes an unexpected structure in comparison to what you might find with other brokers. While a vast of top trading merchants will have committed training areas where you can work through instructional exercises and organized learning courses, this isn&#8217;t the situation at Public.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">There is still a great deal of instructive substance to be found through their site, yet the lion&#8217;s share comes from other investing individuals and merchants.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">You will likewise access recent news in the business as it breaks and gets familiar with resources and the more extensive industry.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify"><strong>Customer Support</strong></p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">As a trader, there are various approaches to connect with the Public team and what they advance through their site as &#8220;top tier&#8221; client assistance.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">You can reach them on them if you need anything via web-based live chat that is accessible to enrolled clients, send them an email or call during the long stretches of 9 am-5 pm EST when the business sectors are open.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Before calling, there are many committed FAQs replied through the Public site segment both by the actual organization and other community members. There is an opportunity then that you will discover the appropriate response you are searching for without expecting to contact the team.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify"><strong>Trust</strong></p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Regarding trust and regulation, while Public.com may appear to be a moderately new name in the sector. However,  they have indeed been around for quite a while. The organization is managed by FINRA and secured under SIPC. This will give your insurance for portfolio resources up to $500,000 or money totals of up to $250,000.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Public.com began working in 2017 however before that, they had been known as Matador. They are an auxiliary of T3 securities and their SEC documenting shows they have been enlisted with the body since 2004.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Add to that the reality that their application adjusts to all security and encryption norms would hope to keep your information free from any harm using AES 128-digit encryption and TLS 1.2 ensuring your trade respectability, at that point, you are very much shrouded in trading with Public as a straightforward and secure choice.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">From the viewpoint of different brokers, the standing of Public.com is likewise one of trust. There seem to have had no been security concerns or grumblings documented during their time working in the area.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify"><strong>Public.Com Usability</strong></p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">The Public investing platform targets new investors with social media aspects, themes, and fractional shares. The first thing for you as a new user is to choose a username and set up your profile. You’ll be required to pick certain themes to follow like meatless food or self-driving cars. You’ll then follow other investors on this platform. After you’ve built a social feed, you’ll be able to view who’s investing in what stocks and how often they’re buying.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify"><strong> <div class="ups-downs"><h5>Pros / Cons</h5><div class="row"><div class="col-md-6 col-sm-12"><div class="icon green"><i class="fa fa-chevron-up" aria-hidden="true"></i></div><ul><li>Praesent sed semper mauris, nec eleifend nibh</li><li>Donec ultricies placerat neque, eu malesuada lacus dignissim in</li><li>Praesent sed semper mauris, nec eleifend nibh</li><li>Praesent sed semper mauris, nec eleifend nibh</li></ul></div><div class="col-md-6 col-sm-12"><div class="icon red"><i class="fa fa-chevron-down" aria-hidden="true"></i></div><ul><li>Donec ultricies placerat neque, eu malesuada lacus dignissim in</li><li>Donec ultricies placerat neque, eu malesuada lacus dignissim in</li><li>Donec ultricies placerat neque, eu malesuada lacus dignissim in</li></ul></div></div></div></strong></p>
<p class="ql-align-justify"><strong>Pros</strong></p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">·         Partial offer and ETFs trading are accessible.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">·         Commission-free trading.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">·         Truly open and simple to use mobile app.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">·         In-built social trading features.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify"><strong>Cons</strong></p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">·         Only mobile trading is available.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">·         Assets are limited to ETFs and major shares.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Public.com is a trusted organization that is both regulated and has a good reputation in this. They profit from the current market pattern by offering an amazingly serious and commission-free trading climate on fractional offers and that&#8217;s only the tip of the iceberg.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Combine this with the evident availability of their top and comprehensive versatile application environment and you have a champ if you are hoping to trade major or fractional shares requiring little to no effort and with the capacity to participate in social trading progressing.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">There is no doubt the organization in its present structure is youthful with a lot of room to advance and develop.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">It’s evident from this <strong>Public review</strong> that advanced and intermediate traders will probably find Public.com not sufficiently able to address their issues. By and large, the platform might not be ideal for everybody. However, Public can be a pleasant choice for novice investors hoping to begin with stocks and ETFs.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify"><strong>Conclusion</strong></p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">This <strong>Public review</strong> demonstrates that this is an app-based stock trading broker that has a wide range of features. The app enables single stock trading, fragmentary share trading, and numerous social trading components. The app gives you the capacity to see the trades of different merchants and speak with them.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">These inventive highlights follow the latest thing in unveiling extremely applicable and the openness they furnish with no base store or trade sum required slings them into the discussion as a top versatile and sans commission agent.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/review/public/">Public Review</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">MrStocks.org</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/review/public/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>XTB Review</title>
		<link>/review/xtb/</link>
					<comments>/review/xtb/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Maximilian Weber]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2017 15:14:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://demos.pokatheme.com/pokatheme/?post_type=affiliates&#038;p=230</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>On XTB, traders can trade real stocks and pay a 0% commission. They invest in the most successful companies, such as Apple, Amazon and Tesla. X Trade Brokers is one of the world&#8217;s leading Forex and CFD brokers. XTB provides traders with straightforward and instant access to hundreds of financial markets around the world. This [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/review/xtb/">XTB Review</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">MrStocks.org</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On XTB, traders can trade real stocks and pay a 0% commission. They invest in the most successful companies, such as Apple, Amazon and Tesla. X Trade Brokers is one of the world&#8217;s leading Forex and CFD brokers. XTB provides traders with straightforward and instant access to hundreds of financial markets around the world. This online broker scores with a clear platform and a wide range of financial products, such as stocks and ETFs, which promise high returns when trading. Based on the XTB broker experience, XTB offers top service around the clock and the basic requirements for successful ETF and CFD trading. In this article we compile the main advantages, strengths and XTB experiences as well as the offers and services of X Trade Brokers.</p>

<p>Why should you trade through XTB Broker?</p>
<p>XTB works ceaselessly to improve its own trading platform and adapt it to the needs of traders. The highest level of security and protection of investors is provided by the largest regulatory bodies, which also controls and regulates X Trade Brokers. In recent years, the online broker has managed to become the award-winning trading platform that helps its clients trade on a daily basis.</p>
<p>The company was once founded in Warsaw and today it has managed to gain international influence. The XTB Depot is available to customers in Germany in German and shares its many years of experience with active traders and newcomers. Thus, it is possible to test yourself on the XTB portal with a free demo account and, starting from the first risk-free experiences, to use your own assets specifically in stocks and bonds.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Who or what is XTB?</p>
<p>XTB has an experience of over 15 years and is today the fourth largest CFD and Forex broker listed on the stock exchange. The company has offices in over 13 countries around the world, which include Germany, the UK, France and Chile. Its key strengths include its wide range of financial offerings and high-quality technology. These strengths at XTB are trusted by more than 220,000 customers. The employees do everything they can to make xStation one of the largest and most successful trading platforms. At the same time, XTB has developed a trading app that has the essential functions.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>What trading instruments does XTB offer on the online platform?</p>
<p>XTB aims to specifically improve the trading experience of its customers. You have access to the global financial markets and can invest your money in the following financial products:</p>
<p>Currencies<br />
ETF savings plans<br />
Indices<br />
Commodities</p>
<p>With xStation, XTB has developed a platform that helps all clients manage Forex positions. Opening an account takes only a few minutes. You can trade CFD on 48 currency pairs with this provider. The most popular currency pairs include eur USD and GBP USD, as well as AUD USD.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>CFD Trading: Trade CFDs with XTB Stocks</p>
<p>The CFDs are the Contracts for Difference or the contracts for difference. This refers to the agreement that has fallen between a trader and the XTB broker on the price developments in the underlying assets. CFDs are leveraged derivatives and maximum leverage of 30 to 1. Traders benefit from falling and rising prices when trading CFDs at XTB. Variable spreads and different asset classes offer traders a wide range of choice when trading CFDs.</p>
<p>CAUTION: The risk of losing money is not to be dismissed when trading with CFD. Start CFD trading with an XTB demo account and take advice in the live chat or by e-mail, so as not to make too high losses and learn about Forex trading.</p>
<p>Stock CFDs are also derivatives. This means that you do not own the underlying assets, but speculate on the fall and rise of prices via XTB broker. For example, if you buy 1,000 shares of Commerzbank and the current share price is 12.80 euros, the amount of the total investment via XTB would come to 12,800 euros. In addition, there are the commissions and the fees that are incurred individually for the respective transactions between the XTB broker and the stock exchange. In return, customers receive a share certificate. This is a legal document that confirms your ownership of the CFDs. Accordingly, you have a physical proof in your hands and take a tidy profit in the best case.</p>
<p>Potentially, CFD trading clients benefit from the same movements of the stock price &#8211; online you can manage and control your position at any time. Compared to traditional trading, you can make CFD transactions faster at XTB. However, you should keep in mind that the lucrative profits in trading can just as quickly turn into the opposite. The broker XTB from Frankfurt am Main recommends from therefore alone its users to first put virtual money with a demo account.</p>
<p>ETF CFDS trading on the trading platform XStation</p>
<p>Among the first decisions on the XTB trading platform is the amount of trading volume for the respective positions. At the broker XTB from Frankfurt am Main, there is a detailed report and guide on what you should consider when choosing bonds and the investment amount. Per account, you have a certain amount of initial assets with the demo account. This is digital money that you can not withdraw cash to your account. Based on the XTB test, these demo versions have proven to be extremely viable to test out the features and not put some of the assets at risk for this.</p>
<p>Trading assets depends on the risk aversion of shareholders and your own emotional well-being. This is how XTB combines wealth management with risk management. So you should understand how the trading volume can affect your future financial decisions. The volume that the client sets determines the coverage, which in technical language is called margin, as well as the value of the pip.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>XTB Experience: How to open a margin at XTB broker?</p>
<p>For a trade, you need a certain amount of security. This is called margin or cover in the trading language. This area is not part of the actual costs. The amount of money is frozen, so to speak, as soon as customers open a position. The XTB broker keeps the margin until the transaction is completed. Before that, it is necessary to determine how much the margin amount is when trading through XTB. This will help you determine the actual risk associated with trading. In addition, you can determine whether you have enough left from the remaining financial resources to open other positions through XTB.</p>
<p>This is particularly interesting in the case of CFDs, because these only take up a fraction of the nominal value. This then allows you to open multiple positions with a lower stake. The maximum leverage is allowed at this XTB broker at 1 to 30. This in turn equates to 3.33% of the nominal value as margin so that you can execute a transaction via XTB. The typical leverage in trading is 1 to 30 anyway, so it is possible for the customer to achieve a higher return on the capital invested. However, at the same time, the risk of losing the money completely increases. You should always be aware of these dangers. Anyone who has no or little experience with CFD trading should in no case start with the bonds in this area at XTB.</p>
<p>An example calculation for margin on XTB</p>
<p>Let&#8217;s discuss the whole thing with a simple example and the most popular currency pair GBP USD with one lot and leverage set at 1:30. At this point, however, we do not know what the nominal value per lot is. You can find all the necessary information when trading directly on the broker for each financial instrument. Through this transparency and overview, XTB makes trading easier for its customers.</p>
<p>In this case, we arrive at a nominal value per lot, which is £100,000. If you now set the leverage at 1 to 30, you only need a margin of 3.33%. In this case, this would correspond to £3,333 if you want to complete a transaction with one lot. It is a basic principle in CFD trading that no trader or client should enter into a transaction with a margin that is greater than 30% in relation to their own capital. This is what years of experience have shown.</p>
<p>Take this formula also as a principle to avoid taking too high risks when trading CFDs through this provider. To be on the safe side, you should check where the maximum margin is when opening the transaction. Otherwise, you run the risk of not following the rules. If you keep to the extremely strict rules of risk management at this broker, you will also increase your chances of success in increasing returns and profits.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<div class="slider-carousel-group"><h5>Screenshots</h5><div class="owl-carousel carousel-screenshot"><div class="item">
                    <a href="" class="lightbox"><img decoding="async" src="  " alt="Screenshot"/></a>
                </div><div class="item">
                    <a href="" class="lightbox"><img decoding="async" src="  " alt="Screenshot"/></a>
                </div><div class="item">
                    <a href="" class="lightbox"><img decoding="async" src="  " alt="Screenshot"/></a>
                </div><div class="item">
                    <a href="" class="lightbox"><img decoding="async" src="  " alt="Screenshot"/></a>
                </div><div class="item">
                    <a href="" class="lightbox"><img decoding="async" src="  " alt="Screenshot"/></a>
                </div></div></div>
<p>XTB Experience: What influence does the pip value have on XTB trading?</p>
<p>A second important factor in this area is the pip value. You should definitely know this value if you are in a safe risk management area . Thus, it is useful to know what the impact on your financial portfolio is if, for example, the market changes by 100 pips against you or in your favor.</p>
<p>Go to the itemized statement online on the broker&#8217;s website and read up. Then you can access the most important information about a financial instrument. If you want to calculate the pip value for a lot, take the nominal value per lot for this and multiply it by the size of a pip. You always specify the value in the respective currency, for example in US dollars or British pounds or euros. For example, if we have a nominal value of 100,000 and 0.001 pips, you multiply 100,000 and 0.001 to come to ten US dollars in the end.</p>
<p>So what does this mean as an example for trading on XTB? Let&#8217;s assume you open a transaction on the currency pair British pound and US dollar with one lot. The market changes by 100 pips in your favor. In this case, you make a profit of $1000 by multiplying $10 by 100 pips. With this simple calculation you can quickly determine where the maximum profits and losses are and in this context you can also set the stop loss. By setting this function, the depository will stop the position if it falls below a specified level range. This is to protect you from unforeseen losses.</p>
<p>XTB scores with enormous advantage in this area, such as with the privileged Pro model. Here, only 0.1 pips of fees are incurred per trade. You still have to calculate plus the other costs. You should have realized at this point that with knowledge of the individual technical terms and size values, you can much better assess when to invest which amount in which stocks and bonds. XTB helps its customers at every point with tutorials and guides as well as explanations. After all, the point is to specifically form your money and learn from the XTB experience.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Broker XTB program &#8211; Metatrader 4</p>
<p>We do not have to tell you at this point that their success as a trader begins with the right trading platform. X Trade Brokers have made it their business to develop their own system that makes it easy to start trading. Customers can enjoy an innovative and easy-to-use trading platform designed according to your needs. Meanwhile, XTB has already received many awards for this. A quality feature is the fast and uncomplicated order execution and the simple and intuitive design. After a few small instructional videos, even beginners should be able to effortlessly find their way around and watch the stock prices.</p>
<p>A multi-award winning team of analysts create the overview in a user-friendly board, which you access via desktop or from your smartphone. The trading calculator provides an overview of all costs and profits before you open a position. You trade all financial products through one platform without ever losing track. For this, X Trade Brokers relies on the operation of a single trading account and more than 4000 financial products. In X Station you can see the chart. This can be customized to your individual preferences, depending on which bonds and stocks you have purchased through XTB.</p>
<p>At X Trader Brokers you can quickly change your settings, because in the dashboard of the financial control center you can not really miss anything. Come to one of the largest listed Forex and CFD brokers there is in the world. The company may not have imagined that it would have such a global impact either, when it was founded back in Warsaw. But today, this provider scores with its clients with the strengths you would want from an international market maker.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>What are the advantages of Metatrader 4?</p>
<p>If you want to trade without distractions, you will probably choose Metatrader 4. The MT4 platform is supposed to make trading easier than ever before. You analyze all financial instruments in a few moments and automate trading. This makes it even easier for experienced and inexperienced clients to regularly rake in high returns without having to worry about your trading account 24/7.</p>
<p>Metatrader 4 is used for technical analysis, among other things, and to be one of the first to identify trends. In this program you set the entry and exit points individually and define stop loss and limit. This way you can prevent losing all your assets in one go. That is why MT4 is one of the most used programs for trading platforms, appreciated by clients all over the world.</p>
<p>MT4 is their strategy tester at XTB and can improve the automatic trading systems &#8211; EAs for short &#8211; for its clients in a straightforward and fast way. You have the possibility to perform back-tests for the respective strategies to find the best option for your trading at XTB.Benefit from the numerous solutions within the MQL4 community that are offered with automated trading through this broker.</p>
<p>The xstation 5 at XTB</p>
<p>This is an award-winning trading platform of the latest generation. xStation 5 works intuitively and can be fully customized to your needs. In addition to technical analyses, you can use numerous statistical tools with xStation 5, such as an ETF or a stock scanner that performs professional market analyses for XTB. Get access to numerous tutorials and training videos and train yourself to become a successful trader with years of experience.</p>
<p>You can open your free demo account at XTB today. To do so, simply fill out the form on the website and then start trading on xStation 5 &#8211; The best thing: It doesn&#8217;t cost a cent with this broker.</p>
<p>xStation 5 was awarded Best Trading Platform by the online Personal Wealth Awards in 2016. As a thank you, XTB gives 10,000 euros of virtual capital for each customer and each new demo account registration per account. Based on the current XTB test, every customer per account is left with two different options to use the innovative platforms. Thus, there are xStation 5 and Metatrader 4 at XTB. From an in-house development, it is actually completely irrelevant how much experience you bring. XTB scores with a rich repertoire and an easy-to-use platform designed for any trader.</p>
<p>CAUTION: Nearly 80% of all small investor accounts lose money trading CFDs with this provider as well. You should think carefully whether you can afford this risk at all, even with XTB. Always use for trading only the part of your assets that you can really spare and do not upload too much money with the broker.</p>
<div class="ups-downs"><h5>Pros / Cons</h5><div class="row"><div class="col-md-6 col-sm-12"><div class="icon green"><i class="fa fa-chevron-up" aria-hidden="true"></i></div><ul><li>Praesent sed semper mauris, nec eleifend nibh</li><li>Donec ultricies placerat neque, eu malesuada lacus dignissim in</li><li>Praesent sed semper mauris, nec eleifend nibh</li><li>Praesent sed semper mauris, nec eleifend nibh</li></ul></div><div class="col-md-6 col-sm-12"><div class="icon red"><i class="fa fa-chevron-down" aria-hidden="true"></i></div><ul><li>Donec ultricies placerat neque, eu malesuada lacus dignissim in</li><li>Donec ultricies placerat neque, eu malesuada lacus dignissim in</li><li>Donec ultricies placerat neque, eu malesuada lacus dignissim in</li></ul></div></div></div>
<p>The Trading Academy: XTB experience and learn</p>
<p>The Trading Academy is the educational area at XTB. Part of this area are the lessons and content from the trading area. This includes eBooks, recordings of past webinars, articles and other topics that XTB offers and provides free of charge to new customers as well as active traders. According to the XTB experience, the teaching units are classified as follows:</p>
<p>Beginner<br />
Advanced<br />
Expert<br />
Premium</p>
<p>Alternatively, you can be displayed in the Trading Academy according to the topics or the lessons. For each topic, the expert editors publish a detailed article and a video in the Trading Academy. In this way, you can specifically expand your XTB experience. To test the learned knowledge in practice at the broker XTB, you must then open a live account or you test the demo version of the X Trade Brokers.</p>
<p>XTB has compiled a trading encyclopedia for its customers, which gives you the chance to look up unknown terms.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Step-by-step guide: Open a live account with XTB</p>
<p>You will be redirected to the registration in a few steps starting from the home page. This is about opening a securities account with the broker XTB. For this, the CFD broker asks for the investor&#8217;s email address and sends you a confirmation email with a link in the next moment. From there you will get to the step-by-step creation of the account at X Trade Brokers.</p>
<p>You will lose money if you hastily deposit cash into the account and then speculate on stocks and bonds whose function you do not know or cannot estimate. When trading, you should not take too high risks if you could not live with a loss.</p>
<p>Attention, if you want to access the full features of the Trading Academy, you should open a free demo account at XTB. You will not take any risk with it and you can extract your advantages when trading CFDs and take regular returns. If you want to deposit cash, convert this demo account into a real account. XTB offers its new and experienced traders regular offers and discounts for this, which will make it easier for you to get started. You will not lose any time in trading if you immediately proceed with the broker test on the trading platform and follow the steps of XTB to the final trading account. Of course, this account also works for mobile trading on your smartphone.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Which XTB account suits me?</p>
<p>At XTB, there are different account types, which are based on the XTB experience of traders. In the standard account, XTB offers CFDs on commodities, forex, stocks, indices, ETF, cryptocurrencies and real stocks. In total, more than 4,000 tradable instruments are available to every customer on the trading platform. Traders set the maximum leverage for CFDs at 1 : 30 with a minimum order size at 0.01 lots. XTB offers its customers a free standard account opening and use of AgendaTrader and xStation. The fees for traders in Germany are 0.08 percent and a minimum of 8.00 euros for the standard account. If the monthly turnover through the XTB broker does not exceed 100,000 euros, traders pay 0 percent commissions for shares and ETF savings plans.</p>
<p>Tip: Download the PDF with the complete list of fees and commissions directly from the X Trade Brothers website. This way you will always keep track of your expenses and fees when trading CFDs.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Is X Trade Brokers custody account suitable for professional traders?</p>
<p>For the beginners and the newbies, XTB offers an appropriate entry level section, but the X Trade Brokers team has by no means failed to target its professionals. A professional client has the chance to set a maximum leverage on CFDs to 200 to 1, at least for the most important currency pairs such as Euro and US Dollar. For the most important indices such as DE30 and gold, the maximum leverage is also 200 to 1. Other commodities such as oils, for example, you have a leverage in CFDs of 67 to 1 at your disposal and 5 to 1 for cryptocurrencies. This opens up completely new possibilities for you at XTB as a professional and makes an account with X Trade Brokers so much more lucrative.</p>
<p>You benefit from capital protection via segregated accounts and from a waiver of the margin call. The latter is a legal provision that saves traders from debts with a broker like XTB. For example, if you make a mistake, you can lose a maximum of all your assets in the account with XTB. However, it is not possible to slip into a minus at any time.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Why register with XTB?</p>
<p>Are you still wondering why you should choose XTB as your professional? X Trade Brokers values each and every client as a partner. The employees are there for you and your questions around the clock. Thus, XTB attaches great importance to a long-term relationship and therefore offers you more than 3,000 CFD financial instruments. So it&#8217;s not just about opening an account with XTB and then being one of many traders left alone with the market action and bonds. It is about XTB being a trustworthy and regulated broker.</p>
<p>By using advanced trading technology, XTB avoids requotes that can occur in the event of delays between the time of placement and execution of the order. In any case, XTB is all about smooth execution of each or and high satisfaction of all customers who move on the platform.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Get the latest market analysis from S Trade Brokers</p>
<p>Take your opportunity and retrieve the market analyses via XTB. Every day, XTB publishes lucrative promotions on the portal and free news that assess the economic situation and market events in a consistent and timely manner. In addition to breaking news join crypto analysis, which in turn discuss the development of bitcoin after strong sell-offs or key investigations. If commodities fall, currently no clear trenfstruktur for certain bonds can be seen or other stocks in turn rise by several percentage points, you will be the first to know about it on XTB in the market analysis.</p>
<p>These analyses and news are more proof that the X Trade Brokers, not simply a depot have developed, but rather a global platform, which has developed with the lucrative investment for private investors and for active traders with years of experience. You can use much of this information and additional features completely free of charge, even if you have not yet created an account with XTB.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>How secure is XTB Broker?</p>
<p>On the portal there is an opportunity to participate in webinars to learn about xStation and the trading platform. Basically, the broker puts everything on the safety of its traders and wants to protect you from losing too much. Nevertheless, there is a huge risk associated with CFD and Forex trading. You lose money if you speculate or do not inform yourself sufficiently about the current market events.</p>
<p>For this reason, XTB uses additional security systems to improve protection on the trading platform. For the Basic account model, for example, XTB uses a guaranteed stop loss. In case of stronger market fluctuations, this guaranteed stop loss can ensure that an order was executed at a desired price. This excludes the possibility of slippage. Of course, a guaranteed stop loss does not cause unnecessary costs, it is only intended to increase safety.</p>
<p>In addition, an exclusion of the obligation to make additional margin is guaranteed. If the deposited capital of a trader is no longer sufficient to cover all his services, you do not have to inject additional capital. Your losses can never exceed the stake. BaFin issued this general ruling for CFDs in 2017, after which CFD brokers had three months to implement this obligation.</p>
<p>The XTB broker founded in 2002 and its headquarters in Warsaw. The broker is regulated by the German BaFin as well as the Polish Supervisory Authority for Security and Trade. So, the capital that you invest with this broker is secured by the Deposit Insurance Fund of the State Securities Administration Office in Warsaw. Therefore, all the evidence that XTB Broker is a reputable provider. Client funds are kept separately from the company&#8217;s funds. This is to protect their assets in the event of insolvency of XTB.</p>
<p>Due to the regulation of BaFin, the German Federal Financial Supervisory Authority, private deposits are safe and secure from the threat of an insolvent broker.</p>
<p>Customer service: How accessible is the broker XTB?</p>
<p>Five days a week you can reach the customer service over 24 hours. On the trading platform, the professionals answer your concerns and questions. Every trader is assigned a personal contact person who will perform a strategy analysis and assist you at any time. For this reason, it is also possible for beginners to join XTB Broker and speculate. If you have virtually no XTB experience, you should first take a look at the trading platform without depositing any money. For beginners and for advanced traders, there are a variety of offers and training opportunities.</p>
<p>In addition, XTB regularly releases new trading packages on the trading platform, including free eBooks and informative articles as well as the daily news and analyses, the Trading Academy 2.0, the ePaper and recordings of webinars. The XTB professionals are all about educating you and helping you learn more about bonds, ETFs, CFDs, stocks and shares.</p>
<p>X Trader Brokers has a base at Mainzer Landstraße 47, 60329 Frankfurt am Main. You can describe an email to XTB at info@xtb.de. The response to the e-mail will take one to three days, depending on the volume. You will receive a confirmation in your mailbox immediately after sending the e-mail. Further, there are various service hotlines to help you with the operation and trading:</p>
<p>Account opening: 0800-9872330<br />
Customer service: 069-96759232<br />
General questions 069-24006868<br />
Marketing: 0800-9872330</p>
<p>It goes without saying that at XTB, German-speaking staff will answer the phone and help you through the next steps. Once they have registered, you should always have their login details ready.</p>
<p>Around the clock you can ask your questions and learn more about the features and the stocks. You will lose money if you don&#8217;t take advantage of these offers and invest in random stocks while trading without knowledge. XTB offers stock CFDs, live account, fair CFD trading and deposit protection fund from the government securities depository. This makes CFD trading so safe and transparent at the same time.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>What is the XTB experience with the trading platform?</p>
<p>XTB or X Trader Brokers is one of the best-known European brokers that specializes in particular in trading forex and CFDs. The regulation of the platform is carried out by BaFin, which XTB has a branch in Germany. Meanwhile, more than 100,000 customers trust the platform &#8211; on the trading platform you have access to the web-based, brokers own and MetaTrader 4 platform. One of the highlights X Trade Brokers offers is via social trading. The main focus is on communication between clients. Everything you need to know about the online broker can be found directly on the home page. The XTB Broker experiences are clearly in favor of the active support and also praise the webinars. Here you can share your wealth of experience in terms of CFD trading and the functions of the platform.</p>
<p>In the XTB experiences, some traders also express criticism of the partly unstable platform and the not always optimal courses. In part, the distances for the limits and the stops are set too high and the traders do not have the chance to trade microlots with this CFD broker. X Trade Brothers deal with customer opinions in a transparent manner. This way, you build customer loyalty and increase trust even towards the new customers.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Summary: How good is XTB really?</p>
<p>X Trade Brothers is one of the leading Forex brokers for CFD trading. Trading at XTB is considered to be safe and fast. Whether Forex or CFD, you can reach XTB staff and advisors around the clock via live chat or email. As the best CFD broker, the provider is subject to the Federal Financial Supervisory Authority BaFin. Traders rate the large selection of financial products, the market maker, Metatrader 4, Forex and CFD, the variable spreads and the XTB demo account just as positively as the returns that arise when trading CFD. With a free account, you can relatively safely place the first orders through the deposit at XTB and invest your assets profitably when trading.</p>
<p>My XTB experience: The broker XTB has been around for some time. There are also good reasons for this. After all, you can trade CFDs and foreign exchange at X Trade Brokers. At the same time, you can also trade binary options. This is an important aspect. After all, you can not practice this form of trading at most brokers in this form. Therefore, the online broker XTB is the first choice for many investors. At least one can enjoy a great variety. In addition, there is a German regulation by BaFin. Thus, a high level of security can be enabled at the X Trade Brokers. With the additional deposit protection, there should be no more doubts about the seriousness of this X Trade broker when using XTB. This is also confirmed by the numerous positive reviews about the XTB broker. Everywhere in the trading forums you can read how good XTB really is.</p>
<p>Interestingly, the XTB experiences show that you can use a demo version. As with many other X Trade brokers, one can participate in an extensive training program at XTB. In this way, one can deepen his knowledge and skills in selected areas at the broker XTB. The demo version helps investors to take their first steps at the XTB broker without any risks. At the same time, this version is suitable for experienced traders who want to create and execute new strategies at the XTB broker.</p>
<p>The standard account can be used by all investors at the XTB broker without any fees. Although there is a premium account, but it is not so interesting for most users.</p>
<p>Deposit opening with the broker XTB</p>
<p>Fortunately, opening a securities account with the XTB broker is simple. In addition, the registration process is based on that of most other X Trade brokers. Those who have already registered for a similar provider will have no difficulties with the XTB broker. For the account opening, you only need to fill out a form, which can be found directly on the website. It must also be said that the XTB broker makes it very easy for new customers.</p>
<p>You do not have to search long until you find the section for registration. Many investors wish that the other X Trade brokers do as well as the XTB broker. At least that is what the numerous positive XTB experiences show. It is important to still enter the address for registration and answer some questions about trading. These questions are about existing knowledge and experience. If possible, you should answer these questions as accurately as possible. In this way, the broker XTB can help the new customer to make the first right steps. If you have entered all the data, a check is made and the customer account is activated at the broker XTB.</p>
<p>Subsequently, the recommendation is to get an overview. In this way, I can familiarize myself with the environment of the broker XTB. Experienced traders recommend beginners to first stay in the demo account to make the first experiences with the X Trade Brokers. The XTB experience shows the following again and again: Many beginners lose money. If they would at least take advantage of the demo account at X Trade Brokers, it would be much easier for them to become successful later.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the first steps lead to the numerous analysis tools and advanced functions. By the way, the web app also makes a good impression. You should use it right away for your mobile device so that you can access your X Trade Brokers securities account on the go. The training courses are an enrichment for every investor at XTB. The XTB experience shows that you should definitely use this offer of the Trading Academy. Traders who regularly watch instructional videos are much more successful later on. This is also due to the fact that these people have built a solid information base at the broker XTB. Subsequently, it is easier for these people to make better decisions at X Trade Brokers.</p>
<p>Overall, the first impression at the broker XTB is very good.</p>
<div class="slider-carousel-group"><h5>Screenshots</h5><div class="owl-carousel carousel-screenshot"><div class="item">
                    <a href="" class="lightbox"><img decoding="async" src="  " alt="Screenshot"/></a>
                </div><div class="item">
                    <a href="" class="lightbox"><img decoding="async" src="  " alt="Screenshot"/></a>
                </div><div class="item">
                    <a href="" class="lightbox"><img decoding="async" src="  " alt="Screenshot"/></a>
                </div><div class="item">
                    <a href="" class="lightbox"><img decoding="async" src="  " alt="Screenshot"/></a>
                </div><div class="item">
                    <a href="" class="lightbox"><img decoding="async" src="  " alt="Screenshot"/></a>
                </div></div></div>
<p>Deposit with the XTB broker</p>
<p>The first deposit into the standard account is very simple. Advantageous for most investors is certainly the fact that there is no minimum deposit. This is particularly convenient. Thus, all investors can immediately make XTB experience. By the way, the broker XTB works together with PayPal. For many traders, this payment service is the first choice. This is also due to the fact that the deposit can be made very quickly. On top of that, you save yourself long waiting times and can start trading with the broker XTB faster.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the XTB experience shows that you do not have to be afraid. After all, the X Trade Brokers has its headquarters in Frankfurt am Main and is supervised by BaFin. This ensures a high level of security. In addition, investors can look forward to professional and safe trading beidem X Trade Brokers.</p>
<p>An additional deposit guarantee protects customer funds, which makes the numerous investors positive XTB experience. A lot of variety is in the foreground at XTB. Thus, it is not boring at any time.</p>
<p>Trading at the X Trade Brokers</p>
<p>For trading at the XTB online broker there are several options. With a web interface, one can access varied trading instruments such as CFDs and Forex. Thus, one enjoys a high flexibility at the XTB online broker. Familiarization should not be a big problem even for beginners. The CFD broker XTB in Frankfurt am Main works similarly to other online brokers. The broker even allows trading binary options. Furthermore, the trading platform is clearly structured and understandable. The operation is intuitive, which makes the XTB experience positive.</p>
<p>The mobile app of XTB also provides a high degree of flexibility. On the smartphone, the securities account is always with the broker. In addition, you can look at his portfolio at any place and at any time. You can also monitor individual orders and place new orders. This allows for a high level of convenience. In addition, the operation of the XTB app is very simple and convenient. Most investors think that XTB is very customer-oriented and there are hardly any negative aspects. The majority of investors feel safe with the broker from Frankfurt am Main and would not want to leave there again.</p>
<p>The first trading experiences</p>
<p>Getting started trading with the XTB broker is unspectacular. Due to different strategies, one can trade successfully and use the bonus payment. Very gladly this bonus is applied to the binary options. However, one must never forget that this trading business is very risky. In order to be successful here, one should know the market sufficiently and observe it around the clock. For many investors CFD trading and trading in stocks CFDs have become a normality. This is no wonder. Many traders feel comfortable with the broker XTB. Whether they want to trade from 0.1 pips or Forex and CFDs. At XTB, these people will make fewer mistakes. Trading is explained very well to beginners at broker XTB. Therefore, they can make more money and keep the fees low.</p>
<p>The overview of the fees is very good and the transparency is high. The returns are appealing and the withdrawals can be made very quickly. While for most people trading stocks CFDs at XTB is a nice pastime, some people have already decided to earn a second income while trading on the XTB platform.</p>
<p>It can also be said that the returns are appealing. It is not for nothing that many people have withdrawals made. Admittedly, there are no fixed cycles for this. On the other hand, few traders consider their activities trading on XTB as the main income. It should not be like that in the first few months either.</p>
<p>A good tip is to lower your expectations. With a realistic attitude, you will experience fewer disappointments and continue to work on your goals without losing motivation. By the way, beginners and averagely experienced traders are happy if they earn enough money trading on XTB to buy a new washing machine or clothes. Expectations should not be higher in the beginning.</p>
<p>Are there any criticisms?</p>
<p>There is a lot of positive talk when trading on XTB. But what is the catch with CFD trading and trading in stock CFDs on XTB?</p>
<p>If there is something to criticize, then it is certainly the interest rate for the premium deposit. At the beginning it was already mentioned that this account plays a minor role for most investors. Interest is actually positive. However, only some people can benefit from the interest. As a normal user, one will not be able to take advantage of interest. Unfortunately, most investors find this a pity at XTB. With the bonus, it actually also works so that all customers get it. Apart from this shortcoming, XTB is an excellent broker. Another positive thing about XTB is the competent and friendly customer service.</p>
<p>The customer service can even be reached via live chat. This gives you a contact person and you can have your questions answered very quickly. In most cases, these are answered very directly and competently by the XTB employees. There is also a hotline. However, this is suitable for complex concerns.</p>
<p>Advantages and disadvantages at a glance</p>
<p>Advantages:</p>
<p>Regulation by the BaFin<br />
Large range of options<br />
Free registration<br />
German speaking customer service<br />
Different account types<br />
Mobile trading<br />
Stop Loss Function<br />
No minimum deposit.<br />
Demo account with 30 days limit<br />
Variable spreads<br />
Extensive teaching offer</p>
<p>Disadvantages:</p>
<p>Conditions for account types not clear or difficult to understand<br />
Demo account only for 30 days<br />
Bonus payments too different.</p>
<div class="ups-downs"><h5>Pros / Cons</h5><div class="row"><div class="col-md-6 col-sm-12"><div class="icon green"><i class="fa fa-chevron-up" aria-hidden="true"></i></div><ul><li>Praesent sed semper mauris, nec eleifend nibh</li><li>Donec ultricies placerat neque, eu malesuada lacus dignissim in</li><li>Praesent sed semper mauris, nec eleifend nibh</li><li>Praesent sed semper mauris, nec eleifend nibh</li></ul></div><div class="col-md-6 col-sm-12"><div class="icon red"><i class="fa fa-chevron-down" aria-hidden="true"></i></div><ul><li>Donec ultricies placerat neque, eu malesuada lacus dignissim in</li><li>Donec ultricies placerat neque, eu malesuada lacus dignissim in</li><li>Donec ultricies placerat neque, eu malesuada lacus dignissim in</li></ul></div></div></div>
<p>The most important facts about XTB<br />
Founded in Warsaw<br />
Branch office in 60329 Frankfurt am Main<br />
German-speaking service, Monday to Friday, around the clock<br />
Regulation in Germany by the German Federal Financial Supervisory Authority<br />
3,000 underlyings<br />
Maximum leverage 1:200.<br />
Security of client funds</p>
<p>The security of trading instruments is primarily guaranteed by the EU Financial Markets Directive. This means that the same requirements apply to all providers within the EU. Trading in Germany is supervised by the Federal Financial Supervisory Authority. Customer funds are held separately from company funds at Commerzbank. Customers benefit from statutory deposit protection. In addition, the extended voluntary deposit insurance takes effect.</p>
<p>XTB states that client and company funds are kept in different accounts. In addition, the XTB broker has set up a deposit protection fund. As a result, customer funds are protected up to an amount of 20,000 euros.</p>
<p>Trading conditions</p>
<p>Fortunately, trading at XTB is also possible without a minimum deposit. The smallest transaction size is 0.1 lot. The maximum leverage is 1:200. It should not be forgotten that the different account models have different conditions. These are not so easy to understand, especially for beginners. The minimum spread is between 2.0 and 0.1 pips. Thus, spreads starting from 0.1 pips are possible. In addition, other conditions apply depending on the order execution. Not to be forgotten is the fact that a fee of 3.50 euros is charged for CFD trading when opening and closing trades on commodities, indices and foreign exchange.</p>
<p>Trading offer: Large selection of tradable products</p>
<p>XTB offers traders a good opportunity to trade Forex and CFD as well as stocks and ETFs. At XTB, one gets access to 3,000 different trading instruments. This makes the XTB broker stand out from the competition. It is therefore worthwhile to study the selection of the Forex and CFD broker more closely. Fortunately, trading at XTB is associated with a lot of fun. You should by no means try to frantically get into trading just because you want to make a main income at XTB. By the way, the biggest components at the XTB broker are the following:</p>
<p>Stocks<br />
Indices<br />
Funds<br />
Commodities<br />
Foreign exchange<br />
Cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>Thereby, stocks take the largest share in the product portfolio. XTB offers over 1,500 different shares. These enable direct market access. The leverage is a maximum of 1:10. The order commissions are 0 percent provided that the monthly turnover is less than 100,000 euros. At the Frankfurt branch, one can buy shares of major market players such as Amazon and Google. Of course, you can also buy German shares. One should know that shares are traded here without leverage. This results in particularly low-risk trading options.</p>
<p>The indices commodities as well as CFD and Forex are traded around the clock. The customer benefits from 35 different indices. Here the spreads are particularly low. At the same time, liquidity is high. The leverage is a maximum of 1:200.</p>
<p>The offer is extended by Forex trading. At the branch in Frankfurt, the investor can decide in which sectors he wants to invest. The broker manages to offer a particularly interesting range. The Forex trading and CFD trading run very well at XTB. The broker stands out from the crowd.</p>
<p>Interestingly, in addition to commodities and precious metals trading, the broker also offers trading in agricultural commodities such as coffee and wheat. Admittedly, these are subject to enormous fluctuations. On the other hand, these trading instruments can be traded with a leverage of up to 1:66.</p>
<p>With its 49 currency pairs, XTB offers customers enough variety. In addition to the classic currencies, the investor can invest in so-called minor currencies such as the Australian dollar.</p>
<p>At the XTB broker, one can also invest in the popular cryptocurrencies. Available on the market at XTB are Bitcoin, Ethereum, Litecoin, Ripple and Dash. However, one can only trade these currencies via the xStation 5 platform.</p>
<p>On top of that, the open positions for the cryptocurrencies are limited to 50 lots. Trading is possible at XTB around the clock, seven days a week. Wallets are not necessary. At the same time, the spreads are very low.</p>
<p>Demo account: Free demo account with virtual credit</p>
<p>At XTB, you get a free demo account with the registration. Here you trade with virtual money. The balance is 10,000 euros, which is available for a period of 30 days. The trader can choose account type and trading platform like xStation 5.</p>
<p>The investor gets access to more than 3,000 CFD markets. Furthermore, the investor gets the opportunity to experience trading under real market conditions. Of course, there is no risk involved. Newcomers can thereby slowly approach the real-time trading. By the way, a free demo account is an excellent opportunity for beginners to learn their first steps. In addition, the demo account is used by experienced traders as well. These people design new strategies and test them under real market conditions. In this way, you get a better impression and understand better what will work later and what will not. The new customers can get to know the numerous functions in the XTB demo account and learn how to use xStation 5.</p>
<p>Not only the beginners, but also advanced traders will be happy with the free demo account. XTB unfortunately offers a XTB demo account, which is only valid for 30 days. After that, the beginners have to switch to the live account. XTB in the test has received only average ratings for the demo account. Losing money just in the beginning of the trading career is a big problem for many beginners. An unlimited demo account would help many of these people to develop a solid knowledge and practical skills so that they make fewer mistakes later in the live account.</p>
<p>For this, one has a personal contact person available with the demo account. This person is available for all questions. If you have any questions, you should contact the personal contact person by e-mail.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Bonus &#8211; Attractive welcome package</p>
<p>There is no classic bonus. On the other hand, customers can take advantage of numerous different bonuses. Premium customers, for example, earn interest on their credit balance. Depending on the current market situation, Pro customers benefit from a 2-4 percent return.</p>
<p>In addition, you get a variable bonus if you recommend XTB to others. Customers receive a subsidy as part of a cashback program. This takes place as part of spreads and commissions. The amount is based on the amount of trades achieved within a month. The cashback is transferred directly to the customer account.</p>
<p>Trading platform</p>
<p>At XTB you can trade via three trading platforms:</p>
<p>MetaTrader 4<br />
xStation 5<br />
Agena Trader.</p>
<p>By the way, Agena Trader is not for the Basic account. In addition, MetaTrader 4 should be common to most users. It has been around since 2005. On top of that, it is also the most popular trading platform. One benefits here from a classic design and advanced analytical tools. Due to the convenient and intuitive interface, one can customize the client area with numerous extensions. These include, for example, practical charting tools.</p>
<p>Furthermore, there are Expert Advisors, which are virtual agents. If you have some programming skills in MQL4, you can automate certain trading activities. These agents can be given some activities to save your own time.</p>
<p>Currently, the MetaTrader 4 platform is only available for Windows. However, MacOS users can install this program through PlayOnMac. Furthermore, traders can download the MetaTrader Mobile app from the broker. On Android and iOS, trading is just as much fun.</p>
<p>The traders who prefer a web-based trading platform with the broker should go for xStation 5. It was developed by XTB and convinces with a fast trade execution time of only 85 milliseconds.</p>
<p>When trading CFDs, one can benefit from practical instruments on xStation 5. These include:</p>
<p>A detailed trading history<br />
Interactive and detailed charts<br />
Technical analyses.</p>
<p>By the way, one can install the platform on various mobile devices such as tablets, smartphones and smartwatches. The additional features such as news, videos, comments and more are very interesting. This allows investors to be positively attuned in their daily trading routine.</p>
<p>The Agena Trader platform is the most advanced one. It looks very professional and has a wide range of features. It is also very easy to use. Standard features are available in the affordable Basic Edition. The Andromeda Edition, on the other hand, offers fully automated solutions. Unfortunately, this software was developed for Windows only. Investors should make use of the so-called Notifier app. This allows them to monitor current news about market events. The Agena platform offers investors a wide range of functions for in-depth analysis of market events. There are available over 100 indicators, seven chart types as well as backtesting.</p>
<p>Opening an account &#8211; How to open a trading account</p>
<p>Opening a live account on Metatrader 4 or any other platform is quite simple. The important thing is to complete three steps, which are ideally completed within a short period of time. Thus, XTB offers a systematic process by which even beginners will have no problems to successfully complete their registration.</p>
<p>First, you have to go to the website of XTB. Thus, XTB offers a separate section on the homepage, where you have to decide on an account type. You can choose between a Basic, a Standard and a Pro account. The only differences are in the spreads.</p>
<p>The Basic account has a limited handle. One should also know at this point that the Forex broker provides this account for beginners. There is a table in the XTB test where you can see the limit. During the trading hours, one can guarantee from a stop loss. In this way, you cannot lose more than your invested money.</p>
<p>The standard account is a market maker account. It allows for unlimited trading. This account is suitable for advanced traders who have extensive market knowledge. However, variable spreads starting from 0.9 pips are possible. This option must be activated in advance in the settings.</p>
<p>XTB does not act as a market maker only with the Professional Account (Pro Account). The orders are forwarded here directly to the corresponding markets. However, this is associated with a commission. The fee will be worthwhile but only at the Forex broker if you have a large trading volume. Thus, this account is also suitable only for experienced traders. By the way, low spreads starting from 0.1 pips are also available with this account.</p>
<p>After registration, one has to confirm his identity. Normally, this process is done through a Postident procedure. Alternatively, one can carry out the identity verification at one&#8217;s house bank. If the verification is successful, the account will be activated.</p>
<p>Payment options</p>
<p>For the deposit the customer can use the following means:</p>
<p>Credit card<br />
PayPal<br />
KLARNA SOFORT<br />
bank transfer.</p>
<p>Very pleasant is the fact that it is possible to deposit with PayPal and Klarna Sofort. This can speed up the payment process. The use of PayPal and Klarna Sofort is also much easier than making a classic bank transfer. Not for nothing is XTB best CFD broker. This is the conclusion reached in a detailed XTB test.</p>
<p>If you want to use the bank transfer, you have to make the deposit to a reference account of the XTB broker. In doing so, one must specify the name of the account holder and the contract number.</p>
<p>Very pleasant is the news that one does not have to pay fees for any deposit method. At the same time, there is no minimum deposit amount. Lastly, one must make sure to provide correct information in the registration for a new account. The personal information or name must be identical to the name of the bank account. This is very important, because many beginners do not take the specification of their personal data so seriously. Problems arise for these people at the latest during the first withdrawal.</p>
<p>Customer service &#8211; professional and reliable</p>
<p>XTB can be reached around the clock within the working week. You can reach the friendly and competent staff by phone, live chat and email. The e-mail address can be found on the homepage of XTB. Support in German is available to the investor. This in particular stands out with the XTB broker. Experience shows that most traders take advantage of the telephone support at a broker. There is nothing wrong with that. However, it can help if you think about why you want to contact support in advance. Most of the time, the concerns are very simple, which makes contacting the live chat sufficient.</p>
<p>By the way, the XTB broker has set up a Training Academy. There are several training areas where you can learn more about the trading platform, mobile trading, social trading, maximum leverage, currencies like US dollars and other trading topics in German for free. The eLearning offer is very convincing. Here there are special course units, where you can get theoretical and practical knowledge. With the help of quizzes you can deepen your knowledge.</p>
<p>Customers should also take a look at the knowledge encyclopedia. Customers can learn more about the most important trading terms here. The live webinars round off the training program harmoniously. They take place at regular intervals for customers.</p>
<p>Mobile Trading</p>
<p>Mobile trading is just as important. More and more customers are trading on the move. More precisely, this means while waiting for public transport, at work, at home on the sofa or on vacation. The development of the mobile internet has made it much easier for many people to use apps on the go. Fortunately, the provider XTB is also one of the brokers that provide customers with a mobile app.</p>
<p>A look at XTB&#8217;s website showed that there is currently no mobile app. Customers therefore have to manage their account with XTB via a web app. But what exactly does that mean?</p>
<p>A web app represents a website that is optimized for the use of mobile devices. More specifically, it means that when trading XTB you have to log into the XTB website. This is done on the go, of course. In most cases, you only have to do this login once. Then it is enough if you save the customer account as a bookmark.</p>
<p>After that, you can log in again and again automatically. A web app is a website that has been optimized for mobile use. This is also called &#8220;Responsive Design&#8221;. The problem is that the XTB website cannot be optimized for all mobile devices. While most users feel that they can trade EUR USD currency pairs on the go without any problems. However, some criticisms have already arisen that the font in the web app cannot be read on all mobile devices. Therefore, many traders wish that XTB will launch a mobile app in the foreseeable future. After all, then it will be much easier to invest and trade 10,000 euros on the go.</p>
<p>Conclusion XTB</p>
<p>In conclusion XTB can only be said that it is an excellent and professional platform. With a choice of 3 different platforms and different account types, every trader can pick his suitable platform for Forex trading. It must also be said that XTB has an excellent customer service. Traders can choose how they want to reach the support for questions about Forex and other things. The service staff can be reached around the clock within the week. One wishes that the customer service is easily accessible on weekends as well. However, this is not tragic since the service within the week has a very good accessibility.</p>
<p>The experience of XTB shows that many traders are very satisfied with XTB. This also speaks for the very high professional level at XTB. When trading, beginners can use the demo account to learn their first steps. Investors can invest US dollars to buy other trading currencies or currency pairs. Customers can still participate in the extensive education program to learn more about CFD and social trading. An excellent selection of educational videos on important topics such as CFD, Forex, cryptocurrencies and commodities enhances the trading experience and turns a beginner into a happy customer. In fact, it can be argued that XTB&#8217;s trading platform is built in such a way that even beginners will have no problems learning their way around their desired trading platform quickly. With the large and unique selection of platforms, this is not a big surprise.</p>
<p>A German-speaking customer service further ensures that German traders can convey all their concerns to the service staff. Overall, the trading experience at XTB is excellent and most customers describe their experience at XTB as top-notch.</p>
<p>The only thing that some customers do not like is the fact that the demo account is only valid for one month. One wishes here that the beginners and customers can use the free demo account for an unlimited time to be able to test trading with CFD for an unlimited time without risks. Especially when trading with CFD, the customers should first train the trade. Otherwise happens very quickly what happens with many other comparable online brokers: Customers do not get enough experience in dealing with CFD and lose their money within the first month.</p>
<p>Despite this minor criticism, most customers are very satisfied with XTB. Thus, happy customers share their positive experiences in online trading forums. These positive reviews once again confirm the high professional level of the XTB broker.</p>
<p>The experiences speak for themselves. Beginners should definitely try XTB. It is not for nothing that many XTB prospects become loyal customers.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/review/xtb/">XTB Review</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">MrStocks.org</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/review/xtb/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Complete Acorns Review 2021</title>
		<link>/review/acorns/</link>
					<comments>/review/acorns/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Maximilian Weber]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 14:37:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://demos.pokatheme.com/pokatheme/?post_type=affiliates&#038;p=116</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Acorn is a computerized investment app that gathers together your trades. After doing so it consequently puts your cash into a portfolio that works best for you. In our Acorns review, you&#8217;ll find out what Acorns offers, how much does Acorns cost, features, pros, cons, and more. Since its underlying delivery, Acorns has proceeded to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/review/acorns/">Complete Acorns Review 2021</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">MrStocks.org</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="ql-align-justify">Acorn is a computerized investment app that gathers together your trades. After doing so it consequently puts your cash into a portfolio that works best for you. In our Acorns review, you&#8217;ll find out what Acorns offers, how much does Acorns cost, features, pros, cons, and more.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Since its underlying delivery, Acorns has proceeded to enhance, and its increased current standards for miniature contributing apps &#8211; and now banking too! A couple of the new component discharges make it sensible to consider Acorns once more. Would it be a good idea for you to make an Acorns account, or is it an exaggerated app? This Acorns review clarifies the good and the terrible.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Acorns is across-the-board monetary well-being contributing app that makes it simple to save and contribute. However, while micro-investing isn&#8217;t their primary driver, Acorns accomplishes something beyond investing your spare change. You can contribute for retirement, set up financial records, and set up family speculation to represent your youngsters, among numerous different administrations.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">While Acorns began as an app, it has a web-based desktop version that you can use to trade. Below you&#8217;ll find a complete Acorns review to help you decide if this is the best investing app for you.</p>
<h2 class="ql-align-justify"><strong>How Does Acorns Work?</strong></h2>
<p class="ql-align-justify">By providing your email address and connecting your Visa and financial records, Acorns peruses your ways of managing money on your Visa and gathers every trade together to the closest entire number. It pulls the distinction from your financial records and puts it in an Acorns account that you set up. Acorns works with a variety of asset classes and investing options. They offer recurring investments and some real-estate investments that set them apart from other apps that only offer moderately conservative investing.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Acorn is an incredible platform for any individual who’s yet to invest or needs some direction to start with, and you can make some money if you invest using this app.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">As an Acorn client, you&#8217;ll download the App and answer a couple of questions. The app will then suggest a product portfolio for you.  Acorn portfolios range from moderately conservative (plenty of bonds) to moderately aggressive (all stocks plus real estate) for those with risk tolerance. They offer corporate bonds, recurring investments, small cap, and Acorns linked accounts to make trading easy.</p>
<h3 class="ql-align-justify">Minimal Costs and Customizable Portfolios</h3>
<p class="ql-align-justify">When you pick your portfolio, (Acorns Lite, Acorns Personal, or Acorns Family, all with a different monthly management fee) you&#8217;ll connect your credit card to the Acorn platform. At the point when you make a transaction, Acorn will round up your trade to the nearest dollar.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">The round-up is like cash back that gets stored in a holding account. In case you burn through $8.65 out of $9.00, Acorn will save $.35 into your holding account. When the account has at least $5, the app will naturally put the returns into the market. They will make use of the investment chance to rebalance your portfolio.</p>
<h3 class="ql-align-justify">The Round-Up Multiplier</h3>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Another element that Acorn has come up with recently is the &#8220;round up multiplier.&#8221; You can twofold to 10X your gatherings. For instance, a $.45 spare change round up could turn into $.90 altogether on the off chance that you select a 2x multiplier. If you select a 10x multiplier it will become $4.50. The multiplier can be changed through the Acorns app, however not from the Acorns’ site, so be cautious with it.</p>
<h3 class="ql-align-justify">Acorns Spend</h3>
<p class="ql-align-justify">At long last, the Acorns app has another charge card stage called Acorns spend. The upside is that you can quickly deduct round-ups from your financial records (something that could require a few days from a credit or debit card).  Acorns offer limitless ATM repayment for your debit card, have no minimum balance, and don&#8217;t charge overdraft expenses.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">You can add your debit card right into the app and change the card 1 per month.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Be that as it may, you&#8217;ll pay the $3 monthly fee, to keep up the account.</p>
<h2 class="ql-align-justify"><strong>Acorns Features</strong></h2>
<h3 class="ql-align-justify"><strong>Learn</strong></h3>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Acorns includes a training segment that incorporates contributing fundamentals, FAQs, and a glossary.</p>
<h3 class="ql-align-justify"><strong>Round-Ups</strong></h3>
<p class="ql-align-justify">For each Visa trade, Acorns rounds up to the closest dollar and puts it into an Acorns account. Peruse more about how round-ups work here.</p>
<h3 class="ql-align-justify"><strong>Round-Up Multiplier</strong></h3>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Rather than simply gathering together to the following dollar, clients would now be able to increase the additional speculation by two, three, or 10.</p>
<h3 class="ql-align-justify"><strong>Found Money</strong></h3>
<p class="ql-align-justify">If you shop with Acorns&#8217;s found money-related brands — which presently incorporate Airbnb, Blue Cover, Macy&#8217;s, and Warby Parker, and others — the additional cash will be added to your Acorns account<strong>.</strong></p>
<h3 class="ql-align-justify"><strong>Acorns Early</strong></h3>
<p class="ql-align-justify">This is an initiative to encourage kids to start investing. It permits guardians, parents, and relatives to set up a custodial account for a kid. To offer help for guardians during the Coronavirus pandemic, Acorns is giving a free account for children brought into the world in 2020 to start investing early.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">This allows parents to start to save and invest on their child&#8217;s behalf and give them the option to start investing early. They won&#8217;t have access to the investing app, a credit card, or the ability to save and invest themselves until the age of maturity.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">This is a great way to get kids excited about saving money and Acorns investing. Investment accounts for kids are becoming extremely popular and Acorns got in on the ground floor.</p>
<h3 class="ql-align-justify"><strong>Acorns Later</strong></h3>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Acorns Later clients can put resources into an uncommonly planned individual retirement account (IRA). Acorns Later are part of the Individual, or Acorns Personal, and Family. These accounts let you take your personal finance into your own hands and make money work for you. Instead of placing your cash into a bank account you can earn interest on it.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">You can set up recurring deposits but you will have to pay management fees if you decide to withdraw money before retirement age.</p>
<h3 class="ql-align-justify"><strong>Money Acorns Gift vouchers</strong></h3>
<p class="ql-align-justify">$25 computerized money Acorns gift vouchers are presently accessible to take part in stores and on the web. This is an extraordinary choice for kicking a companion off with some much-needed assistance.</p>
<h3 class="ql-align-justify"><strong>Acorns Spend</strong></h3>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Acorns has financial accounts called Go through with a charge card that Acorns and Acorn’s Later investing functionality to each buy you make. Later, Acorns Spend allows you in a flash to do constant Round-Ups, just as programmed retirement investment funds and additional reserve funds through Found Money.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">You can likewise invest up to 10% of your daily purchases from nearby retailers that are not enlisted with Found Money.</p>
<h3 class="ql-align-justify"><strong>Acorns Family</strong></h3>
<p class="ql-align-justify">The fee for Acorns Family, 5 bucks per month, is well worth it. For $5 per month, you can get Acorns ahead of schedule for every one of your children, in addition to across the board contributing, retirement, and financial records, Brilliant Store, customized protection alternatives, and different apparatuses to set aside cash.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">For less than your weekly coffee, the $5 per month this plan could set up your kids to invest wisely and be savvy with credit or debit cards. The bottom line is it&#8217;s a great way, regardless of management fees, to get your children off on the right track and invest in their future.</p>
<h2 class="ql-align-justify">Step by Step Instructions to Create an Acorns Account</h2>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Pursuing an Acorns investment account is simple. It begins with joining on the web or downloading the application free of charge from iTunes, Amazon, or Google Play. The application is accessible for iPhone or Android cell phones.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">The three-step process begins with entering a PIN access code, which you will when signing into the app later on. Making an Acorns account is presently accessible only to U.S. residents.</p>
<h3 class="ql-align-justify"><strong>Pick a Round-Ups Account</strong></h3>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Your principle Round-Up Account is the one you will choose; pick which trades you need to gather together and contribute the spare change from. Choose your bank and sign in.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Then, click the account you&#8217;d prefer to use in your round-ups. You can use more than one account on the off chance that you&#8217;d like. Your sales will be rounded to the nearest dollar and deposited into the account they have on file.</p>
<h3 class="ql-align-justify"><strong>Connect Your Checking Account</strong></h3>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Your checking account is unique about your Round-Up Account (this was confounding to me from the outset, as well) and is the record from which subsidies will be moved into your Acorns account. Interface a current checking account from the rundown and sign in using your online accreditation, or info you’re directing and account numbers physically from an alternate bank.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">It requires a few minutes for your Chase Bank account to adjust using your online ID and secret word. Also, don&#8217;t stress over interfacing your banking information, since Acorns encodes and protects all your data with top-notch bank-level security.</p>
<h3 class="ql-align-justify"><strong>Create an Investment Account</strong></h3>
<p class="ql-align-justify">You&#8217;ll be required to type in your first and last names, telephone number, and birth date and to pick your preferred security question/answer. At that point, it&#8217;s ideal to fill in your location and check-in case you&#8217;re a U.S. resident or not.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Then, you&#8217;ll be asked to respond to three simple questions that sound close to the following:</p>
<ul>
<li class="ql-align-justify">It is safe to say that you are or have you been a subsidiary with a broker-dealer?</li>
<li class="ql-align-justify">Has the IRS told you of being dependent upon backup withholding?</li>
<li class="ql-align-justify">Is it true that you are a 10% investor of a publicly-traded company?</li>
</ul>
<p class="ql-align-justify">In case none of these questions concern you, leave them unchecked. These are standard inquiries needed by the SEC when you open a brokerage account.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">The following screen will ask you to fill in your total assets, employment info, yearly pay, and the purpose of your purpose for investing. The responses to these inquiries will assist Acorns to generate a suitable portfolio for you. This portfolio is made by its group of specialists, including a Nobel Prize-winning financial expert.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">You can pick from any of the following five reasons for investing:</p>
<ul>
<li class="ql-align-justify">Long-term investment</li>
<li class="ql-align-justify">Short-term investment</li>
<li class="ql-align-justify">Major purchase</li>
<li class="ql-align-justify">Children</li>
<li class="ql-align-justify">General</li>
</ul>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Lastly, you’ll have to fill in your Social Security number. According to the app, this number is used for ID verification, fraud prevention, and tax reporting. Once you check all the relevant signup boxes in green, proceed and click the “Get Started!” button.</p>
<h2 class="ql-align-justify"><strong>What Does Acorns Charge?</strong></h2>
<p class="ql-align-justify">There are no account or deposit minimums to observe, no commission charges, and no penalties when you decide to withdraw your funds. For its administrations, Acorns charges:</p>
<ul>
<li class="ql-align-justify">A level charge of $1 each month for records of under $5,000</li>
<li class="ql-align-justify">0.25% charge yearly for accounts bigger than $5,000.</li>
</ul>
<p class="ql-align-justify">For $3 per month, you can get a personal account which will include an investing account, retirement account, and checking account. What&#8217;s more, for $5, you can get an Acorns Family account, which incorporates custodial records for your children, alongside the highlights in the Personal account level.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Any time you use Acorns, in case you&#8217;re investing small sums to a great extent, you risk paying some fees. The $1-per-month rate is high when compared to other investment alternatives.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Suppose you make just two purchases with your Acorns-connected account each day with a Round-up of 20 cents for every time. That is just about $12 contributed each month. For this situation, $1 addresses 8.33% in expenses — essentially higher than Robo counselors, for example, Advancement, which charges 0.25% yearly.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Obviously, in case you&#8217;re a regular card client who makes a lot more buys each day, Acorns begins to bode well. Besides, there are a few different ways to amplify your experience and lift your investment funds.</p>
<h2 class="ql-align-justify"><strong>Where Acorn Shines, Found Money, Educational Content, and More</strong></h2>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Automated approach: We&#8217;re behind any instrument that energizes thoughtless, programmed saving. If you don&#8217;t need to consider saving, you&#8217;re bound to do it.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Acorns clear trade change from each purchase using a connected account into a venture portfolio. You can link as many accounts or cards as you need, however, all roundups are taken from the same connected checking account.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">With each purchase, the broker rounds up to the closest $1 and gives you the choice to move that change into a speculation portfolio. You can do that automatically so that every purchase is a roundup and your change transferred, or physically, by going through your recent purchases on the Acorns&#8217; app and choosing which roundups to transfer.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Though these roundups are the bread and butter of this platform, you can likewise invest lump sums physically or set up repeating deposits on a day by day, week after week, or month-to-month basis. Such lump-sum transfers can be as little as $5.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">The Acorns Spend account is like a web-based debit card. Acorns Spend gives real-time roundups to your venture account, mobile check deposits, and free ATMs (or repaid ATM charges). The platform requires no minimum balance and is accessible on the Family and Personal plans only.</p>
<h3 class="ql-align-justify">Found Money</h3>
<p class="ql-align-justify">The single thing better than building a venture portfolio out of spare change is building an investment portfolio out of another person&#8217;s cash. This is what Acorns&#8217; Found Money program allows you to do. It&#8217;s money-back for your investment account.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Acorns have cooperated with more than 350 companies — including Walmart Airbnb, Warby Parker, Nike, and Sephora — to give you money back when you utilize a connected installment strategy at one of the accomplices. As a rule, you get the money back automatically without having to do anything else.</p>
<h3 class="ql-align-justify">Educational content</h3>
<p class="ql-align-justify">We found the site appropriate to new investors, as it explains key terms and uses clear language. Also, Acorns publishes Grow Magazine, a web-based persona finance webpage intended for millennials with guidance about credit card debt, side gigs, student loans, and other financial issues. Besides, Grow Content is integrated into the platform&#8217;s app.</p>
<h3 class="ql-align-justify">Investing for kids</h3>
<p class="ql-align-justify">The Family level incorporates Acorns Early, which makes it simple to make UTMA/UGMA accounts for your children. These custodial accounts permit guardians to invest for a minor kid and use the cash for costs that advantage the kid. When the kid matures they acquire ownership of the account and can use the cash for any purpose.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Custodial accounts mustn&#8217;t be similar to 529 savings accounts. The 529 accounts are less adaptable, as they&#8217;re intended for education expenses. However, these accounts offer more tax advantages and are thought to be a superior method to save for a college education.</p>
<h2 class="ql-align-justify"><strong>Where Acorns Falls Short</strong></h2>
<h3 class="ql-align-justify"><strong>Management fee</strong></h3>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Regardless of whether Acorns&#8217; charges are a plus or a minus depends upon your account balance; $3 per month to add Acorns Later (which is an IRA account) and Acorns Spend (which is the debit card and checking/chequing account offering); and $5 per month for those advantages in addition to Acorns Early, investment for your kids.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Flat fees like this are uncommon among Robo-advisors, which usually charge a fraction of assets under management each year.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">A $1, $3, or $5 a month cost sounds modest, yet it can be high for investors who have small balances. If you make only such roundup contributions, you could drift in that zone for a long time.</p>
<h3 class="ql-align-justify"><strong>Smallish portfolio</strong></h3>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Similar to other Robo-advisors, Acorns takes charge of the investing reins from you &#8211; the investor. The app &#8220;thinks&#8221; about your information — including age, objectives, income, and time horizon — and afterward suggests one of five portfolios that range from the conservative to the aggressive.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">You can agree on that proposal or pick an alternate portfolio that faces more or less risk.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">The actual portfolios, however, are more modest than the normal Robo-advisor portfolio, comprised of low-cost Vanguard and iShares exchange-traded funds that cover only five to seven asset categories, contingent upon the portfolio: land, enormous cap stocks, emerging markets, and government and corporate and government bonds</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">That is sufficient asset classes for an enhanced portfolio. However, if it feels excessively prohibitive, you may like to construct your portfolio without the assistance of a service like Acorns</p>
<h2 class="ql-align-justify"><strong>Is Acorns Safe: Can You Trust Them With Your Checking Account?</strong></h2>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Entrusting your hard-earned money to anyone might not be that easy. This is more so if the target of your trust is an online app that you are not sure about. It&#8217;s no wonder that like many other investors and traders you might be wondering whether Acorns is a legitimate app. If so, don&#8217;t scratch your head again. We&#8217;ve researched for you.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Indeed, Acorns is a genuine, controlled organization. Its dealer and guardianship services are controlled by the Protections and Trade Commission and it&#8217;s additionally an individual from the <strong>Financial Industry Regulatory Authority</strong> (FINRA), an automatic association. It&#8217;s additionally an individual from the <strong>Securities Investor Protection Corporation</strong> (SIPC).</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Acorns are not exclusively committed to submitting data to government controllers, however, it is supposed to maintain the guidelines of FINRA and SIPC.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Remember that there are risks with speculation. The financial trade can be whimsical and you can lose money.</p>
<h2 class="ql-align-justify"><strong>Pros</strong></h2>
<ul>
<li class="ql-align-justify">Effortless Approach to Save—Since the sums removed from your record are little, you will not notice them missing from your financial records.</li>
<li class="ql-align-justify">Begin saving with no cash— Acorns doesn&#8217;t need a base store to begin utilizing the assistance.</li>
<li class="ql-align-justify">Shrouds the Intricacies of investing— you don&#8217;t have to comprehend the Current Portfolio Hypothesis to utilize Acorns.</li>
<li class="ql-align-justify">Simple to set up the family account— Acorns Early makes it simple to set up a custodial contributing record for your kids and begin putting resources into their future.</li>
</ul>
<h2 class="ql-align-justify"><strong>Cons</strong></h2>
<ul>
<li class="ql-align-justify">You Can Lose Your Money- It&#8217;s conceivable to lose cash with Acorns, although the suggested speculations are moderate.</li>
<li class="ql-align-justify">It’s only ideal for &#8220;Boosting&#8221; Your Investment funds—Acorns’ investment funds sums aren&#8217;t fit to save the 5% to 20% every year you need to put toward retirement or bigger objectives.</li>
</ul>
<h2 class="ql-align-justify"><strong>Final Thoughts</strong></h2>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Acorns have modernized the outdated act of saving spare change, combining the Robo-advisor model with modern automated savings too. Acorns deliver by rounding up your purchases on linked debit or credit cards and then clearing the change into a computer-managed portfolio. That approach is unquestionably a helpful device to save more. Acorns provide three levels of participation:</p>
<ul>
<li class="ql-align-justify"><strong>Lite:</strong> $1 per month. Incorporates a taxable investment account.</li>
<li class="ql-align-justify"><strong>Personal</strong>: $3 per month. Adds on an individual retirement account and a financial account.</li>
<li class="ql-align-justify"><strong>Family:</strong> $5 every month. This includes everything in the lower-level tiers, in addition to Acorns Early, which allows you to open investment accounts for your kids.</li>
</ul>
<p class="ql-align-justify">If you need to capitalize on your spare change and get a periodic retailer payoff, there&#8217;s no better place to achieve that objective — particularly since Acorns offers IRA accounts.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">The programmed roundups at Acorns make saving and investing simple, and like many other investors, you might be surprised at how fast your pennies multiply.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/review/acorns/">Complete Acorns Review 2021</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">MrStocks.org</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/review/acorns/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
