<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Online Broker News</title>
	<atom:link href="/category/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description>Best Online Brokers for Free Stock Trading</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 14:52:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Cash Cloud Mining: Profits and Risks</title>
		<link>/bitcoin-cash-cloud-mining-profits-and-risks/</link>
					<comments>/bitcoin-cash-cloud-mining-profits-and-risks/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Maximilian Weber]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 17:56:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=507</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What is Bitcoin Cash? Bitcoin Cash was created by bitcoin miners and developers who were equally concerned with the cryptocurrency&#8217;s future and scalability. These people, though, expressed concerns over the use of separated witness technology. They found that SegWit2x did not adequately resolve the fundamental issue of scalability, nor did it adhere to the roadmap [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/bitcoin-cash-cloud-mining-profits-and-risks/">Bitcoin Cash Cloud Mining: Profits and Risks</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">MrStocks.org</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h3>What is Bitcoin Cash?</h3>
<p>Bitcoin Cash was created by bitcoin miners and developers who were equally concerned with the cryptocurrency&#8217;s future and scalability. These people, though, expressed concerns over the use of separated witness technology. They found that SegWit2x did not adequately resolve the fundamental issue of scalability, nor did it adhere to the roadmap outlined by Satoshi Nakamoto, the unknown group who proposed the blockchain technology that underpins cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>As you go along with this article you are to obtain an introductory overview of the cloud mining mechanism of bitcoin cash (BCH).</p>
<h3>What is Cloud Mining?</h3>
<p>Cloud mining is a technique for mining cryptocurrencies such as bitcoin utilizing borrowed cloud processing space rather than installing and running the hardware and associated applications directly.</p>
<p>Cloud mining companies allow individuals to create an account and engage remotely in the process of cryptocurrency mining for a low monthly fee, making mining available to a larger number of citizens worldwide.</p>
<p>Due to the fact that this method of mining is cloud-based, it eliminates problems such as infrastructure servicing and direct energy costs.</p>
<p>Cloud miners join a mining pool, which allows users to buy a certain amount of &#8220;hash power.&#8221; Each participant is entitled to a pro-rata share of income based on the volume of hashing power leased.</p>
<h3>How Will You Earn Mining?</h3>
<p>As is the case for the majority of other blockchain-based cryptocurrency ventures, cloud miners are expected to validate and confirm the transactions. Anyone can become a Bitcoin Cash miner by purchasing the necessary hardware and installing the necessary software. But is everyone capable of investing such a significant amount? Here&#8217;s where cloud mining comes in.</p>
<p>As for Bitcoin, the Bitcoin Cash mining group confirms a block of transactions every ten minutes. Similarly, Prior to confirming a block, every Bitcoin Cash miner community must attempt to solve a cryptographic puzzle. This problem is so complex to crack that no human being might do so; instead, it takes a great deal of computing power.</p>
<p>In addition to the first BTC/USD payout, the community who can solve the block first would get all the Bitcoin transaction fees that Bitcoin Cash users have been charged as they transfer their funds to the SegWit addresses. In general, the owner with the most mining power wins the jackpot.</p>
<p>An efficient and costly mining rig will always have a better probability of receiving the money than a simple CPU, in the world of crypto cloud mining, in the world of crypto mining.</p>
<h3>Is Bitcoin Cash Mining Profitable?</h3>
<p>Just like any other business on earth, cloud mining has both pros and cons. Here, both the pros and cons will be discussed for your decision-making consideration reg.</p>
<h4>Pros</h4>
<ol>
<li>This is a really straightforward and fast service to use. Technical knowledge of crypto mining is not mandatory for running the mining operations if you are using a cloud solution.</li>
<li>Very less expensive as you do not need to pour money after powerful and modern hardware equipment.</li>
<li>As no device is to be placed at home, you will not have to suffer from irritative noise and excessive heat.</li>
<li>No maintenance or operating cost. Mining computers use an enormous amount of energy. Therefore, it&#8217;s a big save!</li>
<li>No troubleshooting hassle as you&#8217;re mining virtually.</li>
</ol>
<h4>Cons</h4>
<ol>
<li>Fewer investment results in lower-income. As you are not to set up the system and you are using a pre-ready service, the income is not much high.</li>
<li>For newer ones, determining the hash rate at the mining pool often gets confusing.</li>
<li>Cloud mining is full of scams. The cloud provider may close the business or go away with your money.</li>
<li>If you&#8217;re residing somewhere with a poor network connection, it may seem troublesome connecting to your cloud.</li>
</ol>
<h3>Cloud Mining Cost</h3>
<p>When it comes to the disadvantages of paid cloud mining, the most noticeable will obviously be the cost. Paid cloud mining may become very costly. Depending on the sum of money invested in cloud mining, even the entry plans can seem prohibitively costly.</p>
<p>Paid cloud mining entry plans usually cost between $200 and $300. Considering the typical premium fluctuations associated with subsequent plan levels, this is a reasonable starting price. For an entry package, you get the fastest hash rate possible, although the duration of the plan can differ. These entry-level cloud mining plans are mostly intended for individuals who have no prior background of cloud mining and are interested in getting a feel for it.</p>
<p>Others who are committed and certain that cloud mining is the future of their financial profits typically spend significantly more from the start. This is not a concern in and of itself, but those buyers should be cautious and conduct due diligence!</p>
<p>There are several corporations out there with malicious intent that could allow lower-level contracts to move. This will occur mainly because they hoped the person would ultimately upgrade to a more expensive deal. They can, moreover, seize the chance to defraud larger investors.</p>
<p>So, above I have illustrated both the picture for you. Now it&#8217;s your call to make the decision. Any of the paths you choose, it takes loads of patience to be a successful miner.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/bitcoin-cash-cloud-mining-profits-and-risks/">Bitcoin Cash Cloud Mining: Profits and Risks</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">MrStocks.org</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/bitcoin-cash-cloud-mining-profits-and-risks/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>CCG mining review</title>
		<link>/ccg-mining-review/</link>
					<comments>/ccg-mining-review/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Maximilian Weber]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 17:53:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=504</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If you&#8217;re a regular in cloud mining, you&#8217;ve probably come across the branding of this cryptocurrency company, &#8220;CCG Mining,&#8221; several times. CCG Mining was established in 2016 with the primary aim of establishing Europe&#8217;s highest computational hashing capacity. With the tagline &#8216;We make things simple for you,&#8217; they aim to meet the needs of over [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ccg-mining-review/">CCG mining review</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">MrStocks.org</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If you&#8217;re a regular in cloud mining, you&#8217;ve probably come across the branding of this cryptocurrency company, &#8220;CCG Mining,&#8221; several times.</p>
<p>CCG Mining was established in 2016 with the primary aim of establishing Europe&#8217;s highest computational hashing capacity.</p>
<p>With the tagline &#8216;We make things simple for you,&#8217; they aim to meet the needs of over 850 company customers.</p>
<h2>Post Summary</h2>
<p>As you&#8217;re going to read this CCG mining review, you can keep in mind the following sub-oriented headings:</p>
<ul>
<li>Who is CCG Mining?</li>
<li>How to initiate cloud mining contracts on CCG Mining?</li>
<li>CCG Mining Products and Services</li>
<li>Advantages and Disadvantages of Using CCG Mining</li>
<li>CCG Mining: Legit or Scam?</li>
<li>Conclusion</li>
</ul>
<h2>Who is CCG Mining?</h2>
<p>CCG Mining is a crypto mining firm that was established in 2016 at the height of the digital currency market.</p>
<p>It has all the characteristics of a multinational business that has focused on using blockchain technologies to provide holistic solutions.</p>
<p>This set has 5 branches located in Europe: in Belgium, Poland Great Britain, Russia, and Austria, all in different locations, as well as a research institute in Latvia.</p>
<p>Michal Kwiecinski is the CEO/Chairman and President of the company, with over 45,000 private clients, 850 industry clients, and nearly 1,000 corporate ones.</p>
<p>Its aim is to serve and do whatever it takes to make the consumer the happiest with total fulfillment in mind.</p>
<p>Their ultimate goal is to create the most powerful European computing resource. NVIDIA, AMD, Intel, ATI, BITMAIN, and Canaan hardware are used by the firm. They attempt to make it simple for you, and they believe that if they can do so, their users will find it easier to use.</p>
<p>With a highly trained and qualified crew, a proficient squad at dealing with the ever-changing crypto industry, CCG Mining navigates the terrain.</p>
<p>To satisfy this, they are employing the latest operating practices and technology consumers&#8217; preferences, they have to get in on the ground and learn more about their daily habits.</p>
<p>All of the CCG datacenters are located in Central Europe.</p>
<p>The use of many data centers to mine different cryptocurrencies is a common practice in the cloud mining industry.</p>
<p>This cloud mining facility is particularly energy-efficient due to the amount of computing power being used to fuel the usage of which is used, allowing it to cut energy costs.</p>
<p>Since the data centers are optimally situated and have a steady temperature, these facilities support cloud mining facilities well.</p>
<h2>CCG Mining Products and Services</h2>
<p>CCG Mining developed a revolutionary tool for business-to-business (B2B) and business-to-consumer (B2C) customers.</p>
<p>This is to make things as simple as possible for everyone to utilize Blockchain technologies to fulfill their unique needs.</p>
<p>For your better understanding, you have divided this part into 3 sub-parts. They goes:</p>
<ol>
<li>Cloud Mining Contracts</li>
<li>Mining rig</li>
<li>Affiliate Program</li>
</ol>
<p>Each of the sub-part shall be vividly described later.</p>
<p>The service utilizes three primary algorithms for computing the amount of extracted blockchain technology-based currency: SHA-256, ETHASH, and EQUIHASH.</p>
<p>CCG Mining offers the following cryptocurrencies services:</p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin (BTC)</li>
<li>Bitcoin Cash (BCH)</li>
<li>Ethereum (ETH)</li>
<li>Dash</li>
<li>Litecoin (LTC)</li>
<li>Monero</li>
<li>Zcash</li>
</ul>
<p>CCG Mining has diverse policies according to consumer demand including Custom, 1-year contract, and 2-year contract plans for these cryptocurrencies with BTC and BCH having other Unlimited contract plans.</p>
<h5>CCG Mining 1 Year Cloud Mining Contracts Plans for BTC, ETH, BCH, and ZCASH</h5>
<h4>Below are the 1-year contract custom plans for cloud mining :</h4>
<ul>
<li>BTC (Bitcoin): Beginning at USD 99.00 for TH/s</li>
<li>ETH (Ethereum): Beginning at USD 13.50 for TH/s</li>
<li>ZCash: Beginning at USD 1.38 for TH/s</li>
<li>BCH (Bitcoin Cash): Beginning at USD 139.00 for TH/s</li>
</ul>
<h4>Below are the 2-year contract custom plans for cloud mining :</h4>
<ul>
<li>LTC: Beginning at USD 11.40 for TH/s</li>
<li>Monero: Beginning at USD 0.75 for TH/s</li>
<li>ZCash: Beginning at USD 1.69 for TH/s</li>
</ul>
<h4>Below are the unlimited year contract custom plans for cloud mining :</h4>
<ul>
<li>BTC (Bitcoin) : Beginning at $119.00 for TH/s</li>
<li>BCH (Bitcoin Cash): Beginning at $236.00 for TH/s</li>
</ul>
<h2></h2>
<h2>How to initiate cloud mining contracts on CCG Mining?</h2>
<p>Follow the step-by-step instruction for placing a 1-year contract on CCG Mining. Almost the same goes for any other cloud mining contracts, you just need to select the correct cloud mining contracts package.</p>
<h4>Choosing Your Plan</h4>
<ol>
<li>Go to the CCG website</li>
<li>Click on your preferred plan (here, suppose, 1-year cloud mining contract for BTC (bitcoin).</li>
<li>Hit the Order Now and it will redirect you to another page.</li>
<li>Here you shall review your cloud mining order.</li>
</ol>
<h4>Review &amp; Checkout</h4>
<ol>
<li>Reviewing an order means formally confirming that you actually want to do business with CCG Mining and spend money on the mining contract you have selected. So, be careful.</li>
<li>Confirm whether it is the price you are going to spend.</li>
<li>Do not forget to remove all the other orders from your cart.</li>
<li>Click on &#8220;Check Out&#8221; and it will redirect you to a page for registration and choosing the payment method.</li>
</ol>
<h4>Payment</h4>
<p>CCG Mining supports:</p>
<ol>
<li>Payeer</li>
<li>Bitcoin</li>
<li>Some other digital currencies</li>
</ol>
<p>If you&#8217;re already a registered consumer, just input your credential and make the payment.</p>
<p>The contract will be activated within 24 to 48 hours following the payment.</p>
<h2>Mining Rigs</h2>
<p>Mining Rigs are designed for individuals that possess the technical skills required to self-configure and operate mining rigs and want to step into the world of Blockchain technology.</p>
<p>Mining Rigs are specialized computer devices that are used to mine Bitcoins. Rigs may be dedicated miners (purchased, designed, and run exclusively for mining) or they can be used for other purposes such as gaming and partially for mining.</p>
<p>CCG Mining Rigs are often suggested for data center owners and others with the technological expertise needed to calculate Blockchain Algorithms.</p>
<p>They have 3 options available for CCG Mining rigs:</p>
<ol>
<li>Basic</li>
<li>Advanced</li>
<li>Fury</li>
</ol>
<p>Every item has its own price and specs, which can be obtained by clicking on the ‘Order Now&#8217; button.</p>
<p>When you place an order, you can go through the same procedure as a 1-year contract by checking the order and signing before making payment using your chosen payment method.</p>
<p>This way, you own a mining rig that you have complete power over and can customize to meet your specific needs.</p>
<h2>Affiliate Program</h2>
<p>Unlike a traditional mining company, where the affiliate incentive is proportional to your rank, CCG Mining provides an Affiliate Program in which you can earn 6% of any cloud mining contract bought on its website anytime anyone uses your referral connection.</p>
<p>To enroll in the Affiliate Program, you must first register on their website.</p>
<p>Affiliate Program payments support BTC (Bitcoin) or T/T. (Telegraphic Transfer).</p>
<h2>Pros and Cons</h2>
<p>Following careful analysis of the findings, here are the benefits and drawbacks of investing in CCG cloud mining plans:</p>
<h4>Pros</h4>
<ul>
<li>Plans can be purchased using both fiat money and crypto.</li>
<li>When the economy is on a roll, a reinvestment service is open for you.</li>
<li>Mining rigs are quite strong</li>
<li>Excellent reward scheme</li>
<li>Excellent support structure</li>
<li>SSL Protection and DDOS Defense</li>
</ul>
<h4>Cons</h4>
<ul>
<li>Hash electricity rates are very high.</li>
<li>Payouts are made weekly rather than regular. Due to high upfront expenses and operating fees</li>
<li>1-year contract is unprofitable.</li>
</ul>
<h2>FAQ</h2>
<h4>Is CCG Mining legit?</h4>
<p>Is CCG a reputable business to invest in? In terms of protection and payout consistency, the answer is yes. However, based on our ROI research, the firm has a lot of work ahead of it. As compared to other cloud mining sites, the yields are uncompetitive. Hash fuel prices must be reduced, as must original plan costs.</p>
<h4>Is GPU mining still profitable?</h4>
<p>Maybe for a brief period during a bull market, such schemes will become lucrative, but my sense is that the crowd will swarm in again and hash rates will spike, eroding any profit. For bitcoin, the cat is now out of the bag.</p>
<h2>Conclusion</h2>
<p>We have come to an end of this CCG mining review. We tried to illustrate the whole picture of CCG Mining in front of you. Please share this post, comment with your feedback, and follow us on social media.</p>
<p>Happy Mining!!!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ccg-mining-review/">CCG mining review</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">MrStocks.org</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/ccg-mining-review/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Next cryptocurrency to explode in 2024 February</title>
		<link>/next-cryptocurrency-to-explode/</link>
					<comments>/next-cryptocurrency-to-explode/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Maximilian Weber]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 17:40:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=501</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Which crypto is going to explode in ? In 2021, are you planning to purchase or trade in cryptocurrencies? With over 7,000 digital assets accessible, determining the right cryptocurrencies to invest in for 2021 is not a simple task. Not to worry, Trading Education has compiled a selection of the strongest cryptocurrencies to invest in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/next-cryptocurrency-to-explode/">Next cryptocurrency to explode in 2024 February</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">MrStocks.org</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1>Which crypto is going to explode in 2024 February?</h1>
<p>In 2021, are you planning to purchase or trade in cryptocurrencies? With over 7,000 digital assets accessible, determining the right cryptocurrencies to invest in for 2021 is not a simple task. Not to worry, Trading Education has compiled a selection of the strongest cryptocurrencies to invest in in 2021!</p>
<p>According to a number of analysts, Bitcoin <sub>BTC</sub>, Ethereum <sub>eth</sub>, Cardano, and Litecoin <sub>LTC</sub> are the best cryptocurrencies to watch in 2021.</p>
<p>If you&#8217;re considering investing in the cryptocurrency industry this year, we have some positive news for you! Most cryptocurrency enthusiasts believe that 2021 would be the first year to invest in cryptocurrencies. But you must be wondering which is the next cryptocurrency to explode in 2021, right? Keep scrolling.</p>
<p>When choosing which cryptocurrency to invest in, the decision may be somewhat daunting given the market&#8217;s thousands of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s challenging and time-consuming to analyze and separate the worthwhile projects from the &#8220;fruitless&#8221; ones.</p>
<p>This is why we are here to assist you. The following is a list of the top ten cryptocurrencies that are predicted to boom in value in 2021 and continue to grow in importance in the years ahead.</p>
<p>At the end of the day, there is no one cryptocurrency that we would call the best of the best. There are just so many options, and the list continues to expand.</p>
<p>Numerous cryptocurrencies provide very enticing investment options, based on the investment objectives and criteria.</p>
<p>Another factor to remember is the degree of expertise.</p>
<p>For example, certain cryptocurrencies might be ideal for beginners, whereas others may be more suitable for experienced crypto traders.</p>
<p>Additionally, you must bear in mind that simply purchasing the best cryptocurrencies is insufficient to be a good crypto trader.</p>
<p>Consider these top cryptocurrencies to invest in this year to kick-start your 2021.</p>
<h2>Top 10 Cryptocurrencies to Explode in 2024 February:</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>Bitcoin</strong></li>
<li><strong> Litecoin </strong><sub><strong>LTC</strong></sub></li>
<li><strong> Ethereum </strong><sub><strong>ETH</strong></sub></li>
<li><strong> Basic Attention Token</strong></li>
<li><strong> Cardano </strong><sub><strong>ADA</strong></sub></li>
<li><strong> Bitcoin Cash </strong><sub><strong>BCH</strong></sub></li>
<li><strong> Binance Coin</strong></li>
<li><strong> TRON </strong><sub><strong>TRX</strong></sub></li>
<li><strong> EOS</strong></li>
<li><strong> Ripple </strong><sub><strong>XRP</strong></sub></li>
</ul>
<h2>The next cryptocurrency to explode in 2024 February: Top 10 coins</h2>
<p>This list is constantly updated when new cryptocurrencies are introduced. Not all cryptocurrencies can last the test of time, but there will undoubtedly be those that you will recognize in 2021.</p>
<h2></h2>
<h2>Bitcoin <sub>BTC</sub></h2>
<h3><em>Projection: USD 100,000 by the end of 2024 February</em></h3>
<p>When discussing the top ten cryptocurrencies to invest in now, cryptocurrencies in general, or simply smart crypto investments, all conversations must begin with Bitcoin.</p>
<p>That is because Bitcoin is the most widely adopted cryptocurrency to date and is often dubbed &#8220;The King of Cryptocurrencies.&#8221;</p>
<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s primary aim is to evolve into a national, peer-to-peer digital currency that is fully decentralized and unregulated. About any other cryptocurrency attempted to duplicate this concept.</p>
<p>Additionally, Bitcoin was the first blockchain, and many still say it would be the only one remaining throughout the end.</p>
<p>Apart from that, you can hold Bitcoin on your investing radar since it has the highest liquidity in the cryptocurrency room, making it the best cryptocurrency to purchase if you are a novice.</p>
<p>Finally, you would have no difficulty purchasing or selling Bitcoin. Individuals are constantly purchasing and selling Bitcoin.</p>
<p>There will still be someone around to take the order. Not just that, but considering its instability, Bitcoin is one of the most secure cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s power, market, and widespread acceptance are all projected to grow in the coming years (perhaps more so than any of its rivals).</p>
<p>As demand grows, the price of Bitcoin is projected to rise significantly, as there will never be more than 21 million coins.</p>
<p>Tesla has spent $1.5 billion in Bitcoin and could begin taking it as payment in the future. As soon as the news broke, the price of Bitcoin increased by about 14% to more than $44,000 a coin.</p>
<p>However, it did not end there! Bitcoin surpasses $50,000 for the first time in February 2021, when big firms invest in blockchain to push it to $58,000.</p>
<p>Numerous analysts predict that Bitcoin&#8217;s price would reach $100,000 by the end of 2021, and recent developments indicate that Bitcoin is on course to achieve or even exceed those projections.</p>
<p>All of this is projecting Bitcoin to explode in 2021.</p>
<h2>Litecoin <sub>LTC</sub></h2>
<h3><em>Projection: USD 360+ by the end of 2024 February</em></h3>
<p>Litecoin <sub>LTC</sub> has strong visibility and a massive market cap that are two of the primary factors to start trading this year.</p>
<p>If you want to minimize danger, ignore coins with limited market caps and communities and instead invest in cryptocurrencies such as Litecoin.</p>
<p>Why do we believe that Litecoin will be the next cryptocurrency to explode in value this year and in the years ahead?</p>
<p>To begin, there is a small supply of 84 million coins (compared to 21 million of Bitcoin) and a block reward of 12.5 LTC, which is very large in relation to other cryptocurrencies! (With such a payout, miners are certain to stay.)</p>
<p>Additionally, the average time required to mine a block on the Litecoin blockchain is around two minutes, which is faster than the majority of other cryptos available today.</p>
<p>This, along with the reality that Litecoin is one of Coinbase&#8217;s &#8220;major four,&#8221; leads many analysts to believe that Litecoin will undoubtedly be one of the altcoins regardless of what occurs in the future that remains solid until 2021.</p>
<p>Despite stiff rivalry, Litecoin is already considered one of the strongest cryptocurrencies in 2021. Although it is not the strongest technically, it does deliver outstanding investment prospects.</p>
<p>The price estimates for Litecoin in 2021 seem to be fair. According to CoinPedia&#8217;s Delma Wilson, &#8220;[Litecoin] could hit higher levels of $360 by December 2021,&#8221; levels not seen since 2017.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>So, considering the above Litecoin can be an option to consider in 2021.</p>
<h2>Ethereum<sub>ETH</sub></h2>
<h3><em>Projection: USD 4569 by the end of 2024 February</em></h3>
<p>With Ethereum, you can never go wrong.</p>
<p>Ethereum is one of the strongest cryptocurrencies to invest in since it was the first big project to implement smart contracts, allowing developers to create desktop and mobile decentralized applications (dApps) blockchain technology.</p>
<p>Since then, Ethereum has maintained a place in the top ten cryptocurrencies until 2021, and it is expected to do so for decades to come.</p>
<p>Not just that, Ethereum is the second most liquid blockchain, behind only Bitcoin in terms of liquidity. This ensures that purchasing or selling Ethereum would be effortless.</p>
<p>As with Bitcoin, there is still somebody waiting to purchase or sell Ethereum on the other side of the deal.</p>
<p>Another justification to think Ethereum can continue to be a solid cryptocurrency investment in the years to come is its dedicated team and culture.</p>
<p>This increases the likelihood of Ethereum being secure and only rising in value in the long term, far into 2021.</p>
<p>Additionally, since many more Ether (Ethereum tokens) will occur than Bitcoin or Litecoin, it is less likely to face scaling problems. It is less likely to develop a &#8216;locked system&#8217; where only a select few have access to tokens.</p>
<p>The Ether token powers the decentralized application ecosystem, which means that millions of developers and businesses would need it to run smart contracts and launch apps.</p>
<p>And that&#8217;s before you mention the plethora of other tokens that Ethereum&#8217;s blockchain embraces (TRON, for example, began as an ERC-20 Token)!</p>
<p>62% of respondents think Ethereum, the second-largest cryptocurrency by market capitalization after Bitcoin, would reach at least $1900 in 2021, rendering it the coin to follow in 2021.</p>
<p>Ethereum&#8217;s price estimate for 2021 is between $3,802 and $4,569 by December, according to the Economy Forecast Agency!</p>
<p>Ethereum is most definitely the next blockchain to burst in 2021, after Bitcoin.</p>
<p>So, you should better contemplate making an investment in Ethereum in 2021.</p>
<h2>Basic Attention Token <sub>BAT</sub></h2>
<h3><em>Projection: 30.99% rise by the end of 2024 February</em></h3>
<p>BAT was one of the strongest cryptocurrencies in 2018, 2019, and 2020, and it seems that trend will continue far into 2021.</p>
<p>The Basic Attention Token (BAT) is a utility token that the Brave Browser utilizes.</p>
<p>The BAT token is mostly applied to tip content owners and practically everyone else on the Internet that you deem beneficial. It&#8217;s a lucrative niche market.</p>
<p>You have the option of tipping them for any enlightening knowledge or material that you get. This has a lot of promise, given the size of the web browser industry.</p>
<p>Not just that, but people who watch advertisements will also earn BAT. This is an unexplored environment that has the ability to open up a slew of new doors for both the end-user and the Brave Browser.</p>
<p>Brendan Eich, a co-founder of Mozilla Firefox and a co-creator of JavaScript, is the brains behind this idea. With such qualifications, you can bet on BAT&#8217;s potential success.</p>
<p>In the collapse of so many other coins, BAT has remained remarkably consistent, which is an indication of a safe accumulation.</p>
<p>Demand for this cryptocurrency is projected to rise, which would almost certainly increase the token&#8217;s market value in 2021.</p>
<p>In the end, it all comes down to how the culture evolves around the Brave browser and whether people find meaning in their concept.</p>
<p>According to Digitalcoin, by December 2021, this cryptocurrency might be worth up to $0.77361743 per coin, a 30.99 percent raise!</p>
<p>Considering the above, Investing in BAT in 2021 will not be a bad idea.</p>
<h2>Cardano <sub>ADA</sub></h2>
<h3><em>Projection: USD 10 by the end of 2024 February</em></h3>
<p>Cardano has been a dominant force since its inception in 2015, and 2021 seems to be another banner year for this cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>The main feature of Cardano is its Ouroboros network, which is really two blockchains that run in tandem.</p>
<p>One blockchain is used for standard transfers, and the other is used for smart contracts.</p>
<p>Cardano believes that by dividing the two, one will guarantee scalability and speed by ensuring that the two forms of transactions do not interfere with one another.</p>
<p>However, there is far more to Cardano than meets the eye.</p>
<p>Cardano is a third-generation cryptocurrency that appears to be doing a number of the same things as Ethereum. Still, with the addition of a Proof of Stake algorithm, something Ethereum has been planning for a long time.</p>
<p>Additionally, Cardano utilizes time slots (known as an &#8216;epoch&#8217;), in which transaction chains must be generated within a specified time period by slot representatives&#8217; elected by stakeholders.</p>
<p>And here&#8217;s a fun detail about Cardano: Cardano is owned by up to 95% of Japanese residents, and it is often alluded to as the &#8216;Japanese Ethereum&#8217;.</p>
<p>Cardano was on the verge of hitting a $30.7 billion market value in February 2021, and a lone coin was trading at $1.07 (pretty affordable!).</p>
<p>According to others, Cardano has a great deal more to come. According to Dare Shonubi of CoinPedia, it could hit as much as $10 by the close of 2021, which will make it one of the strongest coins to invest in by a long shot.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Cash <sub>BCH</sub></h2>
<h3><em>Projection: USD 1000 to 1500 by the end of 2024 February</em></h3>
<p>Since the day the Bitcoin network was forked in August 2017, Bitcoin Cash has become a thorn in the side of Bitcoin, and in its three short years, it has attracted a lot of publicity from several major stars.</p>
<p>Roger Ver, dubbed &#8216;Bitcoin Jesus,&#8217; is often known as the face of Bitcoin Cash, having previously been an outspoken proponent of Bitcoin.</p>
<p>As is the case with many Bitcoin Cash proponents, he argues that the initial one has strayed way too far from its original purpose.</p>
<p>Bitcoin Cash backers point out how Bitcoin has embraced features such as the Lightning Network and SegWit2x that they claim are superfluous and depart from Nakamoto&#8217;s initial white paper vision.</p>
<p>The Bitcoin Cash squad, on the other hand, is now focusing on introducing smart deals, that many expect would result in a significant contraction. Some were so convinced of this that they jumped ship once more, this time to found Bitcoin SV.</p>
<p>A further significant advantage Bitcoin Cash has over Bitcoin is significantly lower exchange fees, as well as being significantly cheaper to invest in.</p>
<p>Even after the scene, it still offers a plethora of investment opportunities and the potential to amass a sizable fortune.</p>
<p>Bitcoin Cash reached its peak in February 2020, when it crossed nearly a $9 billion sale price, equivalent to $500 per coin.</p>
<p>Then, in February 2021, the rate of BCH reaches $695 per coin. Experts believe that the coin&#8217;s worth will reach $1,500 by the end of 2021</p>
<p>Crispus Nyaga, writing for Investing Cube, provided a more conservative outlook, predicting that BCH would hit $1,000 this year.</p>
<h2>Binance Coin <sub>BNB</sub></h2>
<h3><em>Projection: USD 505 by the end of 2024 February</em></h3>
<p>Binance Coin is one of the better cryptocurrencies to invest in 2021 if you&#8217;re looking to boost your portfolio and already hold big cryptocurrencies such as BTC or ETH.</p>
<p>Binance, the organization behind the coin, has a strong corporate background and an established team behind the primary idea of being a &#8216;utility token.&#8217;</p>
<p>The appeal of Binance Coin stems from its utility, which is to offer a discount to investors who use it to purchase other coins on the Binance Exchange.</p>
<p>The performance of the Binance market demonstrates to a large number of customers that they possess the necessary expertise and tools to ensure the success of this coin.</p>
<p>Additionally, Binance Coin is one of the most volatile cryptocurrencies at the moment, ranking among the top ten on CoinMarketCap.</p>
<p>Additionally, its volume exhibits steady development. Through the fluctuations, Binance Coin&#8217;s price increased threefold in the past year.</p>
<p>Additionally, the Binance Exchange is one of the fastest increasing cryptocurrency exchanges in the world and is very famous.</p>
<p>Binance Coin is used for all trades on the exchange, rendering BNB one of the most rapidly expanding cryptocurrencies this year in terms of trading value.</p>
<p>Binance Coin has an incredible future for 2021, with The Economy Forecast Agency predicting a December price of between $439 and $505, a huge boost.</p>
<h2>TRON <sub>TRX </sub></h2>
<h3><em>Projection: 185% rise by the end of 2024 February</em></h3>
<p>We&#8217;re excited to bring TRON to the roster after it bought BitTorrent a few years back.</p>
<p>In the long run, this could have a significant impact on the company&#8217;s value if they succeed in developing more secure and decentralized torrenting methods.</p>
<p>Some anticipate technologies such as dispersing file segments around a network and reassembling them for consumer installation.</p>
<p>Finally, TRON is seen as an audacious initiative with a ton planned for the future.</p>
<p>Another explanation for TRON&#8217;s inclusion on our list is that TRX or Tronix (the token featured on the Tron network) is one of the only ERC-20 tokens to have made it to the main net. Its blockchain is operational!</p>
<p>Additionally, as of 2021, TRON has over 4 million accounts. The rise is very remarkable and demonstrates TRON&#8217;s enormous potential; not many other coins may boast such a large user base.</p>
<p>TRX was listed 15th on CoinMarketCap&#8217;s ranking of the biggest coins by stock price in 2020.</p>
<p>Tronix may also be used in a similar fashion to BAT for content users to compensate content owners for rights to original media.</p>
<p>The assets would then be sent to the producers&#8217; accounts, where they could be traded for other cryptocurrencies or used to pay for a variety of blockchain services.</p>
<p>As a result of these factors, analysts assume TRX is a viable altcoin and that investors can do additional analysis before trading in it in 2021.</p>
<p>TRON is expected to hit $0.0716 through one year as well as $0.152 in five years, according to Wallet Investor! That&#8217;s a whopping 185.89 percent!</p>
<h2>EOS</h2>
<h3><em>Projection: USD 22 by the end of 2024 February</em></h3>
<p>Many individuals who have discussed the Ethereum network&#8217;s vulnerabilities have now shifted their assets to EOS, dubbed &#8216;The Ethereum Killer&#8217; by others.</p>
<p>EOS has also surpassed some of Ethereum&#8217;s obstacles, such as the need for developers to know how and when to code in Solidity, and is very well for offering developer resources such as account management and database creation that do not involve coding skills.</p>
<p>Investors are also celebrating EOS&#8217;s many technical benefits, including its significantly faster performance and scalability compared to Ethereum and Bitcoin.</p>
<p>Additionally, customers are not required to pay gas charges to access the network; instead, purchases are approved by a centralized body of 21 gatekeepers.</p>
<p>Another factor of EOS that captures your interest this year is its sizable and fervent population.</p>
<p>Additionally, EOS recently concluded a highly profitable token sale, acquiring more than enough money to expand to its maximum potential in 2021 and the future years.</p>
<p>PrimeXBT forecasts that EOS will reach a minimum of $1 and a crazy peak of $22 in 2021.</p>
<h2>RIPPLE <sub>XRP</sub></h2>
<h3><em>Projection: USD 1 by the end of 2024 February</em></h3>
<p>Ripple is ranked seventh in terms of market capitalization, closely followed by Polkadot and Cardano.</p>
<p>Ripple&#8217;s philosophy and aims are quite unique in comparison to the other cryptocurrencies on this list, which renders it very unique.</p>
<p>Ripple is an investment start-up that provides financial settlement facilities to banks, enabling them to conduct trades across national boundaries immediately and instantly.</p>
<p>As a result, Ripple is more geared toward big organizations than toward individual consumers.</p>
<p>It has collaborated with several major banks around the world over the years, including Bank of America, and even more financial companies are considering using the Ripple model to accelerate their purchases.</p>
<p>The explanation why analysts say Ripple could boom in 2021 and subsequent years is due to the legal issue with the SEC (US Securities and Exchange Commission), which believes Ripple should be listed as a defense.</p>
<p>Prices have also fallen precipitously, providing an incredible investment incentive for anyone who thinks Ripple can solve this temporary setback.</p>
<p>Ripple has a strong probability of defeating the lawsuit. To begin, Ripple has already been officially classified as a virtual currency by the Financial Crimes Enforcement Network (FinCEN)</p>
<p>XRP would undoubtedly remain a force in the cryptocurrency world and one of the strongest cryptocurrencies; it just requires some time to regain its foot in.</p>
<p>The City Telegraph has predicted that Ripple would reach a price of $1 per coin in 2021.</p>
<p>All of this suggests that Ripple may be one of the better cryptocurrencies to invest in 2021.</p>
<h2>Conclusion</h2>
<p>We assume you already have a clear understanding of the next cryptocurrency to explode in 2021 and could end up earning you money if you invest in them.</p>
<p>Bear in mind that investment is still a dangerous endeavor that can not be hurried.</p>
<p>You can make investment decisions only after doing an extensive analysis of the investment potential.</p>
<p>Ideally, you should have a firm grasp on how your preferred cryptocurrency operates, its prospects for growth, and, maybe most critically, what influences its price.</p>
<p>That&#8217;s all for today. Share this post and don&#8217;t forget to comment on which digital asset are you thinking to invest in 2021.</p>
<p>Happy Trading!!!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/next-cryptocurrency-to-explode/">Next cryptocurrency to explode in 2024 February</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">MrStocks.org</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/next-cryptocurrency-to-explode/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to buy UK government bonds</title>
		<link>/how-to-buy-uk-government-bonds/</link>
					<comments>/how-to-buy-uk-government-bonds/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Maximilian Weber]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 17:14:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.commissionfreetrading.net/?p=438</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Morbi interdum eu nunc non convallis. Nunc gravida mi ac consequat commodo. Integer ultrices bibendum nisl, vel ultricies elit auctor non. Proin hendrerit turpis sit amet efficitur finibus. Maecenas tempor ligula ac sollicitudin tincidunt. Phasellus nulla mauris, pellentesque at est ultricies, cursus consectetur mauris. Suspendisse potenti. Nulla [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-buy-uk-government-bonds/">How to buy UK government bonds</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">MrStocks.org</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Morbi interdum eu nunc non convallis. Nunc gravida mi ac consequat commodo. Integer ultrices bibendum nisl, vel ultricies elit auctor non. Proin hendrerit turpis sit amet efficitur finibus. Maecenas tempor ligula ac sollicitudin tincidunt. Phasellus nulla mauris, pellentesque at est ultricies, cursus consectetur mauris. Suspendisse potenti. Nulla metus velit, malesuada sed lacinia ut, sagittis et nisi.</p>
<p>Mauris pharetra leo et risus ornare efficitur. Cras velit velit, dapibus at ex at, cursus feugiat eros. Quisque odio ante, consectetur vitae hendrerit eget, vehicula id mi. Aenean vehicula hendrerit dolor, et lacinia est. Mauris venenatis dolor et fermentum laoreet. Suspendisse id magna quam. Donec consectetur augue eget lectus dignissim, sed sodales diam faucibus. Etiam placerat, dui eu scelerisque ullamcorper, urna massa congue mi, sit amet mollis ante nunc et nibh. Sed at ipsum nec ipsum molestie auctor. Sed rhoncus felis eu dolor rutrum, a lobortis nunc condimentum. Etiam gravida ullamcorper nisi iaculis feugiat. Fusce nec diam sed leo commodo faucibus. Nunc dictum nisi at tristique consequat. Duis eget lectus vestibulum, euismod enim vel, tempor eros. Nullam quis enim metus. Mauris faucibus facilisis lacus, id elementum nisl dictum sed.</p>
<p>Cras malesuada consequat nulla eget ultrices. Interdum et malesuada fames ac ante ipsum primis in faucibus. Pellentesque risus justo, euismod at commodo lobortis, eleifend at mauris. Praesent tincidunt nunc turpis, ut posuere magna ultrices at. Ut luctus justo vitae arcu tempus, vel semper purus maximus. Aliquam eu mauris aliquam, mollis tellus at, luctus dolor. Orci varius natoque penatibus et magnis dis parturient montes, nascetur ridiculus mus. In nec quam in metus pretium placerat. Cras vel nunc leo. Aenean euismod erat nec ipsum pretium consequat. Vivamus luctus nec turpis nec pretium. Nulla lacus nibh, aliquam ut risus dictum, pharetra pulvinar urna. Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Maecenas ac est urna. Aenean vulputate nisl ac erat blandit luctus.</p>
<p>Etiam sagittis lectus nec tristique aliquet. Integer dictum sem ipsum. Praesent vitae pulvinar nulla. Proin tristique sem quis metus maximus fermentum. Pellentesque felis ipsum, porta quis ultrices vel, viverra id ex. Quisque non lacinia diam. Suspendisse potenti. Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vivamus vel est eu orci suscipit tempus. Mauris orci mauris, euismod non auctor at, malesuada ac magna. Aliquam ullamcorper elit eleifend, hendrerit tortor in, luctus urna. Integer ut mollis ante, et rutrum ligula. Nullam quis suscipit ligula, non maximus orci. Nullam tempor, nunc in viverra auctor, mi nisi volutpat sem, sit amet pulvinar diam augue et urna. Nam id placerat enim, commodo pretium erat. Sed non urna at sem pellentesque rutrum non pharetra leo.</p>
<p>Phasellus sit amet ipsum interdum, consequat mi vel, faucibus tortor. Sed maximus dolor ut lorem congue, eget tempor quam tristique. Etiam viverra vel nisi vel efficitur. Ut mauris leo, ornare eget eros ac, viverra mattis arcu. Nulla mollis dui sit amet nunc aliquam, vitae aliquam neque convallis. In magna libero, euismod sit amet congue quis, dignissim at lacus. Phasellus non commodo felis. Morbi gravida ipsum nec justo porttitor imperdiet. Vestibulum sit amet feugiat justo, eget mattis mauris. Fusce suscipit nisi quam. Pellentesque interdum at est vitae luctus.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-buy-uk-government-bonds/">How to buy UK government bonds</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">MrStocks.org</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/how-to-buy-uk-government-bonds/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to invest in stocks in Canada</title>
		<link>/how-to-invest-in-stocks-canada/</link>
					<comments>/how-to-invest-in-stocks-canada/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Maximilian Weber]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 14:01:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.commissionfreetrading.net/?p=420</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>how to buy stocks in canada</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-invest-in-stocks-canada/">How to invest in stocks in Canada</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">MrStocks.org</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2><strong>how to buy stocks in canada</strong></h2>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-invest-in-stocks-canada/">How to invest in stocks in Canada</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">MrStocks.org</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/how-to-invest-in-stocks-canada/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Buy Penny Stocks in 2021</title>
		<link>/how-to-buy-penny-stocks/</link>
					<comments>/how-to-buy-penny-stocks/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Maximilian Weber]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 13:59:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.commissionfreetrading.net/?p=417</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The misconceptions around investing in stocks that trade per share prevent many people from making valuable investments. Trading can be intimidating to folks who feel like their knowledge and income level is too low to make smart investments in the stock market. It doesn&#8217;t have to be like that. The truth is there are opportunities [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-buy-penny-stocks/">How to Buy Penny Stocks in 2021</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">MrStocks.org</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The misconceptions around investing in stocks that trade per share prevent many people from making valuable investments. Trading can be intimidating to folks who feel like their knowledge and income level is too low to make smart investments in the stock market.</p>
<p>It doesn&#8217;t have to be like that. The truth is there are opportunities to build wealth with stock market investments at any income level. Gaining knowledge in investment opportunities can help you turn a few pennies into a healthy nest egg.</p>
<p>The term pennies is literal when talking about investing in the best penny stocks. If you know where to look, there are stocks per share available for cents per share that have enormous growth potential. Technology is increasing the availability of knowledge and access to investing in penny stocks. While this doesn&#8217;t come in encyclopedias with a table of contents the information is getting easier to find.</p>
<p>Plenty of resources are available to access financial advice and electronic trading platforms for stocks of small companies at affordable rates. It can all be waiting for you on your personal mobile device or laptop.</p>
<p>Read on to gain resources and valuable information on how to buy penny stocks that will significantly grow your investments.</p>
<h2>What is a Penny Stock?</h2>
<p>For any large investment portfolio to withstand the test of time, it has to start on a solid foundation of information before purchasing your stocks. To start, what is a penny stock?</p>
<p>Penny stocks are stocks, usually, of a small company. To be considered a true penny stock, the per share price should be less than five dollars (USD) each. In the past, to qualify as a penny stock the per share price had to be under one dollar each. In recent times, however, the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) adjusted the definition to include any shares under $5 per share. Many of these small companies penny stocks trade for literal pennies (with a stock price under $1 USD) or for just a few dollars each.</p>
<p>The low price point of these small company shares can make them attractive to potential investors with smaller budgets. Even with low liquidity you can get in on the action. Because of the low initial price point, there is more opportunity for growth.</p>
<p>That opportunity for growth, however, comes with a bigger risk. These smaller, less established companies may or may not experience significant growth as a company. A large percentage are just starting out and have very uncertain futures. Larger companies are able to absorb more risk and failure, while smaller companies could fold after a mistake or economic downturn.</p>
<p>As with many investment opportunities, the larger the potential growth, the bigger the risk. A stocks penny trade can be highly speculative. Therefore, it is advised to seek out information on the companies before buying penny stocks. Always do research, ask for advice, and then do research again.</p>
<h2>How to Buy Penny Stocks</h2>
<p>The majority of stocks trading, that the average individual is familiar with, trade on major stock exchanges like the New York Stock Exchange (NYSE) or the National Association of Securities Dealers Automated Quotations (NASDAQ). Other major international stock exchanges include the Tokyo Stock Exchange, Euronext, and others. Images that come to the mind of many people when they think about stocks trading include trading floors, flashing displays, and organized chaos. This type of environment only exists in those larger stock exchanges, not the penny stock. Penny stocks trade in a much less luxurious setting.</p>
<p>While a tiny fraction of penny stock can be found on those larger exchanges, because they are risky investments, how to buy or sell penny stocks is using over-the-counter (OTC) transactions. All OTC transactions occur electronically, not on a physical trading floor. So, you make money virtually since most aren&#8217;t listed on a major exchange.</p>
<p>OTC transactions operate through electronic transactions either on OTC Bulletin Board (OTCBB) or the OTC Markets Group. Penny stocks can also be found on a listing called the Pink Sheets.</p>
<h3>About OTC Bulletin Board and OTC Markets Group</h3>
<p>The OTCBB as it is more commonly known, is provided by the Financial Industry Regulatory Board (FINRA). It is an electronic quotation service for FINRA subscribers to manage their investments. The OTCBB was developed in 1990 after the SEC was required by recently passed legislation to develop a centralized location for investors to manage stocks that were not available on the major stock exchanges.</p>
<p>The major stock exchanges have certain requirements of businesses in order to trade on their exchange. Smaller businesses often didn&#8217;t meet the requirements for the major stock exchanges. Before there was the OTCBB, these small businesses did not have a centralized location to trade their shares.</p>
<p>With these alternatives, smaller businesses now have a way to earn capital to grow business by trading shares at lower price points. This is attractive to investors who are willing to take bigger risks on lesser known companies for an often much larger return on investment (ROI).</p>
<p>These alternatives are not just smaller versions of the major exchanges. Specifically, they are quotation services that all operate on a centralized server that can be accessed by subscribers. The trading, buying, and selling of penny stocks can be a bit different because of these technicalities.</p>
<h3>About Penny Stock Pink Sheets</h3>
<p>Most people think about the movie, the Wolf of Wall Street, with Leo Dicaprio when they think about penny stock. The movie showcases the pump and dump schemes of the 1980s when a small firm started beating major exchanges. They come in like amateurs and end up taking over the industry. They become brokers and traders by finding investors willing to buy stock in companies that aren&#8217;t the best, pump and dump the stock for epic profits, and start the game all over again the next day.</p>
<p>Historically, pink sheet stocks received their name from the color of paper these stock listings were printed on. Over time this has come to refer to a listing of small-company stocks that trade outside of the major stock exchanges and the OTC electronic quotation services. In many ways, stocks on these sheets are the rebels of the investment world.</p>
<p>These sheets are filled with smaller companies that do not qualify to be listed on the major stock exchanges (NASDAQ, NYSE, etc.). They also exist outside of the OTCBB and the OTC Markets Group. It is a private listing for OTC sales.</p>
<p>Stocks like this can be a tricky, risky investments for several reasons. These stocks carry all of the same risks that OTC sales of penny stocks hold while also maintaining short term private financial information.</p>
<p>Companies that trade on the electronic quotation services are under regulation by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). The publicly traded companies are required to adhere to the SEC&#8217;s trading rules and regulations.</p>
<p>Pink sheets are not under oversight from the SEC. This means they do not need to release as much information publicly. Pink sheet listings are required to submit some information to OTC Compliance Unit, but it is less than the requirements for listing on the OTCBB or OTC Markets Group.</p>
<p>All of the factors (less public information, smaller companies, etc.) involved with pink sheets make sure these penny stock investments are very high risk. It would take in-depth and intense knowledge to understand which pink sheets could prove fruitful so they trade infrequently.</p>
<p>Another risk involved with pink sheet stocks is the higher potential for fraud. Because the companies are under fewer reporting regulations, there has been a history of companies listing themselves on this market as the company is on the verge of collapse. This is in an effort to pump and dump the value of the stock to boost their low liquidity.</p>
<p>Traders dealing in penny stocks have sometimes been a last grab for money as the doors were closing. In some instances, companies&#8217; stocks listed in these markets were discovered to not even be real and were completely fraudulent transactions. They used shady brokers and traders listed to buy and sell their stocks without a company at all.</p>
<p>If you choose to accept the risk of pink sheets trades, be mindful and do plenty of research on the penny stock you&#8217;re considering. Find brokers who will help you find the best match with your budget and the best traders that know how to find the winners. With all the other opportunities available, it isn&#8217;t advised for newcomers to start with the pink sheets. It is especially not advised for pink sheets to be the sole stock investments in a portfolio. This isn&#8217;t the pump and dump 80s after all.</p>
<h2>Where to Trade Penny Stocks</h2>
<p>Smaller businesses with share rates that qualify for trading penny stocks need to find ways to trade outside of the major stock exchanges like NYSE or NASDAQ. There are brokers who specialize in penny stocks but you have to dig to find them. To start trading penny stocks, look into electronic quotation services that provide a centralized digital platform to buy, sell, and trade penny stocks. With the low price point, it is helpful to find companies that minimize the amount of commissions, trade fees, and minimum balances. A $5 commission can eat into a penny stock investment much quicker than a company that trades at $1,000 a share, for example.</p>
<p>The following are fantastic online brokers and traditional places to trade penny stocks with zero commission and all rights reserved:</p>
<ul>
<li>Fidelity</li>
<li>Charles Schwab</li>
<li>TradeStation</li>
<li>Firsttrade</li>
<li>eOption</li>
</ul>
<h2>Apps that Trade Penny Stocks</h2>
<p>Stock traders mobile apps like Stash and Robinhood are gaining fast popularity among newbie stock investors. Success stories surging around the internet of investors hitting it big have boosted their popularity. The apps provide an easy way for investors to get started in stock investments with low account minimums. For example, the mobile trading app Stash allows users to open an account with a minimum of just $1 investment and a $1 fee each month.</p>
<p>The majority of mobile apps are letting investors trade on the major stock exchanges and no not offer penny stock options. The low priced entry point is buying percentages of larger shares on major stock exchanges like NYSE and NASDAQ (and some major international stock exchanges as well.)</p>
<p>The world of mobile investors is starting to get into penny stock trading, however. The following investment companies offer penny stocks and an online brokers trading option:</p>
<ul>
<li>Charles Schwab</li>
<li>Fidelity Investments</li>
<li>Ameritrade</li>
<li>TradeStation</li>
<li>eTrade</li>
</ul>
<p>Mobile apps are a convenient way for investors to manage your penny stock investments. Generally, a robo-investors is part of the experience. This a cheap and user-friendly way to buy, sell, trade, and manage penny stock investments. Because penny stocks value can quickly change, having the option to monitor your investments on your mobile devices could help you avoid a big loss or score a big win.</p>
<h2>Costs of Penny Stock Trading Platforms</h2>
<p>In addition to the cost of the investment itself, investors choosing to use a trading platform comes with certain costs. As outlined above, there are plenty of trading platforms that charge zero commissions to trade. Trading commissions used to be a big expense of stock investing, but technology has lowered the overhead. Now most firms charge zero or very commissions. While others charge zero commissions, but do charge trade fees per trade.</p>
<p>In addition to trade fees and commissions, there are other costs to consider when choosing a trading platform. Many platforms require a minimum investment. With some platforms, there are fees if the balance drops below the minimum investment. Before diving in, determine what your budget is for the minimum investment. This can help you eliminate any platforms where the minimum investment is outside of your budget.</p>
<p>With the investment apps and platforms, some require a repeating membership fee. Usually, these costs are relatively low, but it is something to be aware of.</p>
<h2>Tips for Trading Penny Stocks Successfully</h2>
<p>Stock prices can be confusing if you don&#8217;t understand how the true value of shares is calculated. Individual stock prices are only half of the true value of the stocks. To determine the true value, you have to understand the real business value of the stock or the market capitalization. Market capitalization is determined by two things:</p>
<ul>
<li>The price of the individual stock</li>
<li>The number of shares outstanding</li>
</ul>
<p>Shares outstanding are how many individual shares of stock a company has made available. A penny stock that is trading for $1, for example, and has 100 million shares has the same market capitalization as a firm that trades $100 shares with 1 million shares outstanding.</p>
<p>Understanding this can help avoid overvaluing a penny stock and its potential return on investment (ROI).</p>
<p>Once you have a better grip on the market capitalization of penny stocks, you can make informed decisions. To make the most of trading penny stocks, there are some rules of thumb to follow:</p>
<p><strong>1. Avoid paying commissions</strong>. With the smaller value of the penny stocks, those commission fees could make significant dents in your ROI. Sometimes smaller profit margins mean you need to operate lean. There are plenty of commission-free trading options available, so always check the policies and fine print of any service or brokerage before investing in penny stocks.</p>
<p><strong>2. Diversify.</strong> With great risk comes great reward, but it also comes with loss. In an overall investment portfolio, penny stocks should only be one element. Diversifying investments will prove the most fruitful and balanced in the long term.</p>
<p><strong>3. Research. And then Research Again.</strong> With penny stocks, research is critical to making smart money moves. Dig into all information you can find directly from the company, but don&#8217;t stop there. Third-party information will provide a clearer picture of this company&#8217;s value and ensure that you aren&#8217;t only receiving a rose-colored picture from the company itself.</p>
<p>Expand your research even further and find out what is happening in that company&#8217;s industry. Is the industry experiencing growth? Is that industry oversaturated? Is the company doing something that will set them apart from competitors? Make sure you have a solid understanding of the company&#8217;s position before plunging into the penny stocks.</p>
<p><strong>4. Follow Investments Closely.</strong> Even more so than with the major stock exchanges, you will want to follow your penny stock investments. If you have invested in major or blue-chip stocks in the past, you have probably received advice to hold onto the shares for the long term as the market generally tends to grow over time. Penny stocks are a different beast.</p>
<p>The prices of penny stocks can swing quickly and wildly. The positive is that this can be exciting. Penny stocks have the potential to make significant money in a short amount of time. Alternatively, the stock could quickly dip or the company could even fold. Watching the turns in the value will help you know when it&#8217;s time to sell and get out to protect your investment.</p>
<h2>Common Mistakes and Pitfalls of Penny Stocks</h2>
<p>Making smart investments means staying informed and understanding the real risk of penny stock investments. The following are common mistakes of buying penny stocks.</p>
<p><strong>1. Assuming large growth.</strong> A common misconception about penny stocks, especially for beginners in the arena, is that all penny stocks will provide a larger profit margin because of the low buy-in point. Technically, the potential for growth is larger with a smaller buying point. That is mathematically correct, but it does not guarantee that all penny stocks will experience significant growth.</p>
<p>There is always the potential for huge growth, but it is not an eventuality. Sometimes penny stocks are valued so low because the company and shares are just not worth as much. There is always a risk in losing the entire investment with stocks and with penny stocks that risk is greater. The lower price point puts penny stocks closer to zero from the start.</p>
<p><strong>2. Failing to do research.</strong> Continuing from point number one, not all businesses trading penny stocks are created equal. It is imperative, maybe even more so than with major stocks, to do diligent research on a company before investing. Great questions to ask are:</p>
<ul>
<li>Is the industry this company is in growing?</li>
<li>Is this company doing something innovative or different than competitors? Will this provide this company an advantage?</li>
<li>Who is the leadership? Have the leadership of this company had successful ventures in the past?</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>3. Not seeking professional advice.</strong> Like so many things in life and business, asking for help from a seasoned professional is the smartest move. If you have access to a live person that has experience trading penny stocks, that can be your best resource. If that is unavailable, there is plenty of expertise in online articles, blogs, and forums to help guide your decisions.</p>
<p><strong>4. Investing more than you can truly afford.</strong> Penny stocks can deliver exceptional return. On the flip side, however, penny stocks can have a bigger potential to fail. Be confident that whatever investment is made in penny stocks will not financially ruin you if the investment doesn&#8217;t work out.</p>
<p>In conclusion, penny stocks can be an exciting and beneficial investment opportunity for the right investors. Penny stocks offer a low starting point, active participation, and huge potential to make serious cash. Not to mention, the process of learning the penny stocks industry provides ample opportunity to improve overall financial and investment knowledge. Once you successfully navigate making money in penny stocks, you can have an overall better understanding of all stock investments and how they can benefit your personal portfolio.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-buy-penny-stocks/">How to Buy Penny Stocks in 2021</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">MrStocks.org</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/how-to-buy-penny-stocks/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Best shares to buy for beginner in UK</title>
		<link>/best-shares-to-buy-for-beginner-in-uk/</link>
					<comments>/best-shares-to-buy-for-beginner-in-uk/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Maximilian Weber]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 13:54:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.commissionfreetrading.net/?p=414</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/best-shares-to-buy-for-beginner-in-uk/">Best shares to buy for beginner in UK</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">MrStocks.org</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/best-shares-to-buy-for-beginner-in-uk/">Best shares to buy for beginner in UK</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">MrStocks.org</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/best-shares-to-buy-for-beginner-in-uk/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top 10 Ethical Companies to Invest in for 2021</title>
		<link>/ethical-companies-to-invest-in/</link>
					<comments>/ethical-companies-to-invest-in/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Maximilian Weber]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 14:04:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://demos.pokatheme.com/pokatheme/?p=70</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With climate change increasing every year and corruption regularly exposed through the media, people who invest in stock and are choosing where they want to make an investment and are thinking more and more about which stock they earn money with, their investments, and how they can stay as socially responsible as possible. If the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ethical-companies-to-invest-in/">Top 10 Ethical Companies to Invest in for 2021</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">MrStocks.org</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With climate change increasing every year and corruption regularly exposed through the media, people who invest in stock and are choosing where they want to make an investment and are thinking more and more about which stock they earn money with, their investments, and how they can stay as socially responsible as possible.</p>
<p>If the entity behind the stock uses unsustainable social practices, doesn&#8217;t have fair-trading conditions, or engages in profiteering, you will be supporting those unethical practices by investing in their stock. Do you want that list on your conscience?</p>
<p>The time has come where people don&#8217;t want to have their personal finance portfolio tied up in arms and weapons, fossil fuels, or earn money investing with nuclear power. Those companies with stock available that limit their greenhouse gas emissions year after year, have ESG social practices in place, accept climate change and practice corporate governance are more appealing to a broader range of investors in today&#8217;s economy.</p>
<p>They look for ethical companies to invest in, those publicly traded companies that they feel socially responsible investing (SRI) in. The definition of ethics can be subjective, but the definition used by many financial institutions relates to a publicly traded company that makes a positive impact through environmental, social, and governance (ESG) best practices.</p>
<p>You may be wondering if you can invest and make a profit in a socially responsible publicly traded company that agrees with your beliefs. The answer is, yes you can. There are many ethical companies that you can invest in and some may surprise you. Ready to start ESG investing? Here are 10 of the stock market most ethical companies to invest in for 2021 that care about the environmental, social, and corporate governance (ESG) effects they have globally.</p>
<h2>1. Ford Motor Company (F)</h2>
<p>Ford is a U.S company and is one of the very few automotive companies publicly traded on the stock market that is listed on Ethisphere’s 100 top ethical companies. The Ethisphere Institute measures and defines high ethical standards followed in businesses. It publishes a list and gives an award every year to the World’s Most Ethical Companies. It also provides verification services for ethical practices and gives certificates of social practices.</p>
<p>Even though the automotive industry is heavily dependent on fossil fuels, Ford has taken steps towards greening its business practices through socially responsible investing (SRI) in initiatives such as Partnership for a Cleaner Environment (PACE).</p>
<p>PACE focuses on improving water and energy consumption. Ford aims to save 550 million gallons of water by next year.</p>
<p>Ford was the first manufacturer of vehicles to join the Electronic Industry Citizenship Coalition (EICC), or Responsible Business Alliance (RBA). This non-profit alliance works to create ethical supply chains for motor parts.</p>
<p>Ford’s aim at the beginning of the new decade starts with a fundamental redesign to compete in the emerging era of clean energy and the smart vehicles that support it. This includes heavy investment in the latest technologies and ESG measures to remain competitive.</p>
<h2>2. PUMA (PUM)</h2>
<p>PUMA started its journey to ethical business practices in 1993 with its youngest ever CEO of a German Company, Jochen Zeitz. At that time, PUMA was near bankruptcy and today it is among the top socially responsible companies and one of the top three sports brands in the world. He continues to be a leader in sustainable business practices for other companies, but this is about Puma.</p>
<p>Zeitz’s leadership at Puma showcased how ethical principles and profitability go hand in hand like solar and efficiency. He introduced multiple sustainability projects such as PUMAVision in 2008 which outlined the four business principles including fair business practices, honesty, positive social messages and creativity.</p>
<p>His Environmental Profit &amp; Loss Account (E P&amp;L) is widely used today by many businesses for the ethical use of resources. In 2011, Puma began attributing a monetary value to ecosystem services in every aspect of Puma’s supply chain.</p>
<p>The reason business leaders listen to Zeitz is because he has shown by example. He increased Puma’s share price by 4,000 percent in 13 years while introducing his two main procedures for sustainability. One is PUMAVision with its ethical code of behavior that applies to staff, its relationship to external organizations and its business dealings. The other is the E P&amp;L.</p>
<p>Even after Zeitz left as the CEO, Puma has continued its drive for sustainability and continues to be one of the top ethical companies. For example, by the end of 2020, they promised to derive more than 90 percent of their cotton and polyester used in their products to come from sustainable sources. If you invest in Puma, you can be sure it understands the principle that following ESG and ethical business practices doesn’t cost money, it saves money.</p>
<h2>3. International Business Machines (IBM)</h2>
<p>Everybody knows IBM. The company is U.S based and was founded in 1911. It&#8217;s headquartered in New York. Its main job is to manufacture range of hardware and provide consulting services. IBM is one of the largest companies in the world with more than 350,000 employees in 177 countries. It may seem impossible for such a large company to adhere to ethical and sustainable business practices, but IBM manages to be socially responsible without changing the price.</p>
<p>IBM is a champion of diversity in its workforce. Their data centers are designed to be environmentally friendly with environmental policies that provide for conserving natural resources, like water and like fossil fuels, by recycling and reusing as well as only buying a range of recycled materials in their production processes when they can. This boosts their ESG ratings and reflects in their stock.</p>
<p>They use smart systems that make their products energy-efficient at an affordable price. IBM was listed on the 2019 and 2020 lists of Ethisphere’s most sustainable companies in the world. IBM continues to maintain ethical behavior and says the most successful organizations focus on purpose and values to drive long-term thinking and planning. It gives respect to all its employees. The aim is to make the world a better place for stakeholders and socially responsible investing (SRI) as is clearly expressed in IBM’s Principles of Trust and Transparency regarding their stock.</p>
<h2>4. Microsoft (MSFT)</h2>
<p>Microsoft is the giant American multinational software company founded by Bill Gates and Paul Allen in 1775. The Bill and Melinda Gates Foundation is the wealthiest charitable foundation in the world and helps in the range of millions of people, but that is not enough to be an ethical business. However, the Microsoft company makes a serious commitment to ESG, ethics, the environment, and sustainability regardless of price.</p>
<p>Some of the environmental commitments and the like made by Microsoft include the purchase of more than 1.6 gigawatts of new solar and wind energy and recycling in the range of 10 million kilos of electronic consumer waste every year. The company has also reduced its carbon emissions by 15.6 million tons. Microsoft uses a range of recycled materials, especially in their new products. This boosted the stock price of Microsoft and their image of sustainable investing in the tech market.</p>
<p>Respecting the environment is not the only area in which Microsoft is a socially responsible and ethical company. Investors can rest easy in buying their stock knowing it&#8217;s socially responsible investing (SRI) It also has an anti-corruption service that is implemented through its partnership with CREATe Compliance.</p>
<p>This is not a one-time deal. It is a consistent measurement and improvement of risk areas, so they can be benchmarked and shared throughout the supply chain. CREATe Compliance combines with Ethisphere to provide global companies with expanded services.</p>
<p>When you are looking for investing opportunities with ethical companies, always find out if they are compliant with Ethisphere, CREATe Compliance, or Business Ethics Leadership Alliance (BELA) for investing.</p>
<h2>5. Volvo Cars (VLVLY)</h2>
<p>Volvo is another automotive company that is an ethical company to want for your investment portfolio. It is also one of the few vehicle manufacturers you have the option of investing in that is on Ethisphere’s list in 2019. It is a Swedish luxury car manufacturer that produced in the range of 700,000 cars total in 2019. It has committed to using blockchain technology to track the cobalt used in its batteries.</p>
<p>This is a major ethical move and Volvo is one of the first automotive companies to do so. From 2019 onwards, Volvo will only produce fully electric cars or hybrid models as a commitment to reducing carbon emissions. Cobalt is often produced through environmentally unsustainable practices and may even involve child labor. They will work with companies that produce traceable and sustainable batteries. Its investors will be pleased to know by 2025, it plans to make at least 50 percent of its cars fully electric.</p>
<p>For compliance and ethics in the workplace, Volvo has established a special division to support sustainable business practices that govern the employee’s code of conduct as well as their partner’s business practices. It was named the most ethical company in the world by the Ethisphere Institute for three consecutive years starting in 2017 which is wonderful for investors.</p>
<p>Also, Volvo Cars is a founding member of the United Nations Global Compact to implement universal sustainability principles which helps boost their sustainability status in the mind of investors. This includes a code of conduct that ensures that each employee conducts business ethically and responsibly. You can find these codes on their website. With a company culture of openness and integrity, employees are welcome to ask questions about the code of conduct and anonymously report any concerns they may have. Investors can feel great investing money and buying their share in the stock VLVLY.</p>
<h2>6. Hennes &amp; Mauritz AB aka H&amp;M (HMB.ST)</h2>
<p>Hennes &amp; Mauritz or H&amp;M is a clothing company based in Sweden that is the second largest in the world. It has shops on the high streets and in malls across the United States and Europe. It was founded in 1947 and emerged in 2020 as the second-largest clothing retailer in the world. They focus on quality clothing and accessories at an affordable price.</p>
<p>Investors should note that H&amp;M has met the challenges that all clothing companies face today of ethics and sustainability. Ethisphere has listed H&amp;M as one of the most ethical companies in the world eight times. The company defines and measures high corporate ethical standards and it&#8217;s stock reflects it.</p>
<p>The latest sustainability efforts include a limited edition of popular jeans made with 100 percent post-consumer waste that is recyclable breathable cotton-like fabric. It also includes a children’s collection for rent to encourage reusing clothing. The clothing can include individual pieces or bundles of clothes.</p>
<p>The awards given were based on H&amp;M’s practices in sustainability especially with its supply chain as well as code of ethics for conducting business. One of its major efforts is to reduce the reliance on harmful chemicals in the fabric industry to achieve total toxic-free clothing by 2030.</p>
<p>H&amp;M’s code of conduct makes it a leader among socially responsible companies. It includes teamwork where skills, knowledge, and experience are shared and encouraged. The code also encourages individuality and respect for others as well as maintaining the entrepreneurial spirit. Employees are constantly learning and redefining limits and expectations and looking for sustainable choices that bring value to the business.</p>
<p>This means you can feel good about investing in the stock and that the price will likely continue to move up.</p>
<h2>7. Tesla (TSLA)</h2>
<p>As a pioneer of the U.S and global electric car market since 2003, Tesla has achieved the position of a leader in producing electric cars. Along with electric cars, Tesla has a huge investment in Solar City a renewable energy subsidiary. Tesla has several initiatives that will make it a leader in ethical corporate culture as well as electric vehicles and renewable energies.</p>
<p>Tesla makes a car that is constructed to last 100 years or a lifetime, which certainly goes a long way to justifying their high price tag. This is a totally unique idea for car manufacturers. Of course, there are a few consumables such as tires and battery packs, but Tesla’s ambition is to conserve natural resources and reduce carbon emissions.</p>
<p>Even the design is created to be timeless without trendy decorations, so the car will look good for years. The drive train that usually takes the most abuse in a vehicle is made and tested to last over a million miles. There are several Teslas today that have been driven 486,000 miles and several taxis driven more than 300,000 miles total on the original battery.</p>
<p>Most car manufacturers build with planned obsolescence to force people to buy new cars regularly. Tesla has proven that you can make a profit by providing a high-quality, sustainable product.</p>
<p>In June 2014, the CEO of Tesla, Elon Musk, proved that the company is socially responsible. Since 2003, the engineers at Tesla have created and patented a lot of new technology that is needed for sustainable electric cars. They kept the patents to maintain their edge in the electric car market. In 2014, Elon Musk released access to all of the company’s patents, so any car manufacturer could use them to make electric cars.</p>
<p>This is a clear sign that moving forward, Tesla wants as many electric cars as possible on the roads. Tesla’s mission has an emphasis on social responsibility and works to develop products that have economic and social benefits. If you are looking for ethical companies to invest in, Tesla is a good one and the stock price just keeps continuing to rise.</p>
<h2>8. First Solar (FSLR)</h2>
<p>First Solar is one of the largest solar panel manufacturers anywhere. Being a sustainable energy company isn’t enough to make it an ethical company to invest in. It needs to have an ethical corporate culture. First Solar’s vision is to be a leader in the world’s energy future. It provides cost-advantaged solar technology through innovation as well as customer engagement.</p>
<p>First Solar states that its success derives from employees and leaders that are innovative and passionate people who work ethically and safely together. Every person from the Board of Directors to partners is held accountable to follow the Code of Conduct for ethical business practices. It provides an open, anonymous forum for people to speak up about any irregularities, concerns or questions.</p>
<p>The code addresses working together respectfully, without any kind of harassment in the working environment while working together safely and protecting employee privacy. The Code stands for fundamental human rights and the dignity of workers everywhere. This means it does not work with third parties who use forced or child labor. First Solar follows the law on conflict minerals and all policies and procedures that govern activities that impact the environment.</p>
<h2>9. Weyerhaeuser (WY)</h2>
<p>Weyerhaeuser was named the most ethical company by the Ethisphere Institute 11 times. It has a total 120 years record of corporate ethics and fair practices. It is a member of the Alberta Forest Products Association (AFPA). It&#8217;s known for it&#8217;s Code of Ethics including employee training, confidential reporting of concerns, and clear expectations for suppliers.</p>
<p>The company Code of Ethics is far-reaching and includes guidance on how to handle conflicts of interest, competition and antitrust laws, international business conduct, harassment prevention, discrimination, human rights, health and safety, and more.</p>
<p>It not only follows a code of ethics, it expects its suppliers to be ethical regardless of price. This means they must comply with ESG, health, and safety laws. The company uses a diverse community of suppliers and expects them to be aligned with its needs and values.</p>
<p>Weyerhaeuser is guided by the United Nations’ Universal Declaration of Human Rights as part of its code of ethics and is on the Dow Jones Sustainability Indices and has received numerous awards for diversity, sustainability, and good corporate citizenship. It only uses wood from the Sustainable Forestry Initiative for non-controversial wood fiber even if that makes the price more expensive.</p>
<p>The list goes on and on and it is easy to see why Weyerhaeuser is always listed as one of the most ethical businesses.</p>
<h2>10. 3M (MMM)</h2>
<p>Last on this list is 3M. It has been listed among the most ethical companies for six consecutive years and is a great investment. The 3M culture upholds SRI by including unwavering integrity and doing the right thing each and every day. Customers, employees, and shareholders trust the ethical corporate culture of 3M.</p>
<p>Its long-standing commitment to sustainability is the core value of the company. They have recently shifted to renewable energy sources and commitments including reducing greenhouse gas emissions, and promoting a volunteer skill-based program.</p>
<p>3M is a science-based company that uses scientific exploration to address a huge portfolio of problems, including but not limited to water supply, raw materials, energy, climate, health, safety, education, and development. It launches about 1,000 new products every year and embeds sustainability into each of them which doesn&#8217;t hurt their stock price.</p>
<p>Each new product has a Sustainability Value Commitment that shows how it relates to the greater good which boosts their SRI status. With such a huge diverse realm of global products, it’s important to know that each one has a sustainability value. Not only does this value increase the sustainability of 3M as a company, but it also allows customers to maintain their sustainability goals.</p>
<h2>A Socially Responsible Investment (SRI) Starts with Placing Your Money Behind Socially Responsible Companies with High Standards</h2>
<p>When it comes time for you to buy into a U.S based, or any global ethical company so you can earn money on your investment, you have to decide what you consider ethical. Oil companies are considered a high ethical risk investment, but some are better than others. A few oil companies have a huge investment in finding ways to expand their portfolio and want to transition away from oil raising their standards up high and beyond the abuse of the Earth. They have the potential to become SRI stocks.</p>
<p>By doing some research you can buy in on the ground floor of investments poised to boom high once they&#8217;re listed as a company with social responsibility on their list of priorities and SRI status on the horizon. Being green is the new way of the global economic environment.</p>
<p>Whether it is ESG, environmental practices, or socially responsible companies, SRI in ethical companies with high standards let&#8217;s you rest easy with your portfolio of investments.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ethical-companies-to-invest-in/">Top 10 Ethical Companies to Invest in for 2021</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">MrStocks.org</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/ethical-companies-to-invest-in/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Best stock traders to follow</title>
		<link>/best-stock-traders-to-follow/</link>
					<comments>/best-stock-traders-to-follow/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Maximilian Weber]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 14:04:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://demos.pokatheme.com/pokatheme/?p=69</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Nulla faucibus nunc turpis, eu tristique sem efficitur et. Morbi quis turpis velit. Duis ultricies iaculis ipsum ac interdum. Aenean feugiat mollis metus sit amet dapibus. Mauris quis neque mauris. Quisque eleifend elit et augue condimentum fermentum. Fusce gravida condimentum dolor in fermentum. Donec lacinia nibh id [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/best-stock-traders-to-follow/">Best stock traders to follow</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">MrStocks.org</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Nulla faucibus nunc turpis, eu tristique sem efficitur et. Morbi quis turpis velit. Duis ultricies iaculis ipsum ac interdum. Aenean feugiat mollis metus sit amet dapibus. Mauris quis neque mauris. Quisque eleifend elit et augue condimentum fermentum. Fusce gravida condimentum dolor in fermentum.</p>
<p>Donec lacinia nibh id metus vehicula varius. Nunc vulputate ut eros nec auctor. Praesent vestibulum turpis id tellus egestas, id auctor tellus vestibulum. Suspendisse varius lacus ac nisl iaculis, rhoncus volutpat nunc cursus. Praesent et massa elit. Cras consectetur, dui a mollis consequat, sem nunc tempus arcu, sollicitudin vehicula nibh turpis id nisi. Curabitur vestibulum turpis quis libero fringilla feugiat. Nullam vitae metus aliquet, volutpat ligula eget, gravida nibh. Nullam et urna suscipit, malesuada ante quis, lobortis diam. Suspendisse malesuada tellus ac dui molestie viverra.</p>
<p>Nulla facilisi. Donec elementum nunc vitae diam viverra ullamcorper. Integer ut erat elit. Nunc elementum consequat varius. Sed posuere dictum interdum. Phasellus ut posuere libero, sit amet fringilla neque. Proin malesuada quam a facilisis fringilla. Integer semper, nibh at interdum commodo, tortor orci vulputate odio, a pellentesque erat ex id dui. Suspendisse a venenatis est. Quisque vehicula congue convallis. Vivamus pellentesque consectetur urna, sed porttitor risus malesuada eget. Class aptent taciti sociosqu ad litora torquent per conubia nostra, per inceptos himenaeos. Praesent semper tincidunt cursus. Maecenas id auctor ante. Aenean at mattis ante, eu pharetra nulla.</p>
<p>Pellentesque ac mi vel eros vulputate accumsan id tincidunt quam. Morbi in maximus tellus. Maecenas dictum aliquet odio. Aenean mollis posuere auctor. Fusce vehicula quis ex non mollis. Aliquam sem libero, fringilla vestibulum justo non, sagittis tempus lectus. Etiam ullamcorper ipsum ipsum, at sagittis mi commodo sollicitudin. Fusce ut finibus augue. Donec fermentum magna orci, et convallis arcu facilisis nec. Nullam ac lectus non mi pharetra sollicitudin interdum quis quam. Fusce scelerisque sed nisi non egestas. Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Fusce nibh elit, maximus non justo non, iaculis aliquam dui. Ut porta, metus sit amet eleifend interdum, dolor tellus rhoncus ex, non eleifend nisl arcu sed eros. Praesent enim justo, semper in finibus a, consequat sagittis eros. Interdum et malesuada fames ac ante ipsum primis in faucibus.</p>
<p>Maecenas magna ante, gravida a urna sed, porttitor pulvinar tortor. Praesent ullamcorper ultrices dolor, et suscipit dolor. Cras sollicitudin vel libero vitae maximus. Mauris ultrices leo nibh, id finibus elit vehicula suscipit. Nam id aliquet massa, sit amet pretium odio. Quisque sit amet ante et dolor ornare vulputate. Cras in quam gravida, blandit massa vel, tempor leo. Donec accumsan at velit non malesuada. Mauris accumsan ligula a pretium efficitur. Quisque luctus convallis efficitur. Integer quis sodales enim. Etiam a ultrices risus. Pellentesque tincidunt mollis porta. Phasellus venenatis elementum felis, vitae ullamcorper nibh gravida in. Vestibulum et sollicitudin tortor, a imperdiet neque.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/best-stock-traders-to-follow/">Best stock traders to follow</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">MrStocks.org</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/best-stock-traders-to-follow/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
